{
  "name": "JPDB 20K",
  "cards":[
    {
      "question": "鴨",
      "answer": "かも",
      "meaning": "duck, easy mark, sucker, sitting duck"
    },
    {
      "question": "好き好む",
      "answer": "すきこのむ",
      "meaning": "to do something by choice, to like, to be fond of"
    },
    {
      "question": "間延び",
      "answer": "まのび",
      "meaning": "taking a long time, slowness, sluggishness, lack of firmness, looseness, slovenliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔う",
      "answer": "とむらう,とぶらう",
      "meaning": "to mourn for, to grieve for, to condole with (the bereaved family, etc.), to hold a memorial service"
    },
    {
      "question": "稚拙",
      "answer": "ちせつ",
      "meaning": "unskillful, childish, immature, naive, artless, clumsy, crude"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳す",
      "answer": "やくす",
      "meaning": "to translate, to interpret"
    },
    {
      "question": "擁する",
      "answer": "ようする",
      "meaning": "to have, to possess"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇宙空間",
      "answer": "うちゅうくうかん",
      "meaning": "outer space, void of space"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄則",
      "answer": "てっそく",
      "meaning": "ironclad rule, inviolable rule, invariable principle, iron law"
    },
    {
      "question": "智",
      "answer": "ち",
      "meaning": "wisdom, jnana (higher knowledge)"
    },
    {
      "question": "藪",
      "answer": "やぶ",
      "meaning": "thicket, bush, grove, scrub, (medical) quack"
    },
    {
      "question": "矢印",
      "answer": "やじるし",
      "meaning": "arrow (symbol), (romantic) interest (for a certain person), direction (of one's attention, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "千里眼",
      "answer": "せんりがん",
      "meaning": "clairvoyance, second sight, clairvoyant"
    },
    {
      "question": "綱渡り",
      "answer": "つなわたり",
      "meaning": "tightrope walking, high-wire act, funambulism, treading a tightrope, walking on thin ice, pulling a"
    },
    {
      "question": "投獄",
      "answer": "とうごく",
      "meaning": "imprisonment, incarceration"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸め込む",
      "answer": "まるめこむ",
      "meaning": "to coax, to cajole, to wheedle, to win over, to seduce, to roll up and put into (something), to bund"
    },
    {
      "question": "門前",
      "answer": "もんぜん,メンゼン",
      "meaning": "before the gate, in front of the gate, one's hand being completely concealed, not having called any"
    },
    {
      "question": "尿道",
      "answer": "にょうどう",
      "meaning": "urethra"
    },
    {
      "question": "初手",
      "answer": "しょて",
      "meaning": "beginning, start"
    },
    {
      "question": "充てる",
      "answer": "あてる",
      "meaning": "to assign, to set aside"
    },
    {
      "question": "入荷",
      "answer": "にゅうか",
      "meaning": "arrival of goods, goods received"
    },
    {
      "question": "白ける",
      "answer": "しらける",
      "meaning": "to be dampened (of the mood, interest, etc.), to be spoiled (e.g. of the atmosphere), to become subd"
    },
    {
      "question": "自律",
      "answer": "じりつ",
      "meaning": "autonomy (philosophy), self-control"
    },
    {
      "question": "照射",
      "answer": "しょうしゃ,ともし",
      "meaning": "irradiation, radiation, beaming, exposure (to light), illumination, baiting deer with a lighted torc"
    },
    {
      "question": "凪",
      "answer": "なぎ",
      "meaning": "calm (at sea), lull"
    },
    {
      "question": "郷",
      "answer": "さと,きょう,ごう",
      "meaning": "village, hamlet, countryside, country, hometown, rural township (of China), 50-home township (compri"
    },
    {
      "question": "目上",
      "answer": "めうえ",
      "meaning": "superior, superiors, senior"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝袋",
      "answer": "ねぶくろ",
      "meaning": "sleeping bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "平面",
      "answer": "へいめん",
      "meaning": "level surface, plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "楓",
      "answer": "かえで,かえるで,ふう",
      "meaning": "maple (tree) (Acer spp.), Formosan sweetgum (Liquidambar formosana)"
    },
    {
      "question": "公務員",
      "answer": "こうむいん",
      "meaning": "government worker, public servant, civil servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "行商",
      "answer": "ぎょうしょう",
      "meaning": "monger, peddling"
    },
    {
      "question": "末っ子",
      "answer": "すえっこ",
      "meaning": "youngest child"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙腺",
      "answer": "るいせん",
      "meaning": "tear gland, lacrimal gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "難問",
      "answer": "なんもん",
      "meaning": "perplexity, difficult question, difficult problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭髪",
      "answer": "とうはつ",
      "meaning": "hair (on the head)"
    },
    {
      "question": "離縁",
      "answer": "りえん",
      "meaning": "divorce, dissolution of adoption"
    },
    {
      "question": "釈明",
      "answer": "しゃくめい",
      "meaning": "explanation, vindication"
    },
    {
      "question": "御心",
      "answer": "みこころ",
      "meaning": "(another's) spirit, God's heart or spirit (in Christianity), Lord's will"
    },
    {
      "question": "血流",
      "answer": "けつりゅう",
      "meaning": "bloodstream, blood flow"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷却",
      "answer": "れいきゃく",
      "meaning": "cooling, refrigeration"
    },
    {
      "question": "非合法",
      "answer": "ひごうほう",
      "meaning": "illegal, unlawful"
    },
    {
      "question": "関門",
      "answer": "かんもん",
      "meaning": "barrier, checkpoint, gateway, hurdle, obstacle, trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "咎め",
      "answer": "とがめ",
      "meaning": "blame, censure, rebuke, reproof"
    },
    {
      "question": "一点張り",
      "answer": "いってんばり",
      "meaning": "persistence, single-mindedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "同居人",
      "answer": "どうきょにん",
      "meaning": "person living with a family, lodger, housemate, flatmate, roommate"
    },
    {
      "question": "目録",
      "answer": "もくろく",
      "meaning": "catalogue, catalog, inventory, index, list, certificate indicating an impending gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "横領",
      "answer": "おうりょう",
      "meaning": "embezzlement, misappropriation, usurpation"
    },
    {
      "question": "失",
      "answer": "しつ",
      "meaning": "loss (of something), disadvantage, mistake, error, failure, flaw, defect"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅黒い",
      "answer": "あさぐろい",
      "meaning": "dark (skin, complexion, etc.), swarthy, tanned"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ",
      "answer": "ぬれ",
      "meaning": "wetting, love affair, lover"
    },
    {
      "question": "願い出る",
      "answer": "ねがいでる",
      "meaning": "to ask for, to apply for, to make an application for, to file a request for, to submit (e.g. one's r"
    },
    {
      "question": "土手",
      "answer": "どて",
      "meaning": "embankment, bank, beef sinew stewed in miso and mirin"
    },
    {
      "question": "役回り",
      "answer": "やくまわり",
      "meaning": "role, part, duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "苗",
      "answer": "なえ,ミャオ,びょう",
      "meaning": "seedling, young plant, rice seedling, Miao (people), Hmong"
    },
    {
      "question": "十二時",
      "answer": "じゅうにじ",
      "meaning": "twelve o'clock, noon, midnight"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗野",
      "answer": "そや",
      "meaning": "rustic, rude, vulgar, rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "家主",
      "answer": "やぬし,いえぬし,いえあるじ",
      "meaning": "landlord, landlady, house owner, home owner, head of the household"
    },
    {
      "question": "意識不明",
      "answer": "いしきふめい",
      "meaning": "unconscious, senseless"
    },
    {
      "question": "参列",
      "answer": "さんれつ",
      "meaning": "attendance, participation, presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "双眼鏡",
      "answer": "そうがんきょう",
      "meaning": "binoculars, field glasses"
    },
    {
      "question": "体系",
      "answer": "たいけい",
      "meaning": "system, organization, organisation, architecture"
    },
    {
      "question": "春日",
      "answer": "しゅんじつ,はるひ,はるび",
      "meaning": "spring day, spring sunlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "総攻撃",
      "answer": "そうこうげき",
      "meaning": "all-out attack, general offensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し借り",
      "answer": "かしかり",
      "meaning": "lending and borrowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "翌年",
      "answer": "よくねん,よくとし",
      "meaning": "following year"
    },
    {
      "question": "茸",
      "answer": "きのこ,たけ",
      "meaning": "mushroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "一筋縄",
      "answer": "ひとすじなわ",
      "meaning": "(piece of) rope, ordinary method"
    },
    {
      "question": "防護",
      "answer": "ぼうご",
      "meaning": "protection"
    },
    {
      "question": "性急",
      "answer": "せいきゅう",
      "meaning": "hasty, rash, rushed, hurried, impatient, impetuous, quick-tempered"
    },
    {
      "question": "見出し",
      "answer": "みだし",
      "meaning": "heading, headline, title, caption, index, headword"
    },
    {
      "question": "大金持ち",
      "answer": "おおがねもち,おおかねもち",
      "meaning": "very rich person, the super rich"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き缶",
      "answer": "あきかん",
      "meaning": "empty can"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏を返す",
      "answer": "うらをかえす",
      "meaning": "to turn inside out, to turn the other way, to turn (something) over, to look at (something) from ano"
    },
    {
      "question": "妬み",
      "answer": "ねたみ,そねみ",
      "meaning": "jealousy, envy"
    },
    {
      "question": "十月",
      "answer": "じゅうがつ",
      "meaning": "October, tenth month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "驚異",
      "answer": "きょうい",
      "meaning": "wonder, miracle, amazement, prodigy"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧知",
      "answer": "きゅうち",
      "meaning": "old friend, old acquaintance"
    },
    {
      "question": "強制力",
      "answer": "きょうせいりょく",
      "meaning": "compelling force, legal force"
    },
    {
      "question": "いい迷惑",
      "answer": "いいめいわく",
      "meaning": "real nuisance, becoming inconvenienced by someone else's problems (through no fault of one's own)"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜水艦",
      "answer": "せんすいかん",
      "meaning": "submarine"
    },
    {
      "question": "親交",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "intimacy, friendship, friendly relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "路面",
      "answer": "ろめん",
      "meaning": "road surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "入試",
      "answer": "にゅうし",
      "meaning": "entrance examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "甚だ",
      "answer": "はなはだ",
      "meaning": "very, greatly, exceedingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "最短距離",
      "answer": "さいたんきょり",
      "meaning": "shortest distance (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄生虫",
      "answer": "きせいちゅう",
      "meaning": "parasite"
    },
    {
      "question": "酸欠",
      "answer": "さんけつ",
      "meaning": "oxygen deficiency, oxygen shortage, lack of oxygen"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗因",
      "answer": "はいいん",
      "meaning": "cause of defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "吟遊詩人",
      "answer": "ぎんゆうしじん",
      "meaning": "troubadour, minstrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り心地",
      "answer": "のりごこち",
      "meaning": "one's feeling while riding, comfort (of a vehicle), ride quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "扮する",
      "answer": "ふんする",
      "meaning": "to dress up as, to disguise oneself as, to play the role of"
    },
    {
      "question": "楔",
      "answer": "くさび",
      "meaning": "wedge, chock, linchpin, lynchpin, tie, bond"
    },
    {
      "question": "原初",
      "answer": "げんしょ",
      "meaning": "origin, source, beginning, starting point"
    },
    {
      "question": "王朝",
      "answer": "おうちょう",
      "meaning": "dynasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "平行線",
      "answer": "へいこうせん",
      "meaning": "parallel lines, remaining far apart (e.g. in discussions), not reaching an agreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "標本",
      "answer": "ひょうほん",
      "meaning": "example, specimen, sample"
    },
    {
      "question": "最寄り",
      "answer": "もより",
      "meaning": "nearest, closest"
    },
    {
      "question": "空調",
      "answer": "くうちょう",
      "meaning": "air conditioning"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾薬",
      "answer": "だんやく",
      "meaning": "ammunition, ammo"
    },
    {
      "question": "製法",
      "answer": "せいほう",
      "meaning": "manufacturing method, recipe, formula"
    },
    {
      "question": "三昧",
      "answer": "さんまい,ざんまい",
      "meaning": "samadhi (state of intense concentration achieved through meditation), being immersed in, being absor"
    },
    {
      "question": "三段",
      "answer": "さんだん",
      "meaning": "third stage, three stages"
    },
    {
      "question": "自炊",
      "answer": "じすい",
      "meaning": "cooking for oneself, cooking one's own food, doing one's own cooking, making food oneself, self-cate"
    },
    {
      "question": "杏",
      "answer": "あんず",
      "meaning": "apricot (Prunus armeniaca)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懲罰",
      "answer": "ちょうばつ",
      "meaning": "discipline, punishment, reprimand"
    },
    {
      "question": "大自然",
      "answer": "だいしぜん",
      "meaning": "nature, Mother Nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯飲み",
      "answer": "ゆのみ",
      "meaning": "teacup"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子校",
      "answer": "じょしこう",
      "meaning": "girls' school"
    },
    {
      "question": "揚げ物",
      "answer": "あげもの",
      "meaning": "deep-fried food"
    },
    {
      "question": "威信",
      "answer": "いしん",
      "meaning": "prestige, dignity"
    },
    {
      "question": "近郊",
      "answer": "きんこう",
      "meaning": "outskirts, environs (of a city), surrounding area, surroundings"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦り寄る",
      "answer": "すりよる",
      "meaning": "to draw close to, to edge up to, to snuggle up to, to nestle close to, to cuddle with, to draw close"
    },
    {
      "question": "同列",
      "answer": "どうれつ",
      "meaning": "same row, same line, same file, same rank, same level, same category, same treatment"
    },
    {
      "question": "碌な",
      "answer": "ろくな",
      "meaning": "satisfactory, decent"
    },
    {
      "question": "配給",
      "answer": "はいきゅう",
      "meaning": "distribution (e.g. films, rice), rationing (e.g. food, gasoline), food ration"
    },
    {
      "question": "秋葉原",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "熱狂的",
      "answer": "ねっきょうてき",
      "meaning": "wildly enthusiastic, crazy (about something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "用意周到",
      "answer": "よういしゅうとう",
      "meaning": "very careful, thoroughly prepared"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗っける",
      "answer": "のっける",
      "meaning": "to place on (something), to give (someone) a ride, to give a lift, to pick up, to help on board"
    },
    {
      "question": "不可侵",
      "answer": "ふかしん",
      "meaning": "inviolability, nonaggression, sacredness"
    },
    {
      "question": "光明",
      "answer": "こうみょう,こうめい",
      "meaning": "bright light, hope, bright future, light emanating from a buddha or bodhisattva, symbolizing their w"
    },
    {
      "question": "滲みる",
      "answer": "しみる",
      "meaning": "to pierce, to penetrate, to soak in, to permeate, to be infected (with vice), to be steeped (with pr"
    },
    {
      "question": "従僕",
      "answer": "じゅうぼく",
      "meaning": "attendant male servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "圧巻",
      "answer": "あっかん",
      "meaning": "highlight, best part, stunning, incredible, superb"
    },
    {
      "question": "鶴",
      "answer": "つる,たず",
      "meaning": "crane (any bird of the family Gruidae, esp. the red-crowned crane, Grus japonensis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "時代遅れ",
      "answer": "じだいおくれ",
      "meaning": "old-fashioned, behind the times, out-of-date, antiquated"
    },
    {
      "question": "静める",
      "answer": "しずめる",
      "meaning": "to appease, to suppress, to calm"
    },
    {
      "question": "凱旋",
      "answer": "がいせん",
      "meaning": "triumphal return"
    },
    {
      "question": "当選",
      "answer": "とうせん",
      "meaning": "being elected, being selected (to win a prize, etc.), winning (in a lottery, raffle, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "相続",
      "answer": "そうぞく",
      "meaning": "succession, inheritance"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗い",
      "answer": "あらい",
      "meaning": "coarse, rough"
    },
    {
      "question": "内定",
      "answer": "ないてい",
      "meaning": "unofficial offer (esp. job offer), tentative decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "醜聞",
      "answer": "しゅうぶん",
      "meaning": "scandal"
    },
    {
      "question": "媒介",
      "answer": "ばいかい",
      "meaning": "mediation, agency, serving as a medium, acting as an intermediary, acting as a go-between, carrying"
    },
    {
      "question": "筋違い",
      "answer": "すじちがい,すじかい",
      "meaning": "cramp, sprain, crick, strain (muscle), unreasonableness, absurdity, illogical, unreasonable, misdire"
    },
    {
      "question": "余命",
      "answer": "よめい",
      "meaning": "remainder of one's life, one's remaining days, time left (to live)"
    },
    {
      "question": "出資",
      "answer": "しゅっし",
      "meaning": "investment, contribution, financing"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き立つ",
      "answer": "うきたつ",
      "meaning": "to be enlivened, to be exhilarated"
    },
    {
      "question": "財閥",
      "answer": "ざいばつ",
      "meaning": "zaibatsu, financial conglomerate, industrial group"
    },
    {
      "question": "握り",
      "answer": "にぎり",
      "meaning": "grasping, gripping, grasp, grip, clutch, handful, fistful, handle, knob, rice ball, nigirizushi, han"
    },
    {
      "question": "似顔絵",
      "answer": "にがおえ",
      "meaning": "portrait, likeness, sketch (of a face)"
    },
    {
      "question": "息女",
      "answer": "そくじょ",
      "meaning": "(your, his, her) daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "食料品",
      "answer": "しょくりょうひん",
      "meaning": "foodstuff, groceries"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊撃",
      "answer": "ゆうげき",
      "meaning": "raid, military attack by a mobile unit, hit-and-run attack, search-and-kill mission, search-and-dest"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊的",
      "answer": "れいてき",
      "meaning": "spiritual, incorporeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "澄ます",
      "answer": "すます",
      "meaning": "to clear, to make clear, to be unruffled, to look unconcerned, to feign indifference, to look demure"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝飯前",
      "answer": "あさめしまえ",
      "meaning": "very easy, piece of cake, child's play, easy as pie, cinch, before breakfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "金銀",
      "answer": "きんぎん",
      "meaning": "gold and silver, money"
    },
    {
      "question": "来す",
      "answer": "きたす",
      "meaning": "to cause, to induce, to bring about a result or state, to produce"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き込む",
      "answer": "つきこむ",
      "meaning": "to thrust (something) into (something), to cram, to stuff, to shove, to plunge into, to charge into,"
    },
    {
      "question": "日傘",
      "answer": "ひがさ",
      "meaning": "parasol (esp. one carried in the hand), sunshade"
    },
    {
      "question": "温度差",
      "answer": "おんどさ",
      "meaning": "difference in temperature, difference in degrees of enthusiasm, interest, commitment, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "武官",
      "answer": "ぶかん",
      "meaning": "military or naval officer"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟成",
      "answer": "じゅくせい",
      "meaning": "maturing, ripening, aging, ageing, curing, fermenting"
    },
    {
      "question": "語彙",
      "answer": "ごい",
      "meaning": "vocabulary, lexicon, lexis, terminology"
    },
    {
      "question": "二の舞",
      "answer": "にのまい",
      "meaning": "... all over again (repeating the same failure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "自問自答",
      "answer": "じもんじとう",
      "meaning": "answering one's own question, wondering to oneself, soliloquizing, soliloquising"
    },
    {
      "question": "強硬",
      "answer": "きょうこう",
      "meaning": "firm, strong, unbending, unyielding, uncompromising, stubborn, tough, hard-line"
    },
    {
      "question": "納屋",
      "answer": "なや",
      "meaning": "shed, barn, outhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸出",
      "answer": "ゆしゅつ,しゅしゅつ",
      "meaning": "export, exportation, efferent"
    },
    {
      "question": "落差",
      "answer": "らくさ",
      "meaning": "difference in elevation (between two points in a body of water), head, drop (e.g. of a waterfall), f"
    },
    {
      "question": "同罪",
      "answer": "どうざい",
      "meaning": "same crime, being equally guilty"
    },
    {
      "question": "雅",
      "answer": "みやび,が",
      "meaning": "refinement, elegance, grace, festal song (genre of the Shi Jing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け渡し",
      "answer": "うけわたし",
      "meaning": "delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "現段階",
      "answer": "げんだんかい",
      "meaning": "present stage, current phase, current rank, present grade"
    },
    {
      "question": "二言",
      "answer": "にごん,にげん,ふたこと",
      "meaning": "double-dealing, double tongue, going back on what one has said, repeating oneself, two words, repeti"
    },
    {
      "question": "力関係",
      "answer": "ちからかんけい",
      "meaning": "power relationship"
    },
    {
      "question": "火柱",
      "answer": "ひばしら",
      "meaning": "pillar of fire, blazing column"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾み",
      "answer": "はずみ",
      "meaning": "bounce, spring, rebound, momentum, impetus, impulse, stimulus, inertia, moment, instant, chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "週刊誌",
      "answer": "しゅうかんし",
      "meaning": "weekly publication, weekly magazine"
    },
    {
      "question": "労働力",
      "answer": "ろうどうりょく",
      "meaning": "labor, labour, manpower, working force"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲台",
      "answer": "ほうだい",
      "meaning": "(gun) battery, fort"
    },
    {
      "question": "明朝",
      "answer": "みょうちょう,みんちょう",
      "meaning": "tomorrow morning, Ming dynasty (China, 1368-1644), Ming (typeface), Minchō"
    },
    {
      "question": "教徒",
      "answer": "きょうと",
      "meaning": "believer, adherent"
    },
    {
      "question": "山菜",
      "answer": "さんさい",
      "meaning": "edible wild plants"
    },
    {
      "question": "出荷",
      "answer": "しゅっか",
      "meaning": "shipping, shipment, forwarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "咎",
      "answer": "とが",
      "meaning": "error, mistake, fault, sin, wrongdoing, offense"
    },
    {
      "question": "激闘",
      "answer": "げきとう",
      "meaning": "fierce fighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "資産家",
      "answer": "しさんか",
      "meaning": "wealthy person"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯れ木",
      "answer": "かれき",
      "meaning": "dead tree, withered tree, leafless tree, bare tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "蚊帳の外",
      "answer": "かやのそと",
      "meaning": "being excluded, being ignored, being kept in the dark (about), being kept out of the loop, outside t"
    },
    {
      "question": "謀略",
      "answer": "ぼうりゃく",
      "meaning": "strategy, stratagem, trick, scheme, plot"
    },
    {
      "question": "事案",
      "answer": "じあん",
      "meaning": "concern, circumstance which is becoming a problem, case (court)"
    },
    {
      "question": "身辺",
      "answer": "しんぺん",
      "meaning": "one's person, around one's person"
    },
    {
      "question": "眩む",
      "answer": "くらむ",
      "meaning": "to be dazzled by, to be dizzied by, to be disoriented by, to be lost in (greed, lust, etc.), to beco"
    },
    {
      "question": "水辺",
      "answer": "みずべ,すいへん",
      "meaning": "waterside, waterfront"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽譜",
      "answer": "がくふ",
      "meaning": "score, sheet music"
    },
    {
      "question": "一八",
      "answer": "いちはつ",
      "meaning": "wall iris, roof iris, Iris tectorum, fleur-de-lis"
    },
    {
      "question": "事細か",
      "answer": "ことこまか",
      "meaning": "detailed, minute"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟師",
      "answer": "りょうし",
      "meaning": "hunter, huntsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し隠す",
      "answer": "おしかくす",
      "meaning": "to cover up, to conceal"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒む",
      "answer": "すさむ",
      "meaning": "to grow wild, to run to waste, to become degenerate, to become rough (of art, craft, etc.), to lose"
    },
    {
      "question": "一級",
      "answer": "いっきゅう",
      "meaning": "one grade, first-class, primary"
    },
    {
      "question": "出頭",
      "answer": "しゅっとう",
      "meaning": "appearance, presence, attendance, surrender (e.g. to the police), turning oneself in"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁石",
      "answer": "じしゃく,じせき",
      "meaning": "magnet, compass"
    },
    {
      "question": "色恋",
      "answer": "いろこい",
      "meaning": "sensual love, love affair"
    },
    {
      "question": "武道",
      "answer": "ぶどう",
      "meaning": "martial arts, military arts, Bushido"
    },
    {
      "question": "感傷的",
      "answer": "かんしょうてき",
      "meaning": "sentimental, emotional, maudlin, mawkish"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭巾",
      "answer": "ずきん,ときん",
      "meaning": "hood, kerchief, black headgear worn by yamabushi"
    },
    {
      "question": "実直",
      "answer": "じっちょく",
      "meaning": "honest, steady"
    },
    {
      "question": "二号",
      "answer": "にごう",
      "meaning": "number two, mistress, concubine"
    },
    {
      "question": "主治医",
      "answer": "しゅじい",
      "meaning": "attending physician, physician in charge, (one's) family doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "女好き",
      "answer": "おんなずき",
      "meaning": "fondness for women, woman admirer, lustful man, being attractive to women, being a lady-killer"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙案",
      "answer": "みょうあん",
      "meaning": "ingenious idea, excellent plan, bright idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣室",
      "answer": "りんしつ",
      "meaning": "next or adjoining room"
    },
    {
      "question": "前後左右",
      "answer": "ぜんごさゆう",
      "meaning": "in all directions"
    },
    {
      "question": "下劣",
      "answer": "げれつ",
      "meaning": "base, mean, vulgar, despicable, low"
    },
    {
      "question": "汗臭い",
      "answer": "あせくさい",
      "meaning": "smell(ing) of sweat"
    },
    {
      "question": "社交的",
      "answer": "しゃこうてき",
      "meaning": "sociable"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃紺",
      "answer": "のうこん",
      "meaning": "dark blue"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁",
      "answer": "りょう,すなどり",
      "meaning": "fishing, gathering seafood (e.g. clams, seaweed), catch (e.g. of fish), haul, collecting shells, fis"
    },
    {
      "question": "横柄",
      "answer": "おうへい",
      "meaning": "arrogant, haughty, insolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼福",
      "answer": "がんぷく",
      "meaning": "a sight for sore eyes, seeing something beautiful or precious"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒塗り",
      "answer": "くろぬり",
      "meaning": "blackened, black-painted, black-lacquered, blackened thing"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし物",
      "answer": "おとしもの",
      "meaning": "lost property, something dropped and left behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲食",
      "answer": "いんしょく,おんじき",
      "meaning": "food and drink, eating and drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "酷薄",
      "answer": "こくはく",
      "meaning": "cruel, inhumane, callous, brutal"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き替え",
      "answer": "ひきかえ",
      "meaning": "exchange, conversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "燻製",
      "answer": "くんせい",
      "meaning": "smoked food, smoking (fish, meat, etc.), smoked"
    },
    {
      "question": "学術",
      "answer": "がくじゅつ",
      "meaning": "science, learning, scholarship, arts and sciences, academic pursuits"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝票",
      "answer": "でんぴょう",
      "meaning": "chit, sales slip, voucher"
    },
    {
      "question": "脛",
      "answer": "すね,はぎ",
      "meaning": "shin, shank, lower leg"
    },
    {
      "question": "出過ぎる",
      "answer": "ですぎる",
      "meaning": "to stick out too much, to protrude too far, to be too strong (e.g. of tea), to be too forward, to be"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒っぽい",
      "answer": "くろっぽい",
      "meaning": "dark, blackish"
    },
    {
      "question": "髪形",
      "answer": "かみがた",
      "meaning": "hair style, coiffure, hairdo"
    },
    {
      "question": "隔たり",
      "answer": "へだたり",
      "meaning": "distance, interval, gap, difference, estrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "未亡人",
      "answer": "みぼうじん",
      "meaning": "widow"
    },
    {
      "question": "古典的",
      "answer": "こてんてき",
      "meaning": "classical, classic"
    },
    {
      "question": "男根",
      "answer": "だんこん",
      "meaning": "penis, phallus"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳つい",
      "answer": "いかつい",
      "meaning": "stern, grim, rough, rugged, forbidding, overbearing, square (shoulders)"
    },
    {
      "question": "業績",
      "answer": "ぎょうせき",
      "meaning": "achievement, performance, results, work, contribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "主食",
      "answer": "しゅしょく",
      "meaning": "staple food"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃れる",
      "answer": "すたれる",
      "meaning": "to go out of use, to become obsolete, to die out, to go out of fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "原点",
      "answer": "げんてん",
      "meaning": "starting point, origin, beginning, origin (of coordinate axes), datum point"
    },
    {
      "question": "本文",
      "answer": "ほんぶん,ほんもん",
      "meaning": "text (of a book, document, etc.), body (of a letter), this passage, this sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "餌付け",
      "answer": "えづけ",
      "meaning": "artificial feeding, accustoming wild animals to eating food given by humans"
    },
    {
      "question": "結社",
      "answer": "けっしゃ",
      "meaning": "association, society"
    },
    {
      "question": "従属",
      "answer": "じゅうぞく",
      "meaning": "subordination, dependency"
    },
    {
      "question": "貞操",
      "answer": "ていそう",
      "meaning": "chastity, virtue, fidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻物",
      "answer": "まきもの",
      "meaning": "scroll, rolled book, makimono, scarf, muffler, stole, sushi made rolled in nori seaweed with a core"
    },
    {
      "question": "難色",
      "answer": "なんしょく",
      "meaning": "disapproval"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠隔操作",
      "answer": "えんかくそうさ",
      "meaning": "remote control, remote operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "新参者",
      "answer": "しんざんもの",
      "meaning": "newcomer, neophyte, novice, newbie"
    },
    {
      "question": "併用",
      "answer": "へいよう",
      "meaning": "using together (jointly), used at the same time"
    },
    {
      "question": "背ける",
      "answer": "そむける",
      "meaning": "to turn (one's face) away, to avert (one's eyes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "天命",
      "answer": "てんめい",
      "meaning": "God's will, heaven's decree, mandate of Heaven, fate, karma, destiny, one's life, one's lifespan"
    },
    {
      "question": "各個",
      "answer": "かっこ",
      "meaning": "every one, each"
    },
    {
      "question": "憲兵",
      "answer": "けんぺい",
      "meaning": "military police"
    },
    {
      "question": "下調べ",
      "answer": "したしらべ",
      "meaning": "preliminary investigation, preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "商売人",
      "answer": "しょうばいにん",
      "meaning": "merchant, trader, shrewd businessman, expert (in a trade or profession), professional, woman working"
    },
    {
      "question": "根負け",
      "answer": "こんまけ",
      "meaning": "being beaten by one's opponent's persistence, being outlasted, running out of patience, giving in, s"
    },
    {
      "question": "北上",
      "answer": "ほくじょう",
      "meaning": "going north"
    },
    {
      "question": "農場",
      "answer": "のうじょう",
      "meaning": "farm (agriculture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "涙ながら",
      "answer": "なみだながら",
      "meaning": "while crying, in tears"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕府",
      "answer": "ばくふ",
      "meaning": "bakufu, shogunate"
    },
    {
      "question": "一昨年",
      "answer": "おととし,いっさくねん",
      "meaning": "year before last"
    },
    {
      "question": "生首",
      "answer": "なまくび",
      "meaning": "freshly severed head"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈折",
      "answer": "くっせつ",
      "meaning": "bending, curving, twisting, turning, winding, warping (of feelings, logic, etc.), distortion, refrac"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人称",
      "answer": "いちにんしょう",
      "meaning": "first person"
    },
    {
      "question": "律",
      "answer": "りつ",
      "meaning": "law (esp. ancient East Asian criminal code), regulation, vinaya (rules for the monastic community),"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕送り",
      "answer": "しおくり",
      "meaning": "allowance, remittance, sending (someone) an allowance"
    },
    {
      "question": "笠",
      "answer": "かさ",
      "meaning": "conical hat (East-Asian style), coolie hat, something shaped like a conical hat or an umbrella, shad"
    },
    {
      "question": "処方",
      "answer": "しょほう",
      "meaning": "prescription, formulation, formula, recipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "後任",
      "answer": "こうにん",
      "meaning": "successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "早計",
      "answer": "そうけい",
      "meaning": "overhasty, rash, premature"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝する",
      "answer": "しゅくする",
      "meaning": "to congratulate, to celebrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "風潮",
      "answer": "ふうちょう",
      "meaning": "tide, current, tendency, trend"
    },
    {
      "question": "持論",
      "answer": "じろん",
      "meaning": "one's cherished opinion, pet theory"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い物",
      "answer": "つかいもの",
      "meaning": "useful thing, usable article"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲者",
      "answer": "くせもの",
      "meaning": "ruffian, villain, knave, thief, suspicious fellow, peculiar person, idiosyncratic person, stubborn f"
    },
    {
      "question": "長兄",
      "answer": "ちょうけい",
      "meaning": "eldest brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子力",
      "answer": "じょしりょく",
      "meaning": "woman's level of motivation in fashion, makeup, taste in clothes, etc., femininity"
    },
    {
      "question": "心掛ける",
      "answer": "こころがける",
      "meaning": "to keep in mind, to bear in mind, to try, to aim to do, to endeavor, to endeavour"
    },
    {
      "question": "給う",
      "answer": "たまう,たもう",
      "meaning": "to give, to do ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "権能",
      "answer": "けんのう",
      "meaning": "authority, power, function"
    },
    {
      "question": "一節",
      "answer": "いっせつ,ひとふし",
      "meaning": "a verse (e.g. in the Bible), stanza, paragraph, passage, a joint, section, a tune, note, strain, mea"
    },
    {
      "question": "名作",
      "answer": "めいさく",
      "meaning": "masterpiece"
    },
    {
      "question": "崩れ",
      "answer": "くずれ",
      "meaning": "crumbling, collapse, ruin, has-been, wannabe"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲子園",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "旅先",
      "answer": "たびさき",
      "meaning": "destination, goal (of travel), place one stays during a journey"
    },
    {
      "question": "蹴破る",
      "answer": "けやぶる",
      "meaning": "to break (by kicking), to kick down (e.g. a door), to kick open, to break down, to break open, to sm"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽傷",
      "answer": "けいしょう",
      "meaning": "minor injury"
    },
    {
      "question": "来世",
      "answer": "らいせ,らいせい",
      "meaning": "the next world, the hereafter, life after death"
    },
    {
      "question": "過労",
      "answer": "かろう",
      "meaning": "overwork, strain"
    },
    {
      "question": "抑圧",
      "answer": "よくあつ",
      "meaning": "check, restraint, oppression, suppression"
    },
    {
      "question": "非番",
      "answer": "ひばん",
      "meaning": "off duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "胎児",
      "answer": "たいじ",
      "meaning": "fetus, foetus, embryo, unborn child"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴態",
      "answer": "ちたい",
      "meaning": "foolishness, silliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "実務",
      "answer": "じつむ",
      "meaning": "practical business, practical work experience, practicum, practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "独り立ち",
      "answer": "ひとりだち",
      "meaning": "being independent, standing on one's own, becoming independent"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴徒",
      "answer": "ぼうと",
      "meaning": "insurgent, rioter, mob"
    },
    {
      "question": "煽り",
      "answer": "あおり",
      "meaning": "gust (of wind), blast, influence, impact, instigation, agitation, incitement, tailgating, low angle"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁書",
      "answer": "きんしょ",
      "meaning": "banning of books, banned book"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾げる",
      "answer": "かしげる,かたげる",
      "meaning": "to tilt (esp. head), to lean, to incline, to slant"
    },
    {
      "question": "抱き込む",
      "answer": "だきこむ",
      "meaning": "to hold in one's arms, to bring over a person to one's side, to involve"
    },
    {
      "question": "一因",
      "answer": "いちいん",
      "meaning": "one cause, one reason, one factor"
    },
    {
      "question": "長袖",
      "answer": "ながそで",
      "meaning": "long sleeves"
    },
    {
      "question": "坑道",
      "answer": "こうどう",
      "meaning": "tunnel, (mining) gallery, level, shaft, pit"
    },
    {
      "question": "触れ合い",
      "answer": "ふれあい",
      "meaning": "contact, connectedness, rapport, mutual touching"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴漢",
      "answer": "ぼうかん",
      "meaning": "hoodlum, ruffian"
    },
    {
      "question": "形勢",
      "answer": "けいせい",
      "meaning": "condition, situation, prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "上野",
      "answer": "こうずけ",
      "meaning": "Kōzuke (former province located in present-day Gunma Prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "染み出す",
      "answer": "しみだす",
      "meaning": "to ooze (out), to seep"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄目",
      "answer": "うすめ",
      "meaning": "slight, thin, on the weak side, half-open eyes, half-closed eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "発露",
      "answer": "はつろ",
      "meaning": "appearance, expression, manifestation"
    },
    {
      "question": "萎む",
      "answer": "しぼむ",
      "meaning": "to wither (of flowers, dreams, etc.), to wilt, to droop, to shrivel, to fade (away), to sag, to defl"
    },
    {
      "question": "金になる",
      "answer": "かねになる",
      "meaning": "profitable, lucrative"
    },
    {
      "question": "瀬戸際",
      "answer": "せとぎわ",
      "meaning": "brink, critical moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "葬り去る",
      "answer": "ほうむりさる",
      "meaning": "to consign to oblivion"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋路",
      "answer": "こいじ",
      "meaning": "romance, love's pathway"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻筋",
      "answer": "はなすじ",
      "meaning": "bridge of nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "祖",
      "answer": "おや,そ",
      "meaning": "founder, inventor, ancestor, forefather, progenitor, originator, pioneer, grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "得心",
      "answer": "とくしん",
      "meaning": "consenting to, being convinced of, being satisfied, understanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "密やか",
      "answer": "ひそやか",
      "meaning": "quiet, still, surreptitious"
    },
    {
      "question": "金糸",
      "answer": "きんし",
      "meaning": "gold thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼拝",
      "answer": "れいはい,らいはい",
      "meaning": "worship (esp. Christian), adoration, divine service, worship (esp. Buddhist and Shinto)"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い討ち",
      "answer": "おいうち",
      "meaning": "attacking a fleeing enemy, additional attack on a weakened enemy, additional blow to an already unfo"
    },
    {
      "question": "厚手",
      "answer": "あつで",
      "meaning": "thick (paper, cloth, etc.), heavy"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄泉",
      "answer": "こうせん,よみ",
      "meaning": "underground spring, Hades, hell, underworld"
    },
    {
      "question": "縋り付く",
      "answer": "すがりつく",
      "meaning": "to cling to, to depend on, to embrace, to hug"
    },
    {
      "question": "靴底",
      "answer": "くつぞこ",
      "meaning": "sole (of a shoe), sole (fish)"
    },
    {
      "question": "感化",
      "answer": "かんか",
      "meaning": "influence, inspiration, reform, correction"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜這い",
      "answer": "よばい",
      "meaning": "creeping at night into a woman's bedroom, stealing into a girl's bedroom at night to make love, snea"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘付く",
      "answer": "かんづく",
      "meaning": "to sense, to suspect, to get an inkling (of something), to get wind of, to smell (e.g. danger), to b"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦虫",
      "answer": "にがむし",
      "meaning": "bitter-tasting bug"
    },
    {
      "question": "一代",
      "answer": "いちだい",
      "meaning": "generation, lifetime, age"
    },
    {
      "question": "過大評価",
      "answer": "かだいひょうか",
      "meaning": "overestimation, overvaluing"
    },
    {
      "question": "若い者",
      "answer": "わかいもの",
      "meaning": "young man, young woman, young people, youth, youngsters, young employee, young manservant, young fol"
    },
    {
      "question": "登山",
      "answer": "とざん",
      "meaning": "mountain climbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "狙い撃ち",
      "answer": "ねらいうち",
      "meaning": "sharpshooting, shooting, sniping, setting a goal and carrying it out"
    },
    {
      "question": "不明瞭",
      "answer": "ふめいりょう",
      "meaning": "dimness, obscurity, indistinctness, unclear, unintelligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "戻り",
      "answer": "もどり",
      "meaning": "return, reaction, recovery, return (from a procedure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "血液型",
      "answer": "けつえきがた",
      "meaning": "blood type, blood group"
    },
    {
      "question": "稀有",
      "answer": "けう,きゆう",
      "meaning": "rare, uncommon"
    },
    {
      "question": "自警団",
      "answer": "じけいだん",
      "meaning": "vigilance committee, vigilante corps"
    },
    {
      "question": "初陣",
      "answer": "ういじん",
      "meaning": "one's first campaign, one's first battle"
    },
    {
      "question": "遮蔽物",
      "answer": "しゃへいぶつ",
      "meaning": "shelter, cover, screen, shield, obstruction, defilade"
    },
    {
      "question": "ひ弱",
      "answer": "ひよわ",
      "meaning": "weak, delicate, sickly"
    },
    {
      "question": "力無い",
      "answer": "ちからない",
      "meaning": "feeble"
    },
    {
      "question": "射貫く",
      "answer": "いぬく",
      "meaning": "to shoot through something (wall, body, etc.), to pierce (e.g. with an arrow or a look)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誘発",
      "answer": "ゆうはつ",
      "meaning": "inducing, causing, triggering, giving rise to"
    },
    {
      "question": "回り道",
      "answer": "まわりみち",
      "meaning": "detour, diversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "覇者",
      "answer": "はしゃ",
      "meaning": "supreme ruler, conqueror, champion, winner, titleholder"
    },
    {
      "question": "引率",
      "answer": "いんそつ",
      "meaning": "leading, guiding, commanding"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨雲",
      "answer": "あまぐも",
      "meaning": "rain cloud"
    },
    {
      "question": "覗き見",
      "answer": "のぞきみ",
      "meaning": "peeking, peeping (e.g. through a hole, narrow gap)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱風",
      "answer": "ねっぷう",
      "meaning": "hot wind"
    },
    {
      "question": "空耳",
      "answer": "そらみみ",
      "meaning": "mishearing, (feigned) deafness, homophonic translation of song lyrics for comic effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "外人",
      "answer": "がいじん,ほかびと",
      "meaning": "foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗",
      "answer": "じょう",
      "meaning": "(nth) power, counter for vehicles, multiplication, Buddha's teachings"
    },
    {
      "question": "一等",
      "answer": "いっとう",
      "meaning": "first-class, first-rank, A1, the most, the best"
    },
    {
      "question": "後先",
      "answer": "あとさき",
      "meaning": "front and rear, before and after, both ends, beginning and end, order, consequences, context"
    },
    {
      "question": "粥",
      "answer": "かゆ,しゅく,かい",
      "meaning": "thin rice porridge, watery cooked rice, rice gruel, congee, breakfast (in Zen temples)"
    },
    {
      "question": "即興",
      "answer": "そっきょう",
      "meaning": "improvisation, improvised, impromptu, extempore, ad-lib, off-the-cuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "固まり",
      "answer": "かたまり",
      "meaning": "lump, mass, bundle, clump, clod, cluster, group, crowd, embodiment (of an idea, quality, feeling etc"
    },
    {
      "question": "四苦八苦",
      "answer": "しくはっく",
      "meaning": "being in dire distress, being hard put to it, the four and eight kinds of suffering"
    },
    {
      "question": "身振り",
      "answer": "みぶり",
      "meaning": "gesture, gesticulation, motion"
    },
    {
      "question": "様変わり",
      "answer": "さまがわり",
      "meaning": "changing completely, transformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鴉",
      "answer": "からす",
      "meaning": "crow (Corvus spp.), raven"
    },
    {
      "question": "付き人",
      "answer": "つきびと",
      "meaning": "assistant (esp. in show business or sumo), attendant, chaperon"
    },
    {
      "question": "小太り",
      "answer": "こぶとり",
      "meaning": "plump"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲哀",
      "answer": "ひあい",
      "meaning": "sorrow, grief, sadness"
    },
    {
      "question": "水上",
      "answer": "すいじょう,みなかみ",
      "meaning": "aquatic, on the water, headwaters, source"
    },
    {
      "question": "時代劇",
      "answer": "じだいげき",
      "meaning": "historical play, period drama"
    },
    {
      "question": "停学",
      "answer": "ていがく",
      "meaning": "suspension from school"
    },
    {
      "question": "嚥下",
      "answer": "えんげ,えんか",
      "meaning": "swallowing, deglutition"
    },
    {
      "question": "内政",
      "answer": "ないせい",
      "meaning": "domestic affairs, internal administration"
    },
    {
      "question": "上階",
      "answer": "じょうかい",
      "meaning": "floor above, floor upstairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "等身大",
      "answer": "とうしんだい",
      "meaning": "life-size, life-sized, true-to-life, faithful (depiction), realistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽き足る",
      "answer": "あきたる,あきだる",
      "meaning": "to be satisfied"
    },
    {
      "question": "人心",
      "answer": "じんしん,ひとごころ",
      "meaning": "human nature, human heart, human spirit, kindness, sympathy"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇道",
      "answer": "わきみち",
      "meaning": "side road, byroad, digression (e.g. from argument)"
    },
    {
      "question": "江戸時代",
      "answer": "えどじだい",
      "meaning": "Edo period (1603-1868 CE)"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑空",
      "answer": "かっくう",
      "meaning": "gliding (through the air)"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮込み",
      "answer": "にこみ",
      "meaning": "stew, hodgepodge"
    },
    {
      "question": "学生服",
      "answer": "がくせいふく",
      "meaning": "school uniform"
    },
    {
      "question": "海域",
      "answer": "かいいき",
      "meaning": "area of ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "昂る",
      "answer": "たかぶる",
      "meaning": "to become aroused (of emotions, nerves, etc.), to become excited, to become stirred up, to become wo"
    },
    {
      "question": "罰則",
      "answer": "ばっそく",
      "meaning": "punishment, penalty, penal regulations, penal code"
    },
    {
      "question": "楯",
      "answer": "たて",
      "meaning": "shield, buckler, escutcheon, pretext"
    },
    {
      "question": "橘",
      "answer": "たちばな",
      "meaning": "tachibana orange (Citrus tachibana)"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸能",
      "answer": "げいのう",
      "meaning": "public entertainment, performing arts, accomplishments, attainments"
    },
    {
      "question": "期する",
      "answer": "きする,ごする",
      "meaning": "to fix (a time, date, etc.), to set, to expect, to hope for, to look forward to, to foresee, to anti"
    },
    {
      "question": "針金",
      "answer": "はりがね",
      "meaning": "wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘴",
      "answer": "くちばし,はし",
      "meaning": "beak, bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱力感",
      "answer": "だつりょくかん",
      "meaning": "ennui, languishing, feeling of exhaustion, lassitude, lethargy"
    },
    {
      "question": "街路",
      "answer": "がいろ",
      "meaning": "road, street, avenue"
    },
    {
      "question": "題名",
      "answer": "だいめい",
      "meaning": "title, caption, heading"
    },
    {
      "question": "内々",
      "answer": "うちうち,ないない",
      "meaning": "private, confidential, informal, secret, (within the) family circle, (on the) inside"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷心",
      "answer": "しょうしん",
      "meaning": "heartbreak, grief, sorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "両家",
      "answer": "りょうけ",
      "meaning": "both families"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲求不満",
      "answer": "よっきゅうふまん",
      "meaning": "frustration"
    },
    {
      "question": "罵詈雑言",
      "answer": "ばりぞうごん",
      "meaning": "all manner of (verbal) abuse, all kinds of names, abusive language, torrent of abuse, stream of insu"
    },
    {
      "question": "直ぐ",
      "answer": "すぐ",
      "meaning": "immediately, at once, right away, directly, soon, before long, shortly, easily, readily, without dif"
    },
    {
      "question": "隼人",
      "answer": "はやひと,はやと,はいと",
      "meaning": "people who lived in Kyushu in ancient times, and who opposed the state of Yamato"
    },
    {
      "question": "札束",
      "answer": "さつたば",
      "meaning": "roll of banknotes"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛威",
      "answer": "もうい",
      "meaning": "fury, power, menace"
    },
    {
      "question": "道程",
      "answer": "みちのり,どうてい",
      "meaning": "distance, journey, itinerary, path (e.g. to one's goal), way, process, route, road"
    },
    {
      "question": "新居",
      "answer": "しんきょ",
      "meaning": "new home"
    },
    {
      "question": "桟橋",
      "answer": "さんばし,さんきょう",
      "meaning": "wharf, bridge, jetty, pier"
    },
    {
      "question": "胃液",
      "answer": "いえき",
      "meaning": "gastric juice"
    },
    {
      "question": "居残り",
      "answer": "いのこり",
      "meaning": "working overtime, detention, being kept in (e.g. after school)"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤沢",
      "answer": "じゅんたく",
      "meaning": "abundant, ample, plentiful, affluent, lustrous, glossy"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬眠",
      "answer": "とうみん",
      "meaning": "hibernation, winter sleep, torpor"
    },
    {
      "question": "両名",
      "answer": "りょうめい",
      "meaning": "both persons"
    },
    {
      "question": "小汚い",
      "answer": "こぎたない",
      "meaning": "somehow dirty, slightly dirty, dingy, somewhat base, vaguely underhanded"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳳凰",
      "answer": "ほうおう",
      "meaning": "Chinese firebird, Chinese phoenix"
    },
    {
      "question": "程々",
      "answer": "ほどほど",
      "meaning": "moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆光",
      "answer": "ぎゃっこう",
      "meaning": "backlight (in photography, etc.), illumination (of the subject) from behind"
    },
    {
      "question": "血潮",
      "answer": "ちしお",
      "meaning": "blood spilt from the body, blood circulating within the body (often as a metaphor for strong emotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "猛々しい",
      "answer": "たけだけしい",
      "meaning": "ferocious, fierce, audacious, impudent, shameless, brazen"
    },
    {
      "question": "番長",
      "answer": "ばんちょう",
      "meaning": "leader of a group of juvenile delinquents"
    },
    {
      "question": "博打",
      "answer": "ばくち",
      "meaning": "gambling, gaming, speculation, undertaking a risky venture, professional gambler, gamester"
    },
    {
      "question": "貧乏人",
      "answer": "びんぼうにん",
      "meaning": "poor person, pauper, the poor, the indigent"
    },
    {
      "question": "上向く",
      "answer": "うわむく,うえむく",
      "meaning": "to point upward, to look upward, to improve"
    },
    {
      "question": "精力的",
      "answer": "せいりょくてき",
      "meaning": "energetic, vigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "仇討ち",
      "answer": "あだうち",
      "meaning": "vengeance, revenge, retaliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "荘",
      "answer": "しょう,そう,チャン",
      "meaning": "manor, villa, counter for games of mahjong"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭領",
      "answer": "とうりょう",
      "meaning": "head, chief, boss"
    },
    {
      "question": "目安",
      "answer": "めやす",
      "meaning": "criterion, standard, yardstick, reference, aim, rough estimate, approximation"
    },
    {
      "question": "弁護人",
      "answer": "べんごにん",
      "meaning": "counsel, defender, advocate"
    },
    {
      "question": "初心",
      "answer": "しょしん,うぶ",
      "meaning": "original intention, initial resolution, innocent, naive, unsophisticated, inexperienced, green, wet"
    },
    {
      "question": "片手間",
      "answer": "かたてま",
      "meaning": "spare time, free time, leisure time"
    },
    {
      "question": "荷造り",
      "answer": "にづくり",
      "meaning": "packing, baling, crating"
    },
    {
      "question": "十全",
      "answer": "じゅうぜん",
      "meaning": "perfection, thoroughness, consummation"
    },
    {
      "question": "漬ける",
      "answer": "つける",
      "meaning": "to soak (in), to steep, to dip, to dunk, to pickle, to preserve (in salt, vinegar, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "受注",
      "answer": "じゅちゅう",
      "meaning": "accepting an order, receiving an order, orders received"
    },
    {
      "question": "座敷",
      "answer": "ざしき",
      "meaning": "tatami room, tatami mat room, formal Japanese room, dinner party in a tatami room (esp. when a geish"
    },
    {
      "question": "居城",
      "answer": "きょじょう",
      "meaning": "castle of a feudal lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "中将",
      "answer": "ちゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "lieutenant general, vice-admiral"
    },
    {
      "question": "伯母",
      "answer": "おば,はくぼ",
      "meaning": "aunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "世継ぎ",
      "answer": "よつぎ",
      "meaning": "heir, successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "加算",
      "answer": "かさん",
      "meaning": "addition, adding, supplement"
    },
    {
      "question": "身悶え",
      "answer": "みもだえ",
      "meaning": "writhing (in agony)"
    },
    {
      "question": "匙",
      "answer": "さじ,しゃじ,かい",
      "meaning": "spoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "推移",
      "answer": "すいい",
      "meaning": "transition, change, progress, development, shift, passing (of time)"
    },
    {
      "question": "代替わり",
      "answer": "だいがわり",
      "meaning": "taking over (e.g. store or family's headship), subrogation, substitution of one person for another ("
    },
    {
      "question": "盛況",
      "answer": "せいきょう",
      "meaning": "success, prosperity, boom"
    },
    {
      "question": "見劣り",
      "answer": "みおとり",
      "meaning": "unfavourable comparison, unfavorable comparison"
    },
    {
      "question": "時分",
      "answer": "じぶん",
      "meaning": "time, hour, season, time of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "叩き割る",
      "answer": "たたきわる",
      "meaning": "to smash, to break into pieces"
    },
    {
      "question": "残り香",
      "answer": "のこりが,のこりか",
      "meaning": "lingering scent, lingering fragrance, residual aroma"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽団",
      "answer": "がくだん",
      "meaning": "orchestra, band"
    },
    {
      "question": "市役所",
      "answer": "しやくしょ",
      "meaning": "municipal office, council, city hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "総理",
      "answer": "そうり",
      "meaning": "prime minister (as the head of a cabinet government), premier, leading, overseeing, leader, overseer"
    },
    {
      "question": "入店",
      "answer": "にゅうてん",
      "meaning": "starting to work in a shop, joining a shop as an employee, going inside a shop, opening up a shop (i"
    },
    {
      "question": "空き家",
      "answer": "あきや",
      "meaning": "vacant house, unoccupied house"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガン見",
      "answer": "ガンみ",
      "meaning": "gazing at, staring at fixedly, eyeballing, glaring, giving a hard look"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹の虫",
      "answer": "はらのむし",
      "meaning": "roundworm (Ascaris lumbricoides), mawworm, intestinal worm, (metaphor for) location of one's feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "旬",
      "answer": "しゅん,じゅん",
      "meaning": "season (e.g. fruit, fish), in vogue, popular, fresh, up to date, ten-day period (in a month), ten-ye"
    },
    {
      "question": "煉瓦",
      "answer": "れんが",
      "meaning": "brick"
    },
    {
      "question": "不遇",
      "answer": "ふぐう",
      "meaning": "misfortune, ill fate, bad luck, obscurity"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏差値",
      "answer": "へんさち",
      "meaning": "deviation value (usu. scaled to mean of 50, standard deviation of 10, and often used for academic gr"
    },
    {
      "question": "全快",
      "answer": "ぜんかい",
      "meaning": "complete recovery of health"
    },
    {
      "question": "人命",
      "answer": "じんめい",
      "meaning": "(human) life"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り紙",
      "answer": "はりがみ",
      "meaning": "paper patch, paper backing, poster, sticker, label"
    },
    {
      "question": "七不思議",
      "answer": "ななふしぎ",
      "meaning": "seven wonders (of a particular area), total mystery, enigma, conundrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼気",
      "answer": "こき",
      "meaning": "exhaled air, exhalation, expiration"
    },
    {
      "question": "無秩序",
      "answer": "むちつじょ",
      "meaning": "disorder, chaos, confusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳命",
      "answer": "げんめい",
      "meaning": "strict order, peremptory command"
    },
    {
      "question": "挫く",
      "answer": "くじく",
      "meaning": "to sprain, to twist, to dampen (enthusiasm), to discourage, to dishearten, to dispirit, to depress,"
    },
    {
      "question": "一興",
      "answer": "いっきょう",
      "meaning": "amusement, fun, brief entertainment"
    },
    {
      "question": "当代",
      "answer": "とうだい",
      "meaning": "the present age, these days, (present) head of the family"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛烈",
      "answer": "つうれつ",
      "meaning": "severe, bitter, scathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "勢揃い",
      "answer": "せいぞろい",
      "meaning": "array, muster, line-up, full force"
    },
    {
      "question": "火曜日",
      "answer": "かようび",
      "meaning": "Tuesday"
    },
    {
      "question": "上辺",
      "answer": "うわべ,じょうへん",
      "meaning": "exterior, surface, outside, outward appearance, looks, upper side (go, chess, othello board)"
    },
    {
      "question": "代替",
      "answer": "だいたい,だいがえ,だいがわり",
      "meaning": "substitution, alternation, alternative, substitute, taking over (e.g. store or family's headship), s"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄笑い",
      "answer": "うすわらい",
      "meaning": "faint smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣窟",
      "answer": "そうくつ",
      "meaning": "den, haunt, hangout, nest, lair"
    },
    {
      "question": "馴れる",
      "answer": "なれる",
      "meaning": "to get used to, to grow accustomed to, to become familiar with, to become skilled in, to become expe"
    },
    {
      "question": "国宝",
      "answer": "こくほう",
      "meaning": "national treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "善は急げ",
      "answer": "ぜんはいそげ",
      "meaning": "move with haste (when you have no doubts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "食む",
      "answer": "はむ",
      "meaning": "to eat (fodder, grass, etc.), to receive (a salary), to receive a stipend from one's lord"
    },
    {
      "question": "海老",
      "answer": "えび",
      "meaning": "prawn, shrimp, lobster, crayfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻が高い",
      "answer": "はながたかい",
      "meaning": "proud, having a prominent nose"
    },
    {
      "question": "陳列",
      "answer": "ちんれつ",
      "meaning": "exhibition, display, putting on show"
    },
    {
      "question": "御礼",
      "answer": "おれい,おんれい",
      "meaning": "thanks, gratitude, manners, etiquette, bow, reward, gift, ceremony, ritual"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘆願",
      "answer": "たんがん",
      "meaning": "entreaty, appeal, petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "看取る",
      "answer": "みとる",
      "meaning": "to care for (the sick), to nurse, to attend (someone's deathbed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "桐",
      "answer": "きり",
      "meaning": "paulownia (Paulownia tomentosa), empress tree, foxglove tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "臭気",
      "answer": "しゅうき",
      "meaning": "bad smell, stink"
    },
    {
      "question": "宣誓",
      "answer": "せんせい",
      "meaning": "oath, abjuration, pledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "少なめ",
      "answer": "すくなめ",
      "meaning": "somewhat below, slightly below"
    },
    {
      "question": "悠久",
      "answer": "ゆうきゅう",
      "meaning": "eternity, perpetuity, permanence"
    },
    {
      "question": "母体",
      "answer": "ぼたい",
      "meaning": "mother's body (esp. when pregnant or after giving birth), parent body, parent organization, base, ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "音響",
      "answer": "おんきょう",
      "meaning": "sound, noise, acoustics, reverberation, echo, audio"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠心力",
      "answer": "えんしんりょく",
      "meaning": "centrifugal force"
    },
    {
      "question": "時給",
      "answer": "じきゅう",
      "meaning": "hourly pay, hourly wage"
    },
    {
      "question": "感情移入",
      "answer": "かんじょういにゅう",
      "meaning": "empathy"
    },
    {
      "question": "多様",
      "answer": "たよう",
      "meaning": "diverse, varied"
    },
    {
      "question": "家庭的",
      "answer": "かていてき",
      "meaning": "family-oriented, familial"
    },
    {
      "question": "接合",
      "answer": "せつごう",
      "meaning": "union, joining, conjugation"
    },
    {
      "question": "活路",
      "answer": "かつろ",
      "meaning": "means of survival, means of escape, way out of a difficulty"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き払う",
      "answer": "ひきはらう",
      "meaning": "to vacate, to move out"
    },
    {
      "question": "押収",
      "answer": "おうしゅう",
      "meaning": "seizure, confiscation"
    },
    {
      "question": "二次",
      "answer": "にじ",
      "meaning": "second, secondary, quadratic (function, equation, etc.), second-order"
    },
    {
      "question": "革靴",
      "answer": "かわぐつ",
      "meaning": "leather shoes, leather boots"
    },
    {
      "question": "妬ましい",
      "answer": "ねたましい",
      "meaning": "jealous, envious"
    },
    {
      "question": "加味",
      "answer": "かみ",
      "meaning": "seasoning, flavoring, flavouring, addition, inclusion, taking into account"
    },
    {
      "question": "順応",
      "answer": "じゅんのう,じゅんおう",
      "meaning": "adaptation, accommodation, conforming, adjustment, acclimatization, acclimatisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗装",
      "answer": "とそう",
      "meaning": "coating, painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "創設",
      "answer": "そうせつ",
      "meaning": "establishment, founding, organization, organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "烈火",
      "answer": "れっか",
      "meaning": "raging fire, conflagration"
    },
    {
      "question": "既成事実",
      "answer": "きせいじじつ",
      "meaning": "established fact, fait accompli"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人っ子",
      "answer": "ひとりっこ",
      "meaning": "(an) only child"
    },
    {
      "question": "力添え",
      "answer": "ちからぞえ",
      "meaning": "help, assistance, service"
    },
    {
      "question": "合金",
      "answer": "ごうきん",
      "meaning": "alloy"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀座",
      "answer": "ぎんざ",
      "meaning": "Ginza (shopping district in Tokyo), (Edo period) silver mint"
    },
    {
      "question": "初歩的",
      "answer": "しょほてき",
      "meaning": "elementary, basic, rudimentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "思慮深い",
      "answer": "しりょぶかい",
      "meaning": "prudent, thoughtful, discreet"
    },
    {
      "question": "和菓子",
      "answer": "わがし",
      "meaning": "wagashi, traditional Japanese confectionery"
    },
    {
      "question": "薔薇色",
      "answer": "ばらいろ",
      "meaning": "rose-colour, rose-color, bright (e.g. life, future, prospects), cheerful, rosy"
    },
    {
      "question": "引力",
      "answer": "いんりょく",
      "meaning": "attraction (e.g. magnetic, gravitation), affinity, gravitational pull, attractiveness, magnetism"
    },
    {
      "question": "色仕掛け",
      "answer": "いろじかけ",
      "meaning": "use of seductive techniques to attain one's ends (usu. of women)"
    },
    {
      "question": "温和",
      "answer": "おんわ",
      "meaning": "mild (climate), temperate, clement, pleasant, agreeable, gentle (nature, personality, etc.), mild, q"
    },
    {
      "question": "照れ屋",
      "answer": "てれや",
      "meaning": "shy, a very shy person"
    },
    {
      "question": "呪力",
      "answer": "じゅりょく",
      "meaning": "magical power, mystical force"
    },
    {
      "question": "至宝",
      "answer": "しほう",
      "meaning": "greatest treasure, most valuable asset, pride (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂犬",
      "answer": "きょうけん",
      "meaning": "mad dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "解禁",
      "answer": "かいきん",
      "meaning": "lifting a ban, raising an embargo, opening a season (hunting, fishing, etc.), publishing contents, r"
    },
    {
      "question": "利子",
      "answer": "りし",
      "meaning": "interest (on a loan, deposit, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙に巻く",
      "answer": "けむにまく,けむりにまく",
      "meaning": "to confuse (someone), to befuddle, to bewilder, to mystify, to throw up a smokescreen, to surround w"
    },
    {
      "question": "洒落",
      "answer": "しゃらく,しゃれ,しゃら",
      "meaning": "free and easy, open-hearted, relaxed, not fussy, frank, joke, pun, jest, witticism, wordplay, smartl"
    },
    {
      "question": "着衣",
      "answer": "ちゃくい,ちゃくえ",
      "meaning": "clothes (that one is wearing), wearing clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "汽車",
      "answer": "きしゃ",
      "meaning": "train (esp. long distance train), steam train"
    },
    {
      "question": "採寸",
      "answer": "さいすん",
      "meaning": "taking measurements"
    },
    {
      "question": "財",
      "answer": "ざい,たから",
      "meaning": "fortune, riches, goods, incorporated foundation, treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "素っ裸",
      "answer": "すっぱだか",
      "meaning": "nudity, stark naked, in one's bare skin, penniless"
    },
    {
      "question": "恵む",
      "answer": "めぐむ",
      "meaning": "to bless, to show mercy to, to give (money, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "実を結ぶ",
      "answer": "みをむすぶ",
      "meaning": "to bear fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺青",
      "answer": "しせい,いれずみ",
      "meaning": "tattoo (esp. a traditional Japanese one), tattooing"
    },
    {
      "question": "式神",
      "answer": "しきがみ",
      "meaning": "form of magic or divination (e.g. animating objects to act as the sorcerer's agent)"
    },
    {
      "question": "堤防",
      "answer": "ていぼう",
      "meaning": "bank, weir, embankment, levee"
    },
    {
      "question": "微量",
      "answer": "びりょう",
      "meaning": "minuscule amount, extremely small quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "多用",
      "answer": "たよう",
      "meaning": "busyness, a lot of things to do, frequent use, heavy use (of), many uses"
    },
    {
      "question": "手ずから",
      "answer": "てずから",
      "meaning": "in person, personally, (do) oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "奢り",
      "answer": "おごり",
      "meaning": "luxury, extravagance, treat (i.e. at somebody's expense)"
    },
    {
      "question": "先鋒",
      "answer": "せんぽう",
      "meaning": "advance guard, vanguard, athlete who competes in the first match of a team competition (kendo, judo,"
    },
    {
      "question": "少数派",
      "answer": "しょうすうは",
      "meaning": "minority group (party), minority"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰り",
      "answer": "かげり",
      "meaning": "shadow or cloud (e.g. on someone's happiness), shade, gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "谷底",
      "answer": "たにそこ,たにぞこ",
      "meaning": "valley floor, bottom of a gorge, bottom of a ravine"
    },
    {
      "question": "冊子",
      "answer": "さっし,そうし",
      "meaning": "book, booklet, story book, pamphlet, notebook, written work (esp. a bound text, as opposed to a scro"
    },
    {
      "question": "肩幅",
      "answer": "かたはば",
      "meaning": "shoulder width (breadth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "棄権",
      "answer": "きけん",
      "meaning": "abstention (from voting), renunciation (of a right), withdrawal (from a contest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "審議",
      "answer": "しんぎ",
      "meaning": "deliberation"
    },
    {
      "question": "出払う",
      "answer": "ではらう",
      "meaning": "to be all out (e.g. of people), to be all elsewhere, to be all in use (e.g. of cars), to be sold out"
    },
    {
      "question": "触発",
      "answer": "しょくはつ",
      "meaning": "detonation by contact, contact detonation, touching off (something), triggering, sparking, provocati"
    },
    {
      "question": "救護",
      "answer": "きゅうご",
      "meaning": "relief, aid"
    },
    {
      "question": "磔",
      "answer": "はりつけ,はっつけ,たく",
      "meaning": "execution by tying a victim to a post and stabbing with spears, crucifixion, eighth principle of the"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱屈",
      "answer": "うっくつ",
      "meaning": "gloomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き出す",
      "answer": "かきだす",
      "meaning": "to begin to write, to write out, to export (file), to extract"
    },
    {
      "question": "色違い",
      "answer": "いろちがい",
      "meaning": "variation in color (colour), having a different color"
    },
    {
      "question": "気負い",
      "answer": "きおい",
      "meaning": "eagerness, enthusiasm, fervor, excitement, fighting spirit, fighting mood"
    },
    {
      "question": "見直し",
      "answer": "みなおし",
      "meaning": "review, reconsideration, revision"
    },
    {
      "question": "名人",
      "answer": "めいじん",
      "meaning": "master, expert"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒光り",
      "answer": "くろびかり",
      "meaning": "black lustre, black luster"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞭打つ",
      "answer": "むちうつ",
      "meaning": "to whip, to lash, to give the rod, to spur on, to encourage"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙幣",
      "answer": "しへい",
      "meaning": "paper money, note, bill"
    },
    {
      "question": "運命的",
      "answer": "うんめいてき",
      "meaning": "destined, predestined, fated, fateful"
    },
    {
      "question": "出品",
      "answer": "しゅっぴん",
      "meaning": "exhibiting, showing, putting on display, putting up for sale, entering (a work into a competition),"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡り",
      "answer": "わたり",
      "meaning": "crossing, passage, transit, importing, import, wandering, wanderer, migration, contact, relations, n"
    },
    {
      "question": "口添え",
      "answer": "くちぞえ",
      "meaning": "recommendation, putting in a good word for someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼力",
      "answer": "がんりき,がんりょく",
      "meaning": "insight, power of observation"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑貨",
      "answer": "ざっか",
      "meaning": "miscellaneous goods, general goods, sundries"
    },
    {
      "question": "息継ぎ",
      "answer": "いきつぎ",
      "meaning": "taking a breath (while singing, swimming, etc.), short break, breather"
    },
    {
      "question": "変容",
      "answer": "へんよう",
      "meaning": "change in appearance, transformation"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の手",
      "answer": "ひのて",
      "meaning": "flame, blaze, fire, attack, aggression"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り持つ",
      "answer": "とりもつ",
      "meaning": "to act as a go-between (for), to mediate, to arrange, to entertain (guests), to treat, to receive"
    },
    {
      "question": "幌",
      "answer": "ほろ,とばり",
      "meaning": "canopy (esp. the cloth or canvas used for it), awning, top (of a convertible), hood, helmet cape, cl"
    },
    {
      "question": "狡い",
      "answer": "ずるい,こすい",
      "meaning": "sly, cunning, sneaky, crafty, unfair, dishonest, miserly, mean, stingy"
    },
    {
      "question": "抵抗力",
      "answer": "ていこうりょく",
      "meaning": "(power of) resistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "出し合う",
      "answer": "だしあう",
      "meaning": "to contribute jointly"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り次ぐ",
      "answer": "とりつぐ",
      "meaning": "to act as an agent for, to intermediate, to announce (someone's arrival), to answer (the door, the p"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗雲",
      "answer": "あんうん",
      "meaning": "dark clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "順次",
      "answer": "じゅんじ",
      "meaning": "in order, sequential, seriatim"
    },
    {
      "question": "敬称",
      "answer": "けいしょう",
      "meaning": "title of honour, title of honor"
    },
    {
      "question": "博識",
      "answer": "はくしき",
      "meaning": "extensive knowledge, erudition"
    },
    {
      "question": "排斥",
      "answer": "はいせき",
      "meaning": "rejection, expulsion, boycott, ostracism"
    },
    {
      "question": "大所帯",
      "answer": "おおじょたい",
      "meaning": "large family"
    },
    {
      "question": "破局",
      "answer": "はきょく",
      "meaning": "catastrophe, cataclysm, collapse (of a relationship), breakup, split (friends, lovers, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇役",
      "answer": "わきやく",
      "meaning": "supporting role (actor), minor role"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み切る",
      "answer": "よみきる",
      "meaning": "to finish reading, to read through"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り",
      "answer": "おり",
      "meaning": "opportunity, chance, occasion, time, folding, fold, pleat, crease, small food box (wooden or cardboa"
    },
    {
      "question": "褒賞",
      "answer": "ほうしょう",
      "meaning": "prize, award, reward"
    },
    {
      "question": "覇",
      "answer": "は",
      "meaning": "supremacy (over a nation), hegemony, domination, leadership, championship, victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "梅雨",
      "answer": "つゆ,ばいう",
      "meaning": "rainy season (in Japan usu. from early June to mid-July), rain during the rainy season"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ替え",
      "answer": "いれかえ",
      "meaning": "replacement, substitution, change, shunting (rail), switching"
    },
    {
      "question": "高尚",
      "answer": "こうしょう",
      "meaning": "high, noble, refined, advanced"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣例",
      "answer": "かんれい",
      "meaning": "custom, practice, convention, precedent"
    },
    {
      "question": "桁外れ",
      "answer": "けたはずれ",
      "meaning": "incredible, extraordinary, exceptional, phenomenal"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぶり返す",
      "answer": "ぶりかえす",
      "meaning": "to come back, to return, to recur"
    },
    {
      "question": "命日",
      "answer": "めいにち",
      "meaning": "anniversary of a person's death, monthly return of the date of someone's death"
    },
    {
      "question": "袋小路",
      "answer": "ふくろこうじ",
      "meaning": "blind alley, cul-de-sac, dead end street, deadlock, impasse, dead end"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由行動",
      "answer": "じゆうこうどう",
      "meaning": "free action, free activity, acting at one's own discretion, taking one's own course, free hand, inde"
    },
    {
      "question": "責",
      "answer": "せき",
      "meaning": "responsibility, duty, obligation"
    },
    {
      "question": "強弱",
      "answer": "きょうじゃく",
      "meaning": "strength and weakness, (degree of) strength, stress (of a sound), loudness"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い残す",
      "answer": "おもいのこす",
      "meaning": "to regret"
    },
    {
      "question": "別種",
      "answer": "べっしゅ",
      "meaning": "another kind, distinct species, variety"
    },
    {
      "question": "機種",
      "answer": "きしゅ",
      "meaning": "type of equipment, model"
    },
    {
      "question": "場内",
      "answer": "じょうない",
      "meaning": "in-house, (on) the grounds, (in) the premises, hall, theatre, theater"
    },
    {
      "question": "不仲",
      "answer": "ふなか",
      "meaning": "discord, (on) bad terms (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし",
      "answer": "おとし",
      "meaning": "dropping, losing, missing item, something one forgot to write down, trap, wooden protrusion from a J"
    },
    {
      "question": "不承不承",
      "answer": "ふしょうぶしょう",
      "meaning": "reluctantly, grudgingly, unwillingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "従兄",
      "answer": "じゅうけい,いとこ",
      "meaning": "cousin (elder male)"
    },
    {
      "question": "爛れる",
      "answer": "ただれる",
      "meaning": "to be sore, to be inflamed, to be bleary, to fester, to be dissipated, to be dissolute, to indulge i"
    },
    {
      "question": "流用",
      "answer": "りゅうよう",
      "meaning": "diversion, appropriation (e.g. of funds), misappropriation, re-use (e.g. old computer parts), recycl"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い殺す",
      "answer": "くいころす",
      "meaning": "to devour, to bite to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "親孝行",
      "answer": "おやこうこう",
      "meaning": "filial piety"
    },
    {
      "question": "白目",
      "answer": "しろめ",
      "meaning": "white of the eye, cold, unwelcoming eyes, pewter, solder"
    },
    {
      "question": "医",
      "answer": "い,くすし",
      "meaning": "medicine, the healing art, healing, curing, doctor"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り壊す",
      "answer": "とりこわす",
      "meaning": "to demolish, to tear down, to pull down"
    },
    {
      "question": "白旗",
      "answer": "しらはた,はっき,しろはた",
      "meaning": "white flag, truce flag, surrender flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "妃殿下",
      "answer": "ひでんか",
      "meaning": "princess, Her Royal Highness"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴賓",
      "answer": "きひん",
      "meaning": "noble visitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "清廉",
      "answer": "せいれん",
      "meaning": "honesty, integrity, purity and unselfishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "細腕",
      "answer": "ほそうで",
      "meaning": "thin arm, slender arm, slender means, meager ability to earn a living"
    },
    {
      "question": "菊",
      "answer": "きく",
      "meaning": "chrysanthemum (Chrysanthemum morifolium)"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥地",
      "answer": "おくち,おうち",
      "meaning": "interior, backwoods, hinterland, back regions"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒廃",
      "answer": "こうはい",
      "meaning": "ruin, destruction, devastation, waste, decay"
    },
    {
      "question": "背面",
      "answer": "はいめん",
      "meaning": "rear, back, reverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬の骨",
      "answer": "うまのほね",
      "meaning": "person of doubtful origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "湯浴み",
      "answer": "ゆあみ",
      "meaning": "(taking a) bath, hot spring cure"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏場",
      "answer": "なつば",
      "meaning": "summertime"
    },
    {
      "question": "滲み出す",
      "answer": "しみだす",
      "meaning": "to ooze (out), to seep"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚活",
      "answer": "こんかつ",
      "meaning": "searching for a marriage partner, marriage hunting, activities leading to marriage (e.g. dating, cou"
    },
    {
      "question": "乖離",
      "answer": "かいり",
      "meaning": "divergence, alienation, deviation, estrangement, separation, detachment"
    },
    {
      "question": "群を抜く",
      "answer": "ぐんをぬく",
      "meaning": "to surpass the rest (e.g. of a large group), to stand out from the crowd, to be the best by far"
    },
    {
      "question": "守護神",
      "answer": "しゅごじん,しゅごしん",
      "meaning": "guardian deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐臭",
      "answer": "ふしゅう",
      "meaning": "smell of something rotten, rotten smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "看護",
      "answer": "かんご",
      "meaning": "nursing, (army) nurse"
    },
    {
      "question": "年の頃",
      "answer": "としのころ",
      "meaning": "approximate age, age range"
    },
    {
      "question": "見紛う",
      "answer": "みまがう,みまごう",
      "meaning": "to mistake (A for B), to misread"
    },
    {
      "question": "停戦",
      "answer": "ていせん",
      "meaning": "armistice, ceasefire"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒薬",
      "answer": "どくやく",
      "meaning": "poison"
    },
    {
      "question": "重臣",
      "answer": "じゅうしん",
      "meaning": "chief vassal, senior statesman"
    },
    {
      "question": "格納",
      "answer": "かくのう",
      "meaning": "storage, housing for equipment and machines, putting into computer memory"
    },
    {
      "question": "下敷き",
      "answer": "したじき",
      "meaning": "desk pad, sheet of plastic (or cardboard, felt, etc.) placed under writing paper, underlay, being pi"
    },
    {
      "question": "大司教",
      "answer": "だいしきょう",
      "meaning": "archbishop (Catholic)"
    },
    {
      "question": "護符",
      "answer": "ごふ,ごふう",
      "meaning": "talisman, amulet, charm"
    },
    {
      "question": "首相",
      "answer": "しゅしょう",
      "meaning": "prime minister, chancellor (Germany, Austria, etc.), premier"
    },
    {
      "question": "橙",
      "answer": "だいだい",
      "meaning": "bitter orange (Citrus aurantium), sour orange, Seville orange, orange (color, colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "配合",
      "answer": "はいごう",
      "meaning": "combination, arrangement, distribution, mixture, match, harmony, marrying off"
    },
    {
      "question": "寺院",
      "answer": "じいん",
      "meaning": "Buddhist temple, religious building, church, cathedral, mosque"
    },
    {
      "question": "見取り図",
      "answer": "みとりず",
      "meaning": "rough sketch, floor plan, blueprint"
    },
    {
      "question": "弄する",
      "answer": "ろうする",
      "meaning": "to play with, to joke, to use (esp. trick, sophistry, etc.), to deride, to scoff at, to make fun of"
    },
    {
      "question": "大っぴら",
      "answer": "おおっぴら",
      "meaning": "open, public, overt, free, unreserved, uninhibited"
    },
    {
      "question": "日夜",
      "answer": "にちや",
      "meaning": "day and night, around the clock, always, constantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "酢",
      "answer": "す",
      "meaning": "vinegar"
    },
    {
      "question": "総大将",
      "answer": "そうだいしょう",
      "meaning": "supreme commander"
    },
    {
      "question": "国立",
      "answer": "こくりつ",
      "meaning": "national"
    },
    {
      "question": "看護婦",
      "answer": "かんごふ",
      "meaning": "(female) nurse"
    },
    {
      "question": "近代",
      "answer": "きんだい",
      "meaning": "present day, modern times, recent times, early modern period (in Japan, usu. from the Meiji Restorat"
    },
    {
      "question": "奮う",
      "answer": "ふるう",
      "meaning": "to muster (e.g. one's courage), to call forth, to rouse up, to be enlivened, to be invigorated"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔の手",
      "answer": "まのて",
      "meaning": "evil influence, (evil) clutches, tentacles of evil"
    },
    {
      "question": "犬歯",
      "answer": "けんし",
      "meaning": "eyetooth, cuspid, canine (tooth), dogtooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り子",
      "answer": "うりこ",
      "meaning": "salesperson, shop assistant, hawker, peddler, vendor, male prostitute"
    },
    {
      "question": "実用",
      "answer": "じつよう",
      "meaning": "practical use, utility"
    },
    {
      "question": "衣食住",
      "answer": "いしょくじゅう",
      "meaning": "necessities of life (food, clothing and shelter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "込み入る",
      "answer": "こみいる",
      "meaning": "to be complicated, to be elaborate, to push in, to be crowded"
    },
    {
      "question": "日誌",
      "answer": "にっし",
      "meaning": "journal, log"
    },
    {
      "question": "二刀流",
      "answer": "にとうりゅう",
      "meaning": "two-sword school, style of fencing with one sword in each hand, liking both alcohol and sweets, pers"
    },
    {
      "question": "根を張る",
      "answer": "ねをはる",
      "meaning": "to spread one's roots (of a tree, etc.), to take root (of an ideology, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "願い下げ",
      "answer": "ねがいさげ",
      "meaning": "cancellation, withdrawal, asking to be excused, begging off, not taking, refusing"
    },
    {
      "question": "馬鹿力",
      "answer": "ばかぢから",
      "meaning": "great physical power, animal strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝一",
      "answer": "あさいち",
      "meaning": "first thing in the morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "天啓",
      "answer": "てんけい",
      "meaning": "(divine) revelation, divine oracle"
    },
    {
      "question": "翠",
      "answer": "みどり",
      "meaning": "green, greenery (esp. fresh verdure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大破",
      "answer": "たいは",
      "meaning": "serious damage, drubbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "流麗",
      "answer": "りゅうれい",
      "meaning": "fluent, flowing, elegant"
    },
    {
      "question": "書棚",
      "answer": "しょだな",
      "meaning": "bookshelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心人物",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんじんぶつ",
      "meaning": "leader, central personage"
    },
    {
      "question": "強豪",
      "answer": "きょうごう",
      "meaning": "overwhelming strength, extremely strong person, powerhouse, very strong player, very strong team"
    },
    {
      "question": "短期",
      "answer": "たんき",
      "meaning": "short-term"
    },
    {
      "question": "腑抜ける",
      "answer": "ふぬける",
      "meaning": "to lose one's energy, to be cowardly"
    },
    {
      "question": "町内",
      "answer": "ちょうない",
      "meaning": "neighborhood, neighbourhood, street, block, town"
    },
    {
      "question": "連戦",
      "answer": "れんせん",
      "meaning": "series of battles, successive battles"
    },
    {
      "question": "後ろ髪",
      "answer": "うしろがみ",
      "meaning": "hair on the back of one's head"
    },
    {
      "question": "横倒し",
      "answer": "よこだおし",
      "meaning": "falling over, toppling sideways"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰る",
      "answer": "かげる",
      "meaning": "to darken, to get dark, to be clouded, to be hidden (behind clouds)"
    },
    {
      "question": "世間体",
      "answer": "せけんてい",
      "meaning": "appearance (in the eyes of society), decency"
    },
    {
      "question": "威容",
      "answer": "いよう",
      "meaning": "dignified appearance, majestic appearance, imposing appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "半袖",
      "answer": "はんそで",
      "meaning": "short sleeves"
    },
    {
      "question": "天馬",
      "answer": "てんば,てんま",
      "meaning": "flying horse, Pegasus"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳ね回る",
      "answer": "はねまわる",
      "meaning": "to jump about"
    },
    {
      "question": "厨",
      "answer": "くりや,ちゅう",
      "meaning": "kitchen, (Internet) troll, nerd, freak, addict, fag"
    },
    {
      "question": "往く",
      "answer": "いく,ゆく",
      "meaning": "to go, to move (in a direction or towards a specific location), to head (towards), to be transported"
    },
    {
      "question": "小窓",
      "answer": "こまど",
      "meaning": "small window, fenestella, scuttle (type of hatch on a ship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後見人",
      "answer": "こうけんにん",
      "meaning": "guardian"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗料",
      "answer": "とりょう",
      "meaning": "paints, painting material"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁定",
      "answer": "さいてい,せいてい",
      "meaning": "decision, ruling, award, arbitration"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱",
      "answer": "うつ",
      "meaning": "depression, low spirits, luxuriant (of vegetation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぱっと見",
      "answer": "ぱっとみ",
      "meaning": "(at) a glance, (judging from) appearances"
    },
    {
      "question": "都心",
      "answer": "としん",
      "meaning": "city centre (center) (esp. capital city), urban centre, heart of city a metropolis"
    },
    {
      "question": "瑠璃",
      "answer": "るり",
      "meaning": "lapis lazuli, lapis lazuli (color), beryl, mall blue passerine bird (esp. the blue-and-white flycatc"
    },
    {
      "question": "四大",
      "answer": "よんだい,しだい",
      "meaning": "university or college offering four-year programs, the big four ..., the four major ..., the four el"
    },
    {
      "question": "媚",
      "answer": "こび",
      "meaning": "flattery, cajolery, flirtation"
    },
    {
      "question": "電脳",
      "answer": "でんのう",
      "meaning": "computer, cyberbrain, digital brain"
    },
    {
      "question": "袴",
      "answer": "はかま,パジ,バチ",
      "meaning": "hakama, man's formal divided skirt, traditional Korean pants"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛色",
      "answer": "けいろ",
      "meaning": "hair color, hair colour, fur color, fur colour, disposition, type, kind, nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲張る",
      "answer": "よくばる",
      "meaning": "to covet, to lust for"
    },
    {
      "question": "又",
      "answer": "また",
      "meaning": "again, once more, once again, another time, some other time, also, too, as well, likewise, on the ot"
    },
    {
      "question": "安全圏",
      "answer": "あんぜんけん",
      "meaning": "safety zone, buffer (e.g. against defeat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生易しい",
      "answer": "なまやさしい",
      "meaning": "simple, easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "反復",
      "answer": "はんぷく",
      "meaning": "repetition, iteration, recursion, recurrence, recapitulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "良く言う",
      "answer": "よくいう",
      "meaning": "to say enough (as much as required), to say plenty, to say well, to say cleverly, to say elegantly,"
    },
    {
      "question": "男手",
      "answer": "おとこで,おのこで",
      "meaning": "male help, male labor, male labour, man's handwriting, kanji, man'yōgana written in kaisho or gyōsho"
    },
    {
      "question": "出港",
      "answer": "しゅっこう",
      "meaning": "departure from a port, leaving port, setting sail"
    },
    {
      "question": "誑かす",
      "answer": "たぶらかす",
      "meaning": "to trick, to cheat, to deceive, to seduce"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩味",
      "answer": "しおあじ,えんみ,しおみ",
      "meaning": "salty taste, saltiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸締まり",
      "answer": "とじまり",
      "meaning": "locking up (doors and windows), fastening the doors"
    },
    {
      "question": "窮する",
      "answer": "きゅうする",
      "meaning": "to be hard pressed, to be at a loss, to become poor, to be reduced to poverty"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝心地",
      "answer": "ねごこち",
      "meaning": "sleeping comfort or snugness"
    },
    {
      "question": "幻視",
      "answer": "げんし",
      "meaning": "visual hallucination, vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り倒す",
      "answer": "きりたおす",
      "meaning": "to cut down, to chop down, to fell"
    },
    {
      "question": "金儲け",
      "answer": "かねもうけ",
      "meaning": "money-making, earning money"
    },
    {
      "question": "通告",
      "answer": "つうこく",
      "meaning": "announcement, notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "吐血",
      "answer": "とけつ",
      "meaning": "vomiting of blood"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏道",
      "answer": "うらみち",
      "meaning": "back lane, byway, back street, unfair means, dishonest means"
    },
    {
      "question": "模範",
      "answer": "もはん",
      "meaning": "exemplar, model, example, pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸を打つ",
      "answer": "むねをうつ",
      "meaning": "to be touching, to be moving"
    },
    {
      "question": "一軍",
      "answer": "いちぐん",
      "meaning": "one army, whole army, first string players, the cool kids, the popular kids"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲違い",
      "answer": "なかたがい",
      "meaning": "discord, breaking up (e.g. friendship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "空域",
      "answer": "くういき",
      "meaning": "airspace"
    },
    {
      "question": "転げる",
      "answer": "ころげる",
      "meaning": "to roll over, to tumble, to roll about (with laughter)"
    },
    {
      "question": "片道",
      "answer": "かたみち",
      "meaning": "one-way (trip), one-way ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "実権",
      "answer": "じっけん",
      "meaning": "real power"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻拭い",
      "answer": "しりぬぐい",
      "meaning": "cleaning up somebody else's mess, carrying the can, ass-wiping, arse-wiping"
    },
    {
      "question": "足裏",
      "answer": "あしうら,あなうら",
      "meaning": "sole of the foot"
    },
    {
      "question": "小便",
      "answer": "しょうべん,しょんべん",
      "meaning": "urine, piss, pee, breaking a contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "閃き",
      "answer": "ひらめき",
      "meaning": "flair, flash, insight, flash (of inspiration, wit, etc.), waving (e.g. of a flag in the wind)"
    },
    {
      "question": "中腰",
      "answer": "ちゅうごし",
      "meaning": "half-sitting posture, half-standing posture, half-rising posture, stooping position"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳に残る",
      "answer": "みみにのこる",
      "meaning": "to remain in memory (of sounds and words), to linger in one's ears"
    },
    {
      "question": "館長",
      "answer": "かんちょう",
      "meaning": "superintendent, director, curator, chief librarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "嘯く",
      "answer": "うそぶく",
      "meaning": "to boast, to brag, to recite (a song or poem to oneself), to bark, to roar, to howl"
    },
    {
      "question": "一先ず",
      "answer": "ひとまず",
      "meaning": "for now, for the time being, for the present, though not quite satisfactorily, after a fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "追っ払う",
      "answer": "おっぱらう",
      "meaning": "to chase away, to drive away, to drive out"
    },
    {
      "question": "癒やし",
      "answer": "いやし",
      "meaning": "healing, soothing, therapy, comfort, solace"
    },
    {
      "question": "弱肉強食",
      "answer": "じゃくにくきょうしょく",
      "meaning": "survival of the fittest, the law of the jungle, the weak are meat the strong do eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜色",
      "answer": "きしょく",
      "meaning": "glad countenance, joyful look"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗部",
      "answer": "あんぶ",
      "meaning": "dark side (of nature, town, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無駄死に",
      "answer": "むだじに",
      "meaning": "dying in vain, useless death, meaningless death"
    },
    {
      "question": "賀",
      "answer": "が",
      "meaning": "congratulation, celebration"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱湯",
      "answer": "ねっとう,あつゆ",
      "meaning": "boiling water, warmer than usual bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "残",
      "answer": "ざん",
      "meaning": "remaining, left-over, excess"
    },
    {
      "question": "隔壁",
      "answer": "かくへき",
      "meaning": "barrier wall, bulkhead, partition, septum, diaphragm"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜劇",
      "answer": "きげき",
      "meaning": "comedy, funny show"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼夜",
      "answer": "ちゅうや",
      "meaning": "day and night"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟れる",
      "answer": "うれる,こなれる,なれる",
      "meaning": "to ripen (fruit, grain, etc.), to become ripe, to be digested, to master (a skill), to be proficient"
    },
    {
      "question": "母子",
      "answer": "ぼし,ははこ,おやこ",
      "meaning": "mother and child"
    },
    {
      "question": "小枝",
      "answer": "こえだ",
      "meaning": "twig, spray"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き写す",
      "answer": "かきうつす",
      "meaning": "to transcribe, to copy"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り返す",
      "answer": "おりかえす",
      "meaning": "to turn up (hem, sleeves, etc.), to fold back (e.g. page), to turn back, to double back, to return,"
    },
    {
      "question": "梢",
      "answer": "こずえ",
      "meaning": "treetop, tip of a branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "餓鬼",
      "answer": "がき",
      "meaning": "brat, kid, urchin, little devil, preta, hungry ghost"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂嵐",
      "answer": "すなあらし",
      "meaning": "sandstorm, noise (video), snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "活",
      "answer": "かつ",
      "meaning": "living, life, judo art of resuscitation, action, activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "抉れる",
      "answer": "えぐれる,しゃくれる",
      "meaning": "to be gouged, to be hollowed, to become hollow, to have an underbite, to have a protruding chin, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "竹刀",
      "answer": "しない",
      "meaning": "bamboo sword (for kendo), bamboo fencing stick"
    },
    {
      "question": "工作員",
      "answer": "こうさくいん",
      "meaning": "spy, agent provocateur, covert operative, maker, builder, constructor"
    },
    {
      "question": "算数",
      "answer": "さんすう",
      "meaning": "arithmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "欠如",
      "answer": "けつじょ",
      "meaning": "lack, absence, shortage, deficiency, privation"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄色い声",
      "answer": "きいろいこえ",
      "meaning": "shrill voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒ガス",
      "answer": "どくガス",
      "meaning": "poison gas"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨宿り",
      "answer": "あまやどり",
      "meaning": "taking shelter from rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒々しい",
      "answer": "さむざむしい",
      "meaning": "bleak, chilly, dreary"
    },
    {
      "question": "名義",
      "answer": "めいぎ",
      "meaning": "name (esp. on a deed, contract, etc.), moral duty, justification, pretext"
    },
    {
      "question": "原石",
      "answer": "げんせき",
      "meaning": "(raw) ore, unpolished gemstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "奥手",
      "answer": "おくて",
      "meaning": "late-growing rice, late-ripening crops, late-blooming flowers, late developer (e.g. child who reache"
    },
    {
      "question": "土埃",
      "answer": "つちぼこり",
      "meaning": "dust, cloud of dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "奔る",
      "answer": "はしる",
      "meaning": "to run, to travel (movement of vehicles), to drive, to flow (e.g. energy), to hurry to, to retreat ("
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち止め",
      "answer": "うちどめ",
      "meaning": "end (of play, match, etc.), closing, closing a pachinko machine (after it has paid out its designate"
    },
    {
      "question": "包容力",
      "answer": "ほうようりょく",
      "meaning": "tolerance, broad-mindedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "左遷",
      "answer": "させん",
      "meaning": "demotion, relegation, reduction in rank, degradation, downward move"
    },
    {
      "question": "完備",
      "answer": "かんび",
      "meaning": "(being) fully equipped, (being) fully furnished, completeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "期日",
      "answer": "きじつ,きにち,ごじつ",
      "meaning": "fixed date, settlement date"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗走",
      "answer": "はいそう",
      "meaning": "flight, rout, debacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "獣道",
      "answer": "けものみち",
      "meaning": "animal trail, game trail"
    },
    {
      "question": "捨て駒",
      "answer": "すてごま",
      "meaning": "sacrificial pawn, sacrificed piece, sacrifice"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し入れ",
      "answer": "おしいれ",
      "meaning": "closet"
    },
    {
      "question": "本数",
      "answer": "ほんすう",
      "meaning": "number of long thin objects (movies, TV programs, baseball games, etc.) (programmes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "銅像",
      "answer": "どうぞう",
      "meaning": "bronze statue"
    },
    {
      "question": "控え目",
      "answer": "ひかえめ",
      "meaning": "moderate, reserved, conservative, humble, mild-mannered, self-effacing, unassuming, well-behaved, lo"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗黙",
      "answer": "あんもく",
      "meaning": "tacit, unspoken, implicit"
    },
    {
      "question": "割れ",
      "answer": "われ",
      "meaning": "broken piece, below (a certain level, point, quantity, etc.), dropping below, illegal downloading an"
    },
    {
      "question": "大食い",
      "answer": "おおぐい",
      "meaning": "eating heavily, hearty eating, binge eating, gluttony, big eater, trencherman, gormandizer"
    },
    {
      "question": "持病",
      "answer": "じびょう",
      "meaning": "chronic disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "代価",
      "answer": "だいか",
      "meaning": "price, cost, charge, consideration (in a contract)"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒臭い",
      "answer": "さけくさい",
      "meaning": "reeking of liquor, smelling of alcohol"
    },
    {
      "question": "存命",
      "answer": "ぞんめい",
      "meaning": "being alive"
    },
    {
      "question": "淘汰",
      "answer": "とうた",
      "meaning": "weeding out, elimination (e.g. of unneeded employees), culling, selection, selection (e.g. natural s"
    },
    {
      "question": "怒濤",
      "answer": "どとう",
      "meaning": "surging waves, raging billows, turbulent, tempestuous, tumultuous, chaotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "分岐点",
      "answer": "ぶんきてん",
      "meaning": "junction, crossroads, division point, parting of ways"
    },
    {
      "question": "全能",
      "answer": "ぜんのう",
      "meaning": "almighty, omnipotent"
    },
    {
      "question": "好い",
      "answer": "よい,えい",
      "meaning": "good, excellent, fine, nice, pleasant, agreeable, sufficient, enough, ready, prepared, profitable (d"
    },
    {
      "question": "自虐",
      "answer": "じぎゃく",
      "meaning": "self-torture, masochism, inflicting damage to oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "潔癖",
      "answer": "けっぺき",
      "meaning": "fastidiousness, love of cleanliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥える",
      "answer": "こえる",
      "meaning": "to grow fat, to gain weight, to put on weight, to grow fertile, to be refined (palate), to be discer"
    },
    {
      "question": "千歳",
      "answer": "ちとせ,せんざい",
      "meaning": "millennium, one thousand years, long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "危険物",
      "answer": "きけんぶつ",
      "meaning": "hazardous materials, dangerous goods, explosives, combustibles"
    },
    {
      "question": "奮起",
      "answer": "ふんき",
      "meaning": "stirring, rousing oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "華やぐ",
      "answer": "はなやぐ",
      "meaning": "to become brilliant, to become cheerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "女中",
      "answer": "じょちゅう",
      "meaning": "maid, female servant, hostess (in a ryokan), waitress (in a traditional restaurant), court lady"
    },
    {
      "question": "母乳",
      "answer": "ぼにゅう",
      "meaning": "mother's milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "稲",
      "answer": "いね",
      "meaning": "rice plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "衆目",
      "answer": "しゅうもく",
      "meaning": "all eyes, public attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥水",
      "answer": "どろみず,でいすい",
      "meaning": "muddy water, red-light district"
    },
    {
      "question": "倍率",
      "answer": "ばいりつ",
      "meaning": "magnification, leverage, amplification, scaling factor, scale factor, competitiveness rating (e.g. f"
    },
    {
      "question": "堂々巡り",
      "answer": "どうどうめぐり",
      "meaning": "going around in circles, circling a temple, roll-call vote"
    },
    {
      "question": "家内",
      "answer": "かない,やうち",
      "meaning": "(my) wife, inside the home, one's family"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦国",
      "answer": "せんごく",
      "meaning": "country in civil war, country disarrayed by war, Warring States period (Japan, China), competiton in"
    },
    {
      "question": "刷り込む",
      "answer": "すりこむ",
      "meaning": "to insert (an illustration), to stencil (a pattern), to print on, to instill (thought, impression, e"
    },
    {
      "question": "縛",
      "answer": "ばく",
      "meaning": "tying up, restraint, restriction, arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "多量",
      "answer": "たりょう",
      "meaning": "large quantity, large amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "功",
      "answer": "いたわり,いさお,こう",
      "meaning": "service, labor, labour, trouble, meritorious deed, distinguished service, meritorious service, merit"
    },
    {
      "question": "力持ち",
      "answer": "ちからもち",
      "meaning": "muscleman, strong man"
    },
    {
      "question": "片時",
      "answer": "かたとき,へんじ",
      "meaning": "moment, instant"
    },
    {
      "question": "収穫祭",
      "answer": "しゅうかくさい",
      "meaning": "harvest festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒産",
      "answer": "とうさん",
      "meaning": "(corporate) bankruptcy, insolvency, commercial failure, failed business"
    },
    {
      "question": "米国",
      "answer": "べいこく",
      "meaning": "(United States of) America, USA, US"
    },
    {
      "question": "見え透く",
      "answer": "みえすく",
      "meaning": "to be transparent, to be easily seen through, to be obvious, to be apparent"
    },
    {
      "question": "少ししか",
      "answer": "すこししか",
      "meaning": "(nothing) but a little"
    },
    {
      "question": "大海",
      "answer": "たいかい,おおうみ",
      "meaning": "ocean, large sea, fabric pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "水の泡",
      "answer": "みずのあわ",
      "meaning": "coming to nothing, bubble on the surface of water, something that is short-lived"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍艦",
      "answer": "ぐんかん",
      "meaning": "warship, battleship"
    },
    {
      "question": "用品",
      "answer": "ようひん",
      "meaning": "articles, supplies, parts"
    },
    {
      "question": "会社員",
      "answer": "かいしゃいん",
      "meaning": "company employee, office worker, white-collar worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "郷愁",
      "answer": "きょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "nostalgia, homesickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "土壌",
      "answer": "どじょう",
      "meaning": "soil, breeding ground, fertile ground (for), foundation (for the development of ...)"
    },
    {
      "question": "帳消し",
      "answer": "ちょうけし",
      "meaning": "writing off (a debt), cancellation, balancing the books, cancelling out (gains or losses), making ev"
    },
    {
      "question": "大鎌",
      "answer": "おおがま,だいかま",
      "meaning": "scythe"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗暴",
      "answer": "そぼう",
      "meaning": "rough (behaviour, temperament, etc.), wild, rude, violent"
    },
    {
      "question": "怠慢",
      "answer": "たいまん",
      "meaning": "negligence, neglect, carelessness, procrastination"
    },
    {
      "question": "各方面",
      "answer": "かくほうめん",
      "meaning": "every quarter, all sides"
    },
    {
      "question": "天職",
      "answer": "てんしょく",
      "meaning": "vocation, lifework, calling, sacred task (esp. the emperor's rule over the nation), prostitute of th"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷房",
      "answer": "れいぼう",
      "meaning": "air conditioning, air cooling"
    },
    {
      "question": "周期",
      "answer": "しゅうき",
      "meaning": "cycle, period"
    },
    {
      "question": "財務",
      "answer": "ざいむ",
      "meaning": "financial affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "施し",
      "answer": "ほどこし",
      "meaning": "charity, almsgiving"
    },
    {
      "question": "同郷",
      "answer": "どうきょう",
      "meaning": "same village, same town, same province"
    },
    {
      "question": "輿",
      "answer": "かご,こし",
      "meaning": "palanquin, litter, bier"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り盛り",
      "answer": "きりもり",
      "meaning": "management, administration, cutting up and serving food, cut and fill (e.g. earthwork)"
    },
    {
      "question": "凍死",
      "answer": "とうし",
      "meaning": "death from cold, freezing to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "主として",
      "answer": "しゅとして",
      "meaning": "mainly, chiefly, primarily, for the most part"
    },
    {
      "question": "結び目",
      "answer": "むすびめ",
      "meaning": "knot"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴",
      "answer": "はれ",
      "meaning": "clear weather, fine weather, formal, ceremonial, public, cleared of suspicion"
    },
    {
      "question": "銭",
      "answer": "せん,ぜに,ぜぜ",
      "meaning": "hundredth of a yen, coin made of non-precious materials, one-thousandth of a kan (as a unit of curre"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り消し",
      "answer": "とりけし",
      "meaning": "cancellation, withdrawal, abolition, revocation, cancel, CAN"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛み入る",
      "answer": "いたみいる",
      "meaning": "to be greatly obliged, to be very sorry"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟",
      "answer": "とどろ",
      "meaning": "roaring"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬局",
      "answer": "やっきょく",
      "meaning": "pharmacy, drugstore, chemist's (shop), hospital pharmacy, dispensary"
    },
    {
      "question": "保育園",
      "answer": "ほいくえん",
      "meaning": "nursery school, day nursery, preschool"
    },
    {
      "question": "大家",
      "answer": "おおや,たいか,たいけ",
      "meaning": "landlord, landlady, master, expert, authority, leading figure, mansion, large house, rich family, di"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸焼き",
      "answer": "まるやき",
      "meaning": "whole roast (e.g. pig, turkey, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "混入",
      "answer": "こんにゅう",
      "meaning": "mixing, blending, adding, adulteration"
    },
    {
      "question": "彗星",
      "answer": "すいせい",
      "meaning": "comet"
    },
    {
      "question": "指揮権",
      "answer": "しきけん",
      "meaning": "(exercising) the right to command"
    },
    {
      "question": "ならず者",
      "answer": "ならずもの",
      "meaning": "ruffian, scoundrel, rogue, rascal, villain, hoodlum, thug"
    },
    {
      "question": "餞別",
      "answer": "せんべつ",
      "meaning": "farewell gift"
    },
    {
      "question": "千載一遇",
      "answer": "せんざいいちぐう",
      "meaning": "once in a lifetime (opportunity), (a golden opportunity that may) happen only once in a thousand yea"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕開け",
      "answer": "まくあけ",
      "meaning": "the rise of the curtain, opening (of play), beginning (e.g. of an era), opening (festival, event, et"
    },
    {
      "question": "日直",
      "answer": "にっちょく",
      "meaning": "day duty, day shift, class duty (students)"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓を引く",
      "answer": "ゆみをひく",
      "meaning": "to draw a bow, to oppose, to defy, to disobey one's superiors, to rebel"
    },
    {
      "question": "未明",
      "answer": "みめい",
      "meaning": "early dawn, grey of morning, gray of morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "極寒",
      "answer": "ごっかん,ごくかん",
      "meaning": "extreme cold, intense cold, coldest season, midwinter"
    },
    {
      "question": "内気",
      "answer": "うちき",
      "meaning": "shy, bashful, timid, reserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "不慮",
      "answer": "ふりょ",
      "meaning": "unforeseen, unexpected, sudden, accidental"
    },
    {
      "question": "巨木",
      "answer": "きょぼく",
      "meaning": "big tree"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛糸",
      "answer": "けいと",
      "meaning": "knitting wool, woolen yarn, woollen yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "旧友",
      "answer": "きゅうゆう",
      "meaning": "old friend, old pal"
    },
    {
      "question": "果",
      "answer": "か,はたて,はか",
      "meaning": "phala (attained state, result), enlightenment (as the fruits of one's Buddhist practice), fruit, cou"
    },
    {
      "question": "原形",
      "answer": "げんけい",
      "meaning": "original form, base form"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦行",
      "answer": "くぎょう",
      "meaning": "penance, austerities, mortification, asceticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "桜花",
      "answer": "おうか,さくらばな",
      "meaning": "cherry blossom"
    },
    {
      "question": "無体",
      "answer": "むたい",
      "meaning": "intangible, incorporeal, by force, outrageous, cruel, unreasonable, making light of, making fun of"
    },
    {
      "question": "促進",
      "answer": "そくしん",
      "meaning": "promotion, acceleration, encouragement, facilitation, spurring on"
    },
    {
      "question": "居残る",
      "answer": "いのこる",
      "meaning": "to stay behind, to remain, to work overtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂時計",
      "answer": "すなどけい",
      "meaning": "hourglass"
    },
    {
      "question": "凶行",
      "answer": "きょうこう",
      "meaning": "violence, murder, crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "土壁",
      "answer": "つちかべ",
      "meaning": "mud wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "木曜日",
      "answer": "もくようび",
      "meaning": "Thursday"
    },
    {
      "question": "適材適所",
      "answer": "てきざいてきしょ",
      "meaning": "the right person in the right place"
    },
    {
      "question": "工業",
      "answer": "こうぎょう",
      "meaning": "(manufacturing) industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "実害",
      "answer": "じつがい",
      "meaning": "real harm, actual damage"
    },
    {
      "question": "灯台",
      "answer": "とうだい",
      "meaning": "lighthouse, old-fashioned interior light fixture comprising a wooden pole with an oil-filled dish an"
    },
    {
      "question": "分け入る",
      "answer": "わけいる",
      "meaning": "to force one's way, to push through"
    },
    {
      "question": "妄執",
      "answer": "もうしゅう",
      "meaning": "deep-rooted delusion, firm conviction (based on incorrect beliefs)"
    },
    {
      "question": "停泊",
      "answer": "ていはく",
      "meaning": "anchorage, anchoring, mooring"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩急",
      "answer": "かんきゅう",
      "meaning": "pace, tempo, slow and fast, in case of emergency"
    },
    {
      "question": "座り",
      "answer": "すわり",
      "meaning": "sitting, stability"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り合い",
      "answer": "つりあい",
      "meaning": "balance, equilibrium"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦橋",
      "answer": "かんきょう",
      "meaning": "bridge (e.g. on a warship)"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い",
      "answer": "あらい",
      "meaning": "washing, sashimi chilled in iced water"
    },
    {
      "question": "庵",
      "answer": "いおり,あん,いお",
      "meaning": "hermitage, retreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "状況証拠",
      "answer": "じょうきょうしょうこ",
      "meaning": "circumstantial evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ知恵",
      "answer": "いれぢえ",
      "meaning": "putting an idea into someone's head, suggestion, hint"
    },
    {
      "question": "易々",
      "answer": "やすやす,いい",
      "meaning": "easily, readily, with ease, without trouble, easy, simple, plain"
    },
    {
      "question": "石碑",
      "answer": "せきひ",
      "meaning": "stone monument"
    },
    {
      "question": "先触れ",
      "answer": "さきぶれ",
      "meaning": "preliminary announcement, previous announcement, portent, sign, forewarning"
    },
    {
      "question": "二三",
      "answer": "にさん",
      "meaning": "two or three"
    },
    {
      "question": "老化",
      "answer": "ろうか",
      "meaning": "ageing, aging, senile deterioration"
    },
    {
      "question": "有志",
      "answer": "ゆうし",
      "meaning": "interested person, volunteer, supporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し味",
      "answer": "かくしあじ",
      "meaning": "subtle seasoning that brings out the flavor, secret ingredient"
    },
    {
      "question": "伝え聞く",
      "answer": "つたえきく",
      "meaning": "to learn by hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚れ惚れ",
      "answer": "ほれぼれ,ほれほれ",
      "meaning": "fondly, admiringly, with fascination, with adoration, with enchantment"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉈",
      "answer": "なた",
      "meaning": "nata, sturdy broad-bladed knife, used in woodcraft and hunting (often with a rectangular blade)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風車",
      "answer": "ふうしゃ,かざぐるま",
      "meaning": "windmill, pinwheel (toy), windmill (toy), Clematis patens (species of climbing plant)"
    },
    {
      "question": "現状維持",
      "answer": "げんじょういじ",
      "meaning": "maintaining the status quo"
    },
    {
      "question": "霜",
      "answer": "しも",
      "meaning": "frost"
    },
    {
      "question": "却って",
      "answer": "かえって",
      "meaning": "on the contrary, rather, all the more, instead"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒い霧",
      "answer": "くろいきり",
      "meaning": "thick fog (of suspicion), black veil of secrecy, covered-up crime, unethical act, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "純然",
      "answer": "じゅんぜん",
      "meaning": "absolute, complete, utter, pure, sheer"
    },
    {
      "question": "南下",
      "answer": "なんか",
      "meaning": "going south"
    },
    {
      "question": "生足",
      "answer": "なまあし",
      "meaning": "bare legs, bare feet, stockingless legs"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀願",
      "answer": "あいがん",
      "meaning": "supplication, appeal, entreaty, petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "香草",
      "answer": "こうそう",
      "meaning": "herb, fragrant grass"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ暗闇",
      "answer": "まっくらやみ",
      "meaning": "pitch dark, total darkness"
    },
    {
      "question": "背表紙",
      "answer": "せびょうし",
      "meaning": "spine (of book), binding (of book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "氾濫",
      "answer": "はんらん",
      "meaning": "overflowing, flood, inundation, deluge, oversupply, plethora"
    },
    {
      "question": "二枚目",
      "answer": "にまいめ",
      "meaning": "handsome man, actor in a love scene"
    },
    {
      "question": "出生",
      "answer": "しゅっしょう,しゅっせい",
      "meaning": "birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "官能",
      "answer": "かんのう",
      "meaning": "the senses, sensuality, carnality"
    },
    {
      "question": "一太刀",
      "answer": "ひとたち",
      "meaning": "stroke of sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "間取り",
      "answer": "まどり",
      "meaning": "layout (of a house or apartment), arrangement of rooms"
    },
    {
      "question": "厄災",
      "answer": "やくさい",
      "meaning": "calamity, disaster, accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "権化",
      "answer": "ごんげ",
      "meaning": "incarnation (of Buddha or bodhisattva), avatar, embodiment (as in 'embodiment of evil'), incarnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ物",
      "answer": "いれもの",
      "meaning": "container, case, receptacle, coffin, casket"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗面台",
      "answer": "せんめんだい",
      "meaning": "washbasin, washstand"
    },
    {
      "question": "澄み渡る",
      "answer": "すみわたる",
      "meaning": "to be perfectly clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "非常階段",
      "answer": "ひじょうかいだん",
      "meaning": "emergency staircase, emergency stairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "発声",
      "answer": "はっせい",
      "meaning": "utterance, speaking, vocalization, vocalisation, enunciation, pronouncing, leading a group of people"
    },
    {
      "question": "離",
      "answer": "り",
      "meaning": "li (one of the trigrams of the I Ching: fire, south)"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋敵",
      "answer": "こいがたき",
      "meaning": "one's rival in love"
    },
    {
      "question": "連休",
      "answer": "れんきゅう",
      "meaning": "consecutive holidays"
    },
    {
      "question": "解錠",
      "answer": "かいじょう",
      "meaning": "unlocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "破瓜",
      "answer": "はか",
      "meaning": "age 16 (of a girl), pubescence, puberty, age 64 (of a man), breaking of the hymen (during sex), defl"
    },
    {
      "question": "秀才",
      "answer": "しゅうさい",
      "meaning": "bright person, talented student, prodigy"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖塔",
      "answer": "せんとう",
      "meaning": "spire, steeple, pinnacle, minaret"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝臓",
      "answer": "かんぞう",
      "meaning": "liver"
    },
    {
      "question": "流れ弾",
      "answer": "ながれだま",
      "meaning": "stray bullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠱惑的",
      "answer": "こわくてき",
      "meaning": "fascinating, alluring"
    },
    {
      "question": "理論的",
      "answer": "りろんてき",
      "meaning": "theoretical"
    },
    {
      "question": "致し方",
      "answer": "いたしかた",
      "meaning": "way, method, means, resource, course"
    },
    {
      "question": "福",
      "answer": "ふく",
      "meaning": "good fortune, happiness, blessing, good luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "学舎",
      "answer": "がくしゃ,まなびや",
      "meaning": "school (building), school, school building, schoolhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "僧",
      "answer": "そう",
      "meaning": "monk, priest, sangha (the Buddhist community)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絡み",
      "answer": "からみ,がらみ",
      "meaning": "linkage, entanglement, involvement, relationship, interaction, about, concerning, related to, -ish"
    },
    {
      "question": "内壁",
      "answer": "ないへき",
      "meaning": "inner wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "一朝一夕",
      "answer": "いっちょういっせき",
      "meaning": "in a day, in a brief space of time"
    },
    {
      "question": "如何にも",
      "answer": "いかにも,どうにも",
      "meaning": "indeed, really, truly, just (like), very, extremely, totally, terribly, absolutely, certainly, for s"
    },
    {
      "question": "家紋",
      "answer": "かもん",
      "meaning": "family crest"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳天気",
      "answer": "のうてんき",
      "meaning": "laid-back, carefree, easygoing, thoughtless, happy-go-lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "古参",
      "answer": "こさん",
      "meaning": "seniority, long service"
    },
    {
      "question": "掃く",
      "answer": "はく",
      "meaning": "to sweep, to brush, to clean, to gather silkworms"
    },
    {
      "question": "日が浅い",
      "answer": "ひがあさい",
      "meaning": "it hasn't been long since"
    },
    {
      "question": "平伏す",
      "answer": "ひれふす",
      "meaning": "to prostrate oneself before"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖典",
      "answer": "せいてん",
      "meaning": "sacred scripture, sacred book, holy book, holy writings, writings of a sage"
    },
    {
      "question": "手中",
      "answer": "しゅちゅう",
      "meaning": "in one's hands, in one's control"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔写真",
      "answer": "かおじゃしん,かおしゃしん",
      "meaning": "portrait photo, mug shot, face shot, photograph of a person's face"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦横",
      "answer": "じゅうおう,たてよこ",
      "meaning": "length and width, length and breadth, lengthwise and crosswise, longitude and latitude, vertical and"
    },
    {
      "question": "微睡む",
      "answer": "まどろむ",
      "meaning": "to doze (off)"
    },
    {
      "question": "明く",
      "answer": "あく",
      "meaning": "to open (e.g. doors), to open (e.g. business, etc.), to be empty, to be vacant, to be available, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄らぐ",
      "answer": "うすらぐ",
      "meaning": "to become thin, to fade, to grow pale"
    },
    {
      "question": "隣り合う",
      "answer": "となりあう",
      "meaning": "to adjoin each other, to sit side by side"
    },
    {
      "question": "古城",
      "answer": "こじょう",
      "meaning": "old castle, old fortress"
    },
    {
      "question": "日取り",
      "answer": "ひどり",
      "meaning": "fixed date, appointed day"
    },
    {
      "question": "道楽",
      "answer": "どうらく,みちがく",
      "meaning": "pastime, hobby, favorite amusement, dissipation, debauchery, loose living, prodigality, indulging in"
    },
    {
      "question": "反応速度",
      "answer": "はんのうそくど",
      "meaning": "reaction velocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "侵害",
      "answer": "しんがい",
      "meaning": "infringement, violation, invasion, encroachment, trespass"
    },
    {
      "question": "下流",
      "answer": "かりゅう",
      "meaning": "downstream, lower reaches of a river, lower classes"
    },
    {
      "question": "家来",
      "answer": "けらい",
      "meaning": "retainer, retinue, servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "合言葉",
      "answer": "あいことば",
      "meaning": "password, watchword, motto, slogan"
    },
    {
      "question": "手動",
      "answer": "しゅどう",
      "meaning": "manual (operation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "声掛け",
      "answer": "こえかけ",
      "meaning": "saying something (to someone), greeting, approaching (someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "春先",
      "answer": "はるさき",
      "meaning": "beginning of spring"
    },
    {
      "question": "野性",
      "answer": "やせい",
      "meaning": "wildness (plants, animals, etc.), uncouth, rough, unpolished"
    },
    {
      "question": "照る",
      "answer": "てる",
      "meaning": "to shine, to look slightly upward (of a noh mask; indicating joy, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "緋",
      "answer": "あけ,ひ,あか",
      "meaning": "scarlet, red, crimson, red-containing colour (e.g. brown, pink, orange), Red (i.e. communist), red l"
    },
    {
      "question": "思索",
      "answer": "しさく",
      "meaning": "speculation, thinking, meditation"
    },
    {
      "question": "不平",
      "answer": "ふへい",
      "meaning": "discontent, dissatisfaction, complaint, grievance"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨霊",
      "answer": "おんりょう",
      "meaning": "revengeful ghost, apparition"
    },
    {
      "question": "写し",
      "answer": "うつし",
      "meaning": "copy, duplicate, facsimile, transcript"
    },
    {
      "question": "不貞",
      "answer": "ふてい",
      "meaning": "unfaithfulness, infidelity, unchastity"
    },
    {
      "question": "認可",
      "answer": "にんか",
      "meaning": "approval, license, licence, permission"
    },
    {
      "question": "偽善者",
      "answer": "ぎぜんしゃ",
      "meaning": "hypocrite, dissembler, wolf in sheep's clothing, fox in a lamb's skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "増築",
      "answer": "ぞうちく",
      "meaning": "addition to a building"
    },
    {
      "question": "当局",
      "answer": "とうきょく",
      "meaning": "authorities, relevant authorities, authorities concerned, this office"
    },
    {
      "question": "他界",
      "answer": "たかい",
      "meaning": "death, the next world, to pass away, to die"
    },
    {
      "question": "艦艇",
      "answer": "かんてい",
      "meaning": "military vessel, war fleet"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛾",
      "answer": "が",
      "meaning": "moth"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨抜き",
      "answer": "ほねぬき",
      "meaning": "boning (fish or meat), deboning, watering down (a plan, bill, etc.), dilution, emasculation, taking"
    },
    {
      "question": "高くつく",
      "answer": "たかくつく",
      "meaning": "to be expensive, to be costly"
    },
    {
      "question": "前歯",
      "answer": "まえば,ぜんし",
      "meaning": "front tooth"
    },
    {
      "question": "邁進",
      "answer": "まいしん",
      "meaning": "pushing forward (undaunted, bravely), working vigorously towards an aim, struggling on, striving tow"
    },
    {
      "question": "密告",
      "answer": "みっこく",
      "meaning": "anonymous report, (secret) information, tip-off, informing (against)"
    },
    {
      "question": "稀代",
      "answer": "きたい,きだい",
      "meaning": "uncommon, rare, extraordinary, matchless"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗車",
      "answer": "じょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "boarding (a train, bus, etc.), getting into (e.g. a taxi)"
    },
    {
      "question": "日暮れ",
      "answer": "ひぐれ",
      "meaning": "twilight, sunset, dusk, evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘境",
      "answer": "ひきょう",
      "meaning": "unexplored region, one of the most secluded regions"
    },
    {
      "question": "差し迫る",
      "answer": "さしせまる",
      "meaning": "to be urgent, to be pressing, to be imminent"
    },
    {
      "question": "我関せず",
      "answer": "われかんせず",
      "meaning": "no concern of mine, nothing to do with me"
    },
    {
      "question": "種子",
      "answer": "しゅし,しゅうじ,しゅじ",
      "meaning": "seed, pit, bija, seed syllable (Sanskrit character representing a Buddha or Bodhisattva)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て込む",
      "answer": "たてこむ",
      "meaning": "to be crowded (with), to be packed, to be piled up (of work), to be busy (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "模試",
      "answer": "もし",
      "meaning": "mock exam, practice exam, practice test"
    },
    {
      "question": "再三",
      "answer": "さいさん",
      "meaning": "again and again, repeatedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "休戦",
      "answer": "きゅうせん",
      "meaning": "cease-fire, truce, armistice"
    },
    {
      "question": "公然",
      "answer": "こうぜん",
      "meaning": "open, public, official, overt"
    },
    {
      "question": "見付かる",
      "answer": "みつかる",
      "meaning": "to be found, to be discovered"
    },
    {
      "question": "見咎める",
      "answer": "みとがめる",
      "meaning": "to find fault with, to question"
    },
    {
      "question": "転機",
      "answer": "てんき",
      "meaning": "turning point"
    },
    {
      "question": "外科",
      "answer": "げか",
      "meaning": "surgery, department of surgery (hospital, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "守衛",
      "answer": "しゅえい",
      "meaning": "security guard, doorkeeper"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶目っ気",
      "answer": "ちゃめっけ",
      "meaning": "playfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "歓楽街",
      "answer": "かんらくがい",
      "meaning": "pleasure quarter"
    },
    {
      "question": "国連",
      "answer": "こくれん",
      "meaning": "United Nations, UN"
    },
    {
      "question": "微調整",
      "answer": "びちょうせい",
      "meaning": "minute adjustment, fine tuning"
    },
    {
      "question": "極刑",
      "answer": "きょっけい",
      "meaning": "capital punishment, death penalty, maximum penalty, ultimate punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "手数料",
      "answer": "てすうりょう",
      "meaning": "(handling) fee, charge (e.g. for a cancellation), commission, brokerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "養成",
      "answer": "ようせい",
      "meaning": "training, education, development, cultivation"
    },
    {
      "question": "勢い込む",
      "answer": "いきおいこむ",
      "meaning": "to do with enthusiasm, to be excited to do, to throw oneself into"
    },
    {
      "question": "漸く",
      "answer": "ようやく",
      "meaning": "finally, at last, barely, narrowly, hardly, only just, gradually, little by little, by degrees"
    },
    {
      "question": "文様",
      "answer": "もんよう",
      "meaning": "pattern, design"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼窩",
      "answer": "がんか,がんわ",
      "meaning": "eye socket, orbit"
    },
    {
      "question": "着任",
      "answer": "ちゃくにん",
      "meaning": "taking up a new post"
    },
    {
      "question": "了見",
      "answer": "りょうけん",
      "meaning": "idea, thought, intention, design, view, inclination, decision, motive, discretion, forgiveness, pard"
    },
    {
      "question": "表札",
      "answer": "ひょうさつ",
      "meaning": "nameplate, doorplate"
    },
    {
      "question": "偉人",
      "answer": "いじん",
      "meaning": "great person, eminent figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "数個",
      "answer": "すうこ",
      "meaning": "several (objects, usu. from two to six)"
    },
    {
      "question": "召使い",
      "answer": "めしつかい",
      "meaning": "servant, menial"
    },
    {
      "question": "頻発",
      "answer": "ひんぱつ",
      "meaning": "frequent occurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "破産",
      "answer": "はさん",
      "meaning": "bankruptcy, insolvency"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛る",
      "answer": "かかる",
      "meaning": "to take (a resource, e.g. time or money), to hang, to come into view, to arrive, to come under (a co"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜在的",
      "answer": "せんざいてき",
      "meaning": "latent, potential"
    },
    {
      "question": "短所",
      "answer": "たんしょ",
      "meaning": "defect, demerit, weak point, disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "手榴弾",
      "answer": "しゅりゅうだん,てりゅうだん",
      "meaning": "hand grenade, grenade"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪廻",
      "answer": "りんね",
      "meaning": "samsara, cycle of death and rebirth, being reborn, reincarnation"
    },
    {
      "question": "恰幅",
      "answer": "かっぷく",
      "meaning": "physique, bodily build"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾ぐ",
      "answer": "かしぐ,かたぐ",
      "meaning": "to incline toward, to slant, to lurch, to heel over, to be disposed to, to trend toward, to be prone"
    },
    {
      "question": "染み付く",
      "answer": "しみつく",
      "meaning": "to be indelibly stained or ingrained, to be dyed in deeply"
    },
    {
      "question": "腐食",
      "answer": "ふしょく",
      "meaning": "corrosion, etching, action of acid, rot, rust, erosion, saprophagy"
    },
    {
      "question": "出向",
      "answer": "しゅっこう",
      "meaning": "temporary transfer (of an employee), secondment, relocation, loan, proceeding to, leaving for"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽め",
      "answer": "かるめ",
      "meaning": "light (weight)"
    },
    {
      "question": "体たらく",
      "answer": "ていたらく",
      "meaning": "(unpleasant) state of affairs, predicament, mess"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾道",
      "answer": "だんどう",
      "meaning": "trajectory, line of fire, ballistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷居",
      "answer": "しきい",
      "meaning": "threshold (esp. one with grooves for sliding doors), sill"
    },
    {
      "question": "翅",
      "answer": "はね",
      "meaning": "(insect) wing"
    },
    {
      "question": "下段",
      "answer": "げだん,かだん",
      "meaning": "lower tier, lower step, lower column, lower berth, bottom shelf, low position (of a sword in kendo,"
    },
    {
      "question": "南国",
      "answer": "なんごく",
      "meaning": "southern country, southern provinces, southern lands"
    },
    {
      "question": "下回る",
      "answer": "したまわる",
      "meaning": "to fall below (esp. figures: profits, unemployment rate, etc.), to be less than, to be lower than, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "老い",
      "answer": "おい",
      "meaning": "old age, old person, the old, the aged"
    },
    {
      "question": "観",
      "answer": "かん",
      "meaning": "look, appearance, spectacle, sight, observation meditation, outlook on ..., view of ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "風俗",
      "answer": "ふうぞく",
      "meaning": "manners, customs, sex service, sex industry, sex-oriented entertainment"
    },
    {
      "question": "実用的",
      "answer": "じつようてき",
      "meaning": "practical, useful, utilitarian, pragmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "総称",
      "answer": "そうしょう",
      "meaning": "general term, generic name"
    },
    {
      "question": "出来栄え",
      "answer": "できばえ",
      "meaning": "result, effect, performance, success, workmanship, execution, shape and quality (of an article), fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "海を渡る",
      "answer": "うみをわたる",
      "meaning": "to cross the ocean (i.e. to go to or come from overseas)"
    },
    {
      "question": "百戦錬磨",
      "answer": "ひゃくせんれんま",
      "meaning": "veteran, battle-worn, schooled by adversity in many battles, rich in experience"
    },
    {
      "question": "鑑識",
      "answer": "かんしき",
      "meaning": "judgement, judgment, discernment, discrimination, having an eye for, appraisal (e.g. of an antique),"
    },
    {
      "question": "収益",
      "answer": "しゅうえき",
      "meaning": "earnings, proceeds, returns, revenue"
    },
    {
      "question": "不純物",
      "answer": "ふじゅんぶつ",
      "meaning": "foreign matter, impurities"
    },
    {
      "question": "老舗",
      "answer": "しにせ,ろうほ",
      "meaning": "long-established shop, shop of long standing, old shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "気が立つ",
      "answer": "きがたつ",
      "meaning": "to be wrought up, to be on edge, to get irritated, to get excited (about), to be unsettled"
    },
    {
      "question": "分隊",
      "answer": "ぶんたい",
      "meaning": "squad, team"
    },
    {
      "question": "極小",
      "answer": "きょくしょう,ごくしょう",
      "meaning": "minimum, minuscule, local minimum"
    },
    {
      "question": "万々歳",
      "answer": "ばんばんざい",
      "meaning": "matter for great congratulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "人肌",
      "answer": "ひとはだ",
      "meaning": "the skin (of a human being), warmth of the skin, body warmth"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆睡",
      "answer": "ばくすい",
      "meaning": "sleeping like a log, (being) fast asleep (bombed, crashed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "少将",
      "answer": "しょうしょう",
      "meaning": "major general, rear admiral, air commodore"
    },
    {
      "question": "総本山",
      "answer": "そうほんざん",
      "meaning": "head temple of a sect, (organizational) headquarters, (organisational) headquarters"
    },
    {
      "question": "失墜",
      "answer": "しっつい",
      "meaning": "abasement, fall, forfeiture, sinking (in people's estimation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "締結",
      "answer": "ていけつ",
      "meaning": "conclusion, execution (of a contract), entering (into treaty), fastening (as in a joint)"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち残る",
      "answer": "かちのこる",
      "meaning": "to win and advance to the next round"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝取る",
      "answer": "ねとる",
      "meaning": "to steal another's spouse, to steal another's lover"
    },
    {
      "question": "行程",
      "answer": "こうてい",
      "meaning": "journey, course, distance, march, flight, drive, leg (of a journey, relay race, etc.), itinerary, st"
    },
    {
      "question": "刻々",
      "answer": "こっこく,こくこく",
      "meaning": "moment by moment, hour by hour"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲泥の差",
      "answer": "うんでいのさ",
      "meaning": "wide difference, a world of difference"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉塵",
      "answer": "ふんじん",
      "meaning": "mineral dust, mine dust, fine particles, dust"
    },
    {
      "question": "水没",
      "answer": "すいぼつ",
      "meaning": "submerge"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄ら",
      "answer": "うっすら,うすら",
      "meaning": "slightly, lightly, thinly, faintly, dimly, slight, light, thin, faint, dim"
    },
    {
      "question": "火の海",
      "answer": "ひのうみ",
      "meaning": "sea of fire, sea of flame"
    },
    {
      "question": "啞然",
      "answer": "あぜん",
      "meaning": "dumbfounded, in mute amazement"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥じ入る",
      "answer": "はじいる",
      "meaning": "to feel ashamed, to be abashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "横転",
      "answer": "おうてん",
      "meaning": "toppling sideways, turning sideways, falling over sideways, barrel roll"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び",
      "answer": "しのび",
      "meaning": "stealth, travelling incognito (traveling), ninjutsu, ninja, sneak theft, sneak thief, tolerance"
    },
    {
      "question": "祈願",
      "answer": "きがん",
      "meaning": "prayer (for something), supplication"
    },
    {
      "question": "発足",
      "answer": "ほっそく,はっそく",
      "meaning": "starting, inauguration, launch, founding, establishment, start-up"
    },
    {
      "question": "育児",
      "answer": "いくじ",
      "meaning": "childcare, child-rearing, nursing, upbringing"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦心",
      "answer": "くしん",
      "meaning": "pains, hard work, effort, trouble, labour, labor"
    },
    {
      "question": "誉れ",
      "answer": "ほまれ",
      "meaning": "honour, honor"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥を知る",
      "answer": "はじをしる",
      "meaning": "to know shame, to have a sense of shame, to be ashamed"
    },
    {
      "question": "有害",
      "answer": "ゆうがい",
      "meaning": "harmful, hazardous"
    },
    {
      "question": "居室",
      "answer": "きょしつ",
      "meaning": "living room"
    },
    {
      "question": "擦れ合う",
      "answer": "すれあう,こすれあう",
      "meaning": "to rub against, to chafe, to quarrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊具",
      "answer": "ゆうぐ",
      "meaning": "play equipment, playground equipment"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み食い",
      "answer": "のみくい",
      "meaning": "food and drink, eating and drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "門前払い",
      "answer": "もんぜんばらい",
      "meaning": "turning another away at the gate or front door, refusing to receive a caller"
    },
    {
      "question": "航空機",
      "answer": "こうくうき",
      "meaning": "aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "カップ麺",
      "answer": "カップめん",
      "meaning": "instant noodles (sold in a cup), cup noodles"
    },
    {
      "question": "一心同体",
      "answer": "いっしんどうたい",
      "meaning": "being one in body and soul, of one flesh, two hearts beating as one"
    },
    {
      "question": "万年筆",
      "answer": "まんねんひつ,まんねんぴつ,まんねんふで",
      "meaning": "fountain pen"
    },
    {
      "question": "注射器",
      "answer": "ちゅうしゃき",
      "meaning": "syringe, hypodermic needle, injector"
    },
    {
      "question": "人波",
      "answer": "ひとなみ",
      "meaning": "surging crowd, wave of humanity, stampede"
    },
    {
      "question": "猫背",
      "answer": "ねこぜ",
      "meaning": "bent back, hunchback, stoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "観察眼",
      "answer": "かんさつがん",
      "meaning": "observing eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "人が悪い",
      "answer": "ひとがわるい",
      "meaning": "ill-natured, mean, mischievous, nasty, unkind, teasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "墓所",
      "answer": "ぼしょ,はかしょ,はかどころ",
      "meaning": "graveyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ黒い",
      "answer": "まっくろい",
      "meaning": "pitch black, deep black"
    },
    {
      "question": "整頓",
      "answer": "せいとん",
      "meaning": "orderliness, put in order, tidying up, arranging neatly"
    },
    {
      "question": "孤島",
      "answer": "ことう",
      "meaning": "solitary island"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け布団",
      "answer": "かけぶとん",
      "meaning": "duvet, bed cover, coverlet, quilt, comforter, eiderdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "男物",
      "answer": "おとこもの",
      "meaning": "men's things, menswear, men's wear, men's, for men"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪道",
      "answer": "じゃどう",
      "meaning": "improper way (of doing), wrong way, unorthodox method, evil course, evil path, heresy"
    },
    {
      "question": "円満",
      "answer": "えんまん",
      "meaning": "harmonious, peaceful, happy, amicable, smooth, free from trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮族",
      "answer": "ばんぞく",
      "meaning": "barbarian tribe, savage tribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "蜘蛛の糸",
      "answer": "くものいと",
      "meaning": "spider's thread, spider silk"
    },
    {
      "question": "惨敗",
      "answer": "ざんぱい,さんぱい",
      "meaning": "ignominious defeat, crushing failure, utterly beaten, overwhelming defeat"
    },
    {
      "question": "座り心地",
      "answer": "すわりごこち",
      "meaning": "level of comfort (of objects you sit on)"
    },
    {
      "question": "経理",
      "answer": "けいり",
      "meaning": "accounting, administration (of money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "元素",
      "answer": "げんそ",
      "meaning": "element, chemical element, (classical) element (e.g. earth, water, air, fire), origin, source"
    },
    {
      "question": "重ね",
      "answer": "かさね",
      "meaning": "pile, heap, layers (e.g. of clothing), set (e.g. of boxes), course (e.g. of stones), counter for thi"
    },
    {
      "question": "一世一代",
      "answer": "いっせいちだい,いっせいいちだい",
      "meaning": "once in a lifetime, the first and last occurrence (event, experience) of one's lifetime"
    },
    {
      "question": "家令",
      "answer": "かれい",
      "meaning": "steward, butler"
    },
    {
      "question": "極論",
      "answer": "きょくろん",
      "meaning": "extreme logic, extreme argument, unreserved argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "体積",
      "answer": "たいせき",
      "meaning": "capacity, volume"
    },
    {
      "question": "終い",
      "answer": "しまい,じまい",
      "meaning": "end, close, finish, termination, ending, quitting, closing, ending before one had time to do somethi"
    },
    {
      "question": "擬音",
      "answer": "ぎおん",
      "meaning": "imitative sound (in film, theatre, etc.), sound effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "慇懃",
      "answer": "いんぎん",
      "meaning": "politeness, courtesy, civility, friendship, (sexual) intimacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "義務感",
      "answer": "ぎむかん",
      "meaning": "sense of duty (obligation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎌倉",
      "answer": "かまくら",
      "meaning": "Kamakura (city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に際",
      "answer": "しにぎわ",
      "meaning": "one's last moments, (on) the point of death, (on) one's deathbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "久遠",
      "answer": "くおん,きゅうえん",
      "meaning": "eternity"
    },
    {
      "question": "集積",
      "answer": "しゅうせき",
      "meaning": "accumulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "世論",
      "answer": "よろん,せろん,せいろん",
      "meaning": "public opinion, popular voice, public sentiment, consensus"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒労",
      "answer": "とろう",
      "meaning": "fruitless effort, wasted effort, abortive scheme, futility"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭数",
      "answer": "あたまかず,とうすう",
      "meaning": "number of persons, numerical strength, head count, number of (large) animals"
    },
    {
      "question": "低音",
      "answer": "ていおん",
      "meaning": "low tone, bass, low voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き際",
      "answer": "ひきぎわ",
      "meaning": "moment to quit, way to quit"
    },
    {
      "question": "着手",
      "answer": "ちゃくしゅ",
      "meaning": "to start work (on), to undertake, to start committing a crime, embarkation, launch"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼服",
      "answer": "れいふく,らいふく",
      "meaning": "ceremonial dress, evening dress, dress suit, morning suit, ceremonial clothes formerly worn by nobil"
    },
    {
      "question": "下に見る",
      "answer": "したにみる",
      "meaning": "to look down on, to condescend"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰陽",
      "answer": "いんよう,おんみょう,おんよう",
      "meaning": "cosmic dual forces, yin and yang, sun and moon, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "跋扈",
      "answer": "ばっこ",
      "meaning": "rampancy, prevalence, domination"
    },
    {
      "question": "櫂",
      "answer": "かい",
      "meaning": "paddle, oar, scull"
    },
    {
      "question": "様式",
      "answer": "ようしき",
      "meaning": "style, form, pattern"
    },
    {
      "question": "一画",
      "answer": "いっかく",
      "meaning": "one plot (of land), one block (i.e. one city block), one area, one lot, one brush stroke, one kanji"
    },
    {
      "question": "皿洗い",
      "answer": "さらあらい",
      "meaning": "washing-up, dish-washing"
    },
    {
      "question": "発育",
      "answer": "はついく",
      "meaning": "(physical) growth, development"
    },
    {
      "question": "有り得",
      "answer": "ありう",
      "meaning": "to be possible, to be likely, to be probable"
    },
    {
      "question": "正規軍",
      "answer": "せいきぐん",
      "meaning": "regular army"
    },
    {
      "question": "総帥",
      "answer": "そうすい",
      "meaning": "commander-in-chief, leader, head of a group of companies"
    },
    {
      "question": "指南",
      "answer": "しなん",
      "meaning": "instruction (in martial arts, performance, etc.), teaching, coaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢者の石",
      "answer": "けんじゃのいし",
      "meaning": "philosopher's stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "待ち時間",
      "answer": "まちじかん",
      "meaning": "waiting time, latency, standby time (e.g. cellular phones), queueing time"
    },
    {
      "question": "体育座り",
      "answer": "たいいくずわり,たいいくすわり",
      "meaning": "sitting on the floor grasping one's knees (as in a gym class)"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪癖",
      "answer": "あくへき,わるぐせ",
      "meaning": "bad habit, vice"
    },
    {
      "question": "がら空き",
      "answer": "がらあき,がらすき",
      "meaning": "virtually empty, quite empty, inadequately defended, defenseless, defenceless"
    },
    {
      "question": "構内",
      "answer": "こうない",
      "meaning": "premises, grounds, campus, compound, precincts"
    },
    {
      "question": "公安",
      "answer": "こうあん",
      "meaning": "public safety, public welfare"
    },
    {
      "question": "気圧",
      "answer": "きあつ",
      "meaning": "atmospheric pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "流し目",
      "answer": "ながしめ",
      "meaning": "sidelong glance, flirtatious glance"
    },
    {
      "question": "保健",
      "answer": "ほけん",
      "meaning": "preservation of health, hygiene, sanitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "火を放つ",
      "answer": "ひをはなつ",
      "meaning": "to set fire (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "礼節",
      "answer": "れいせつ",
      "meaning": "decorum, propriety, politeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "在住",
      "answer": "ざいじゅう",
      "meaning": "residing, living, dwelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "被害妄想",
      "answer": "ひがいもうそう",
      "meaning": "persecution complex, paranoia"
    },
    {
      "question": "首が飛ぶ",
      "answer": "くびがとぶ",
      "meaning": "to be sacked, to be dismissed"
    },
    {
      "question": "飾り付け",
      "answer": "かざりつけ",
      "meaning": "decoration, arrangement"
    },
    {
      "question": "根絶やし",
      "answer": "ねだやし",
      "meaning": "rooting up (weeds, etc.), eradication, rooting out, stamping out, getting rid of"
    },
    {
      "question": "意中",
      "answer": "いちゅう",
      "meaning": "one's mind, one's heart, one's intention"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔ながら",
      "answer": "むかしながら",
      "meaning": "the same as it was long ago, unchanged, traditional"
    },
    {
      "question": "昆布",
      "answer": "こんぶ,こぶ",
      "meaning": "kombu (usu. Saccharina japonica), konbu, kelp, any edible species from the family Laminariaceae"
    },
    {
      "question": "飴玉",
      "answer": "あめだま",
      "meaning": "candy"
    },
    {
      "question": "残量",
      "answer": "ざんりょう",
      "meaning": "remaining quantity, residual quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "即決",
      "answer": "そっけつ",
      "meaning": "prompt decision, quick decision, immediate judgement, summary judgment, summary judgement"
    },
    {
      "question": "名を残す",
      "answer": "なをのこす",
      "meaning": "to be remembered, to go down in history"
    },
    {
      "question": "良からぬ",
      "answer": "よからぬ",
      "meaning": "bad, wrong, evil, no good, wicked, reprehensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "下地",
      "answer": "したじ",
      "meaning": "groundwork, foundation, inclination, aptitude, elementary knowledge (of), grounding (in), undercoat,"
    },
    {
      "question": "母国",
      "answer": "ぼこく",
      "meaning": "one's home country, one's homeland"
    },
    {
      "question": "英知",
      "answer": "えいち",
      "meaning": "wisdom, intelligence, intellect"
    },
    {
      "question": "間隙",
      "answer": "かんげき",
      "meaning": "gap"
    },
    {
      "question": "品揃え",
      "answer": "しなぞろえ",
      "meaning": "assortment, product lineup"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽々",
      "answer": "らくらく",
      "meaning": "comfortably, easily"
    },
    {
      "question": "激務",
      "answer": "げきむ",
      "meaning": "exhausting work, hard work, severe duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "白馬",
      "answer": "あおうま,はくば,しろうま",
      "meaning": "dark-colored horse with a lustrous coat (coloured), white horse, unrefined sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "潤滑油",
      "answer": "じゅんかつゆ",
      "meaning": "lubricating oil, lubricant, lube"
    },
    {
      "question": "担架",
      "answer": "たんか",
      "meaning": "stretcher, litter"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き魚",
      "answer": "やきざかな",
      "meaning": "grilled fish"
    },
    {
      "question": "憐れみ",
      "answer": "あわれみ",
      "meaning": "pity, compassion"
    },
    {
      "question": "萎れる",
      "answer": "しおれる",
      "meaning": "to wither, to wilt, to droop, to fade, to be dejected, to be disheartened, to be depressed, to be cr"
    },
    {
      "question": "住",
      "answer": "じゅう",
      "meaning": "dwelling, living"
    },
    {
      "question": "史実",
      "answer": "しじつ",
      "meaning": "historical fact"
    },
    {
      "question": "交尾",
      "answer": "こうび",
      "meaning": "copulation (in animals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "両隣",
      "answer": "りょうどなり",
      "meaning": "both sides"
    },
    {
      "question": "楽屋",
      "answer": "がくや",
      "meaning": "dressing room, green room, backstage, behind the scenes, the inside, inside affairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "慣性",
      "answer": "かんせい",
      "meaning": "inertia"
    },
    {
      "question": "前脚",
      "answer": "まえあし,ぜんきゃく",
      "meaning": "forefoot, forefeet, foreleg, forelimb"
    },
    {
      "question": "天変地異",
      "answer": "てんぺんちい",
      "meaning": "natural disaster, cataclysm"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠れ蓑",
      "answer": "かくれみの",
      "meaning": "cover (e.g. for illegal activity), front, guise, Dendropanax trifidus (species of flowering plant),"
    },
    {
      "question": "自慰",
      "answer": "じい",
      "meaning": "masturbation, self consolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "片や",
      "answer": "かたや",
      "meaning": "on one hand, on the other hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏れる",
      "answer": "おそれる",
      "meaning": "to fear, to be afraid of"
    },
    {
      "question": "消去法",
      "answer": "しょうきょほう",
      "meaning": "(process of) elimination"
    },
    {
      "question": "簒奪",
      "answer": "さんだつ",
      "meaning": "usurpation"
    },
    {
      "question": "自給自足",
      "answer": "じきゅうじそく",
      "meaning": "self-sufficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "空母",
      "answer": "くうぼ",
      "meaning": "aircraft carrier"
    },
    {
      "question": "幽鬼",
      "answer": "ゆうき",
      "meaning": "ghost, revenant, spirit (of the dead), departed soul"
    },
    {
      "question": "直線的",
      "answer": "ちょくせんてき",
      "meaning": "linear, rectilinear, straight-line, straightforward, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥界",
      "answer": "めいかい",
      "meaning": "hades, realm of the dead"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯨",
      "answer": "くじら",
      "meaning": "whale (Cetacea spp.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盤面",
      "answer": "ばんめん",
      "meaning": "surface of a board or record"
    },
    {
      "question": "手裏剣",
      "answer": "しゅりけん",
      "meaning": "shuriken, small throwing blade, throwing star"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪念",
      "answer": "じゃねん",
      "meaning": "wicked thought, wicked mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "類似",
      "answer": "るいじ",
      "meaning": "resemblance, similarity, likeness, analogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "火星",
      "answer": "かせい",
      "meaning": "Mars (planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "子弟",
      "answer": "してい",
      "meaning": "children, sons, children and younger brothers, young people"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙秘",
      "answer": "もくひ",
      "meaning": "remaining silent, keeping secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "連盟",
      "answer": "れんめい",
      "meaning": "league, federation, union, alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い違う",
      "answer": "くいちがう",
      "meaning": "to cross each other, to run counter to, to differ, to clash, to go awry"
    },
    {
      "question": "不確定",
      "answer": "ふかくてい",
      "meaning": "uncertain, indefinite"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り崩す",
      "answer": "きりくずす",
      "meaning": "to level (earth), to cut through (a mountain), to split (the opposition), to break (strike)"
    },
    {
      "question": "死線",
      "answer": "しせん",
      "meaning": "borderline between life and death, verge of death, deadline (boundary around a prison which prisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "建設的",
      "answer": "けんせつてき",
      "meaning": "constructive"
    },
    {
      "question": "脇の下",
      "answer": "わきのした",
      "meaning": "armpit, axilla"
    },
    {
      "question": "扇動",
      "answer": "せんどう",
      "meaning": "incitement, sedition, agitation, abetting"
    },
    {
      "question": "短距離",
      "answer": "たんきょり",
      "meaning": "short distance, short range, short-haul"
    },
    {
      "question": "一区切り",
      "answer": "ひとくぎり",
      "meaning": "end, break"
    },
    {
      "question": "宵闇",
      "answer": "よいやみ",
      "meaning": "dusk, twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "激高",
      "answer": "げっこう,げきこう,げきだか",
      "meaning": "excitement, exasperation, indignation, rage, fury, extremely expensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "再利用",
      "answer": "さいりよう",
      "meaning": "reuse, recycling"
    },
    {
      "question": "国防",
      "answer": "こくぼう",
      "meaning": "national defence, national defense"
    },
    {
      "question": "低俗",
      "answer": "ていぞく",
      "meaning": "vulgar, lowbrow, coarse"
    },
    {
      "question": "物憂い",
      "answer": "ものうい",
      "meaning": "languid, weary, listless, melancholy"
    },
    {
      "question": "見目",
      "answer": "みめ",
      "meaning": "appearance, looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "当る",
      "answer": "あたる",
      "meaning": "to be hit, to strike, to touch, to be in contact, to be affixed, to be equivalent to, to be applicab"
    },
    {
      "question": "跡形",
      "answer": "あとかた",
      "meaning": "trace, vestige, evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "終電",
      "answer": "しゅうでん",
      "meaning": "last train (of the day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "重責",
      "answer": "じゅうせき",
      "meaning": "heavy responsibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "晴れ舞台",
      "answer": "はれぶたい",
      "meaning": "big moment (e.g. performance, in the spotlight), gala occasion, (on the) world stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "不安感",
      "answer": "ふあんかん",
      "meaning": "uneasy feeling, sense of anxiety, malaise"
    },
    {
      "question": "街角",
      "answer": "まちかど",
      "meaning": "street corner"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙する",
      "answer": "もくする",
      "meaning": "to stop talking, to be silent"
    },
    {
      "question": "只者",
      "answer": "ただもの",
      "meaning": "ordinary person"
    },
    {
      "question": "格式",
      "answer": "かくしき,きゃくしき",
      "meaning": "formality, social rules, social status, social standing, amendments and enforcement regulations (of"
    },
    {
      "question": "激化",
      "answer": "げきか,げっか",
      "meaning": "intensification, aggravation"
    },
    {
      "question": "渚",
      "answer": "なぎさ,みぎわ",
      "meaning": "water's edge, beach, shore, waterside"
    },
    {
      "question": "外交官",
      "answer": "がいこうかん",
      "meaning": "diplomat"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛快",
      "answer": "つうかい",
      "meaning": "exhilarating, thrilling, intensely pleasurable"
    },
    {
      "question": "親類",
      "answer": "しんるい",
      "meaning": "relative, relation, kin"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡立てる",
      "answer": "あわだてる",
      "meaning": "to beat, to whip, to whisk, to lather"
    },
    {
      "question": "御曹司",
      "answer": "おんぞうし",
      "meaning": "son of a distinguished family, son of a noble"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒気",
      "answer": "どっき,どっけ,どくけ",
      "meaning": "poisonous air, poisonous gas, poisonous vapour, poisonous ingredient, poisonous nature, toxicity, ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "嵌まる",
      "answer": "はまる",
      "meaning": "to fit, to get into, to go into, to be fitted with (e.g. door with a window), to be fit for (a job,"
    },
    {
      "question": "間者",
      "answer": "かんじゃ",
      "meaning": "spy, secret agent"
    },
    {
      "question": "騎士道",
      "answer": "きしどう",
      "meaning": "chivalry"
    },
    {
      "question": "人造",
      "answer": "じんぞう",
      "meaning": "artificial, man-made, imitation, synthetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "契り",
      "answer": "ちぎり",
      "meaning": "pledge, vow, promise, (of a man and woman) having sexual relations, having sexual intercourse, desti"
    },
    {
      "question": "電話口",
      "answer": "でんわぐち",
      "meaning": "telephone receiver, telephone mouthpiece, making a telephone call, receiving a telephone call"
    },
    {
      "question": "何用",
      "answer": "なによう",
      "meaning": "what kind of business, what sort of matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "準決勝",
      "answer": "じゅんけっしょう",
      "meaning": "semifinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭る",
      "answer": "まつる",
      "meaning": "to deify, to enshrine, to pray, to worship"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎か",
      "answer": "おろそか,おろか",
      "meaning": "negligent, neglectful, careless, remiss, not to mention ..., needless to say ..., not to speak of .."
    },
    {
      "question": "野犬",
      "answer": "やけん",
      "meaning": "stray dog, ownerless dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "問題視",
      "answer": "もんだいし",
      "meaning": "viewing as a problem, problematizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯉",
      "answer": "こい",
      "meaning": "common carp (Cyprinus carpio), koi carp"
    },
    {
      "question": "予防",
      "answer": "よぼう",
      "meaning": "prevention, precaution, protection against"
    },
    {
      "question": "織る",
      "answer": "おる",
      "meaning": "to weave"
    },
    {
      "question": "目鼻立ち",
      "answer": "めはなだち",
      "meaning": "(set of) facial features, looks"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮",
      "answer": "に",
      "meaning": "simmered with, cooked with, boiling, boiled dish"
    },
    {
      "question": "彼我",
      "answer": "ひが",
      "meaning": "self and others, this and that, both sides, oneself and one's opponent, he and I"
    },
    {
      "question": "改修",
      "answer": "かいしゅう",
      "meaning": "repair, improvement"
    },
    {
      "question": "死滅",
      "answer": "しめつ",
      "meaning": "extinction, annihilation, destruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "優良",
      "answer": "ゆうりょう",
      "meaning": "superior, excellent, fine"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁判所",
      "answer": "さいばんしょ",
      "meaning": "court, courthouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "翳る",
      "answer": "かげる",
      "meaning": "to darken, to get dark, to be clouded, to be hidden (behind clouds)"
    },
    {
      "question": "食物",
      "answer": "しょくもつ,くいもの",
      "meaning": "food, foodstuff, prey, victim"
    },
    {
      "question": "財団",
      "answer": "ざいだん",
      "meaning": "foundation"
    },
    {
      "question": "家業",
      "answer": "かぎょう",
      "meaning": "family business, family trade, one's occupation, one's trade"
    },
    {
      "question": "三位",
      "answer": "さんみ,さんい",
      "meaning": "third rank (in the Japanese court system), Trinity, the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "紗",
      "answer": "しゃ",
      "meaning": "(silk) gauze"
    },
    {
      "question": "夥しい",
      "answer": "おびただしい",
      "meaning": "large number, innumerable, great many, immense, vast, abundant"
    },
    {
      "question": "深緑",
      "answer": "しんりょく,ふかみどり",
      "meaning": "dark (deep) green"
    },
    {
      "question": "全否定",
      "answer": "ぜんひてい",
      "meaning": "complete denial, complete disavowal, total negation"
    },
    {
      "question": "太刀筋",
      "answer": "たちすじ",
      "meaning": "swordsmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "野原",
      "answer": "のはら",
      "meaning": "field, plain, prairie, moor"
    },
    {
      "question": "新婚旅行",
      "answer": "しんこんりょこう",
      "meaning": "honeymoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "高官",
      "answer": "こうかん",
      "meaning": "high official"
    },
    {
      "question": "放電",
      "answer": "ほうでん",
      "meaning": "electrical discharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "既知",
      "answer": "きち",
      "meaning": "already known, well-known"
    },
    {
      "question": "母方",
      "answer": "ははかた",
      "meaning": "mother's side of family, maternal (grandfather, uncle, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "沼地",
      "answer": "ぬまち,しょうち",
      "meaning": "marshland, wetland, swampland"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲観的",
      "answer": "ひかんてき",
      "meaning": "pessimistic, gloomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪名",
      "answer": "あくめい,あくみょう",
      "meaning": "bad reputation, ill repute, bad name, notoriety, evil deed, wrongdoing, wrongdoer"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔肌",
      "answer": "やわはだ",
      "meaning": "soft fair skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "不死鳥",
      "answer": "ふしちょう",
      "meaning": "phoenix"
    },
    {
      "question": "変じる",
      "answer": "へんじる",
      "meaning": "to change into, to be transformed, to be transfigured, to transform, to alter, to convert"
    },
    {
      "question": "高所",
      "answer": "こうしょ",
      "meaning": "high place, high altitude, heights, elevation, broad view"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨日今日",
      "answer": "きのうきょう",
      "meaning": "yesterday and today, only recently, just recently, only yesterday"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡",
      "answer": "じゅん",
      "meaning": "counter for tours, cycles, rounds, circuits, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "服飾",
      "answer": "ふくしょく",
      "meaning": "clothing and accessories, attire"
    },
    {
      "question": "開放的",
      "answer": "かいほうてき",
      "meaning": "open, frank, liberal, open-minded"
    },
    {
      "question": "後の祭り",
      "answer": "あとのまつり",
      "meaning": "a day after the fair, (at a) stage when it's too late"
    },
    {
      "question": "人面",
      "answer": "じんめん",
      "meaning": "human face"
    },
    {
      "question": "葉巻",
      "answer": "はまき",
      "meaning": "cigar"
    },
    {
      "question": "望",
      "answer": "もち,ぼう",
      "meaning": "full moon, 15th day of the lunar month"
    },
    {
      "question": "特効薬",
      "answer": "とっこうやく",
      "meaning": "specific medicine, wonder drug, silver bullet"
    },
    {
      "question": "中心地",
      "answer": "ちゅうしんち",
      "meaning": "center, centre, metropolis"
    },
    {
      "question": "老後",
      "answer": "ろうご",
      "meaning": "old age"
    },
    {
      "question": "精気",
      "answer": "せいき",
      "meaning": "(mind and) spirit, life energy, vitality, essence"
    },
    {
      "question": "軒先",
      "answer": "のきさき",
      "meaning": "edge of the eaves, house frontage"
    },
    {
      "question": "網羅",
      "answer": "もうら",
      "meaning": "encompassing, covering (exhaustively), including (all of), comprising, comprehending"
    },
    {
      "question": "独学",
      "answer": "どくがく",
      "meaning": "self-education, self-instruction, self-study"
    },
    {
      "question": "部分的",
      "answer": "ぶぶんてき",
      "meaning": "partial"
    },
    {
      "question": "与する",
      "answer": "くみする",
      "meaning": "to take part in, to be a party to, to side with, to support, to agree with"
    },
    {
      "question": "事切れる",
      "answer": "こときれる",
      "meaning": "to breathe one's last, to pass away, to die, to expire"
    },
    {
      "question": "尻に敷く",
      "answer": "しりにしく",
      "meaning": "to dominate (usu. one's husband)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白煙",
      "answer": "はくえん",
      "meaning": "white smoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "地竜",
      "answer": "じりゅう",
      "meaning": "herbal medicine prepared from dried earthworms"
    },
    {
      "question": "排泄",
      "answer": "はいせつ",
      "meaning": "excretion"
    },
    {
      "question": "兆",
      "answer": "ちょう",
      "meaning": "10^12, 1,000,000,000,000, trillion, sign, omen, indication, portent"
    },
    {
      "question": "流入",
      "answer": "りゅうにゅう",
      "meaning": "afflux, influx"
    },
    {
      "question": "武蔵",
      "answer": "むさし",
      "meaning": "Musashi (former province located in parts of present-day Tokyo, Kanagawa and Saitama prefectures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮮度",
      "answer": "せんど",
      "meaning": "(degree of) freshness"
    },
    {
      "question": "生家",
      "answer": "せいか,しょうか",
      "meaning": "house where one was born, one's parents' house"
    },
    {
      "question": "一説",
      "answer": "いっせつ",
      "meaning": "one theory (opinion), another theory (opinion)"
    },
    {
      "question": "室長",
      "answer": "しつちょう",
      "meaning": "section chief, laboratory manager, office head, room monitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "陵辱",
      "answer": "りょうじょく",
      "meaning": "insult, affront, disgrace, indignity, sexual assault, rape"
    },
    {
      "question": "母屋",
      "answer": "おもや,もや,むや",
      "meaning": "main building (of a manor), central room (of a house), purlin (structural beam in a roof), purline,"
    },
    {
      "question": "白米",
      "answer": "はくまい,しらよね,しろごめ",
      "meaning": "polished rice, (uncooked) white rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "匠",
      "answer": "たくみ,しょう",
      "meaning": "workman, artisan, mechanic, carpenter, craft, skill, means, idea"
    },
    {
      "question": "踊り子",
      "answer": "おどりこ",
      "meaning": "dancer (usu. female)"
    },
    {
      "question": "片膝",
      "answer": "かたひざ",
      "meaning": "one knee"
    },
    {
      "question": "光輝",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "brightness, splendour, splendor"
    },
    {
      "question": "告ぐ",
      "answer": "つぐ",
      "meaning": "to tell, to inform, to announce, to indicate, to signal, to mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "来店",
      "answer": "らいてん",
      "meaning": "coming to a store (restaurant, bar, shop, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "符",
      "answer": "ふ",
      "meaning": "charm, talisman, amulet, tally, sign, mark, note, fu, unit used in calculation of a hand's score"
    },
    {
      "question": "英霊",
      "answer": "えいれい",
      "meaning": "spirits of war dead, person of great ability, soul of a talented person"
    },
    {
      "question": "怒張",
      "answer": "どちょう",
      "meaning": "overswelling (of a blood vessel), engorgement, bulging, squaring one's shoulders, flexing one's musc"
    },
    {
      "question": "手勢",
      "answer": "てぜい",
      "meaning": "one's troops"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉢植え",
      "answer": "はちうえ",
      "meaning": "potted plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "対比",
      "answer": "たいひ",
      "meaning": "contrast, comparison"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き立つ",
      "answer": "ひきたつ",
      "meaning": "to cheer up, to liven up, to become active, to look better, to improve (in appearance), to stand out"
    },
    {
      "question": "難攻不落",
      "answer": "なんこうふらく",
      "meaning": "impregnable"
    },
    {
      "question": "敗退",
      "answer": "はいたい",
      "meaning": "being defeated, being eliminated (from competition)"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち往生",
      "answer": "たちおうじょう",
      "meaning": "being brought to a standstill, being stranded, getting stuck, stalling, deadlock, being stumped, bei"
    },
    {
      "question": "保安",
      "answer": "ほあん,ほうあん",
      "meaning": "peace preservation, security, safety, Hōan era (1120.4.10-1124.4.3), Hoan era"
    },
    {
      "question": "制す",
      "answer": "せいす",
      "meaning": "to control, to command, to get the better of"
    },
    {
      "question": "八百",
      "answer": "はっぴゃく,やお",
      "meaning": "800, eight hundred, multitude, large number"
    },
    {
      "question": "若様",
      "answer": "わかさま",
      "meaning": "young master, son of a high-ranking person"
    },
    {
      "question": "相対的",
      "answer": "そうたいてき",
      "meaning": "relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "現実離れ",
      "answer": "げんじつばなれ",
      "meaning": "unreality, becoming disconnected from reality"
    },
    {
      "question": "三代",
      "answer": "さんだい",
      "meaning": "three generations, three periods, third generation"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り渡す",
      "answer": "うりわたす",
      "meaning": "to sell over to"
    },
    {
      "question": "性行為",
      "answer": "せいこうい",
      "meaning": "sexual act, sexual intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "義手",
      "answer": "ぎしゅ",
      "meaning": "artificial arm (hand)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盗品",
      "answer": "とうひん",
      "meaning": "stolen goods, loot, spoils"
    },
    {
      "question": "失禁",
      "answer": "しっきん",
      "meaning": "incontinence"
    },
    {
      "question": "悦楽",
      "answer": "えつらく",
      "meaning": "enjoyment, pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "余剰",
      "answer": "よじょう",
      "meaning": "surplus, remainder, residue, margin, balance"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り子",
      "answer": "ふりこ",
      "meaning": "pendulum"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇",
      "answer": "ゆう",
      "meaning": "bravery, courage, heroism"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄",
      "answer": "だ",
      "meaning": "poor, low-grade, trivial, insignificant, worthless, load, pack, horse load, packhorse"
    },
    {
      "question": "毎夜",
      "answer": "まいよ,まいや",
      "meaning": "every evening, every night"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘やか",
      "answer": "あまやか",
      "meaning": "sweet (voice, fragrance, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉球",
      "answer": "にくきゅう",
      "meaning": "(sole of the) paw, pad"
    },
    {
      "question": "一切れ",
      "answer": "ひときれ",
      "meaning": "slice, small piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "目移り",
      "answer": "めうつり",
      "meaning": "being drawn to many things, distraction, difficulty of choice, difficulty in choosing, being unable"
    },
    {
      "question": "人らしい",
      "answer": "ひとらしい",
      "meaning": "like a decent person, human"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇蹟",
      "answer": "きせき",
      "meaning": "miracle, wonder, marvel"
    },
    {
      "question": "無にする",
      "answer": "むにする",
      "meaning": "to bring to naught, to bring to nought, to waste, to empty, to clear"
    },
    {
      "question": "帆船",
      "answer": "はんせん,ほぶね",
      "meaning": "sailing ship, sailing boat, sailing vessel"
    },
    {
      "question": "漫画家",
      "answer": "まんがか",
      "meaning": "cartoonist, comic book artist, manga artist, manga author, mangaka"
    },
    {
      "question": "半狂乱",
      "answer": "はんきょうらん",
      "meaning": "half-crazed, frantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "探求",
      "answer": "たんきゅう",
      "meaning": "search, quest, pursuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "突然変異",
      "answer": "とつぜんへんい",
      "meaning": "mutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "総量",
      "answer": "そうりょう",
      "meaning": "aggregate amount"
    },
    {
      "question": "点る",
      "answer": "ともる,とぼる",
      "meaning": "to be lit (e.g. candle, lamp, light bulb), to be lighted, to be burning"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り去る",
      "answer": "とりさる",
      "meaning": "to remove, to eliminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "巡査",
      "answer": "じゅんさ",
      "meaning": "police officer, policeman, constable"
    },
    {
      "question": "梅干し",
      "answer": "うめぼし",
      "meaning": "umeboshi, pickled dried ume, pickled dried plum"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜目",
      "answer": "よめ",
      "meaning": "in the dark"
    },
    {
      "question": "下世話",
      "answer": "げせわ",
      "meaning": "common saying, everyday talk, common parlance"
    },
    {
      "question": "初夜",
      "answer": "しょや",
      "meaning": "first night, first watch of the night, bridal night"
    },
    {
      "question": "白昼夢",
      "answer": "はくちゅうむ",
      "meaning": "daydream, waking dream"
    },
    {
      "question": "口約束",
      "answer": "くちやくそく",
      "meaning": "verbal promise, one's word"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉厚",
      "answer": "にくあつ",
      "meaning": "thick, meaty, fleshy"
    },
    {
      "question": "島国",
      "answer": "しまぐに,とうごく",
      "meaning": "island country"
    },
    {
      "question": "同士討ち",
      "answer": "どうしうち,どしうち",
      "meaning": "friendly fire, killing each other by mistake, internecine strife"
    },
    {
      "question": "葡萄酒",
      "answer": "ぶどうしゅ",
      "meaning": "(grape) wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "未確認",
      "answer": "みかくにん",
      "meaning": "unconfirmed, unidentified"
    },
    {
      "question": "一陣",
      "answer": "いちじん",
      "meaning": "gust of wind, vanguard"
    },
    {
      "question": "為になる",
      "answer": "ためになる",
      "meaning": "to be of benefit, to be useful, to be good for you"
    },
    {
      "question": "兼任",
      "answer": "けんにん",
      "meaning": "serving concurrently as, holding the additional post of"
    },
    {
      "question": "謎解き",
      "answer": "なぞとき",
      "meaning": "solution of a riddle"
    },
    {
      "question": "付加",
      "answer": "ふか",
      "meaning": "addition, annexation, appendage"
    },
    {
      "question": "同窓会",
      "answer": "どうそうかい",
      "meaning": "alumni association, graduates' association, alumni meeting, class reunion"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰結",
      "answer": "きけつ",
      "meaning": "consequence, result, conclusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉体労働",
      "answer": "にくたいろうどう",
      "meaning": "manual or physical labor, manual or physical labour"
    },
    {
      "question": "死罪",
      "answer": "しざい",
      "meaning": "capital crime, crime resulting in a death penalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "三重",
      "answer": "さんじゅう,みえ",
      "meaning": "triple, treble, threefold, three-ply, triplicate, Mie (prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "商い",
      "answer": "あきない",
      "meaning": "trade, business, trading, dealing, turnover, sales, takings"
    },
    {
      "question": "不適切",
      "answer": "ふてきせつ",
      "meaning": "unsuitable, inappropriate, improper"
    },
    {
      "question": "留守電",
      "answer": "るすでん",
      "meaning": "answering machine, answerphone"
    },
    {
      "question": "額縁",
      "answer": "がくぶち",
      "meaning": "frame (e.g. picture frame, decorative door frame, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小躍り",
      "answer": "こおどり",
      "meaning": "dancing or jumping for joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "救急",
      "answer": "きゅうきゅう",
      "meaning": "first-aid, emergency (aid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴衆",
      "answer": "ちょうしゅう",
      "meaning": "audience, attendance, hearers"
    },
    {
      "question": "交わり",
      "answer": "まじわり",
      "meaning": "acquaintance, relations, fellowship, sexual intercourse, intersection"
    },
    {
      "question": "捌き",
      "answer": "さばき",
      "meaning": "handling (e.g. knife, reins), control, use, -work (e.g. footwork), dealing with (e.g. customers), ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "白磁",
      "answer": "はくじ",
      "meaning": "white porcelain"
    },
    {
      "question": "体を張る",
      "answer": "からだをはる",
      "meaning": "to devote oneself wholeheartedly to, to sacrifice one's health for, to risk one's life"
    },
    {
      "question": "追い打ち",
      "answer": "おいうち",
      "meaning": "attacking a fleeing enemy, additional attack on a weakened enemy, additional blow to an already unfo"
    },
    {
      "question": "金網",
      "answer": "かなあみ",
      "meaning": "wire netting, wire mesh, wire screen, chain-link mesh"
    },
    {
      "question": "四角",
      "answer": "しかく",
      "meaning": "quadrilateral, square"
    },
    {
      "question": "改竄",
      "answer": "かいざん",
      "meaning": "alteration, falsification, faking"
    },
    {
      "question": "臓物",
      "answer": "ぞうもつ",
      "meaning": "entrails, giblets, tripe, offal"
    },
    {
      "question": "燐光",
      "answer": "りんこう",
      "meaning": "phosphorescence"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏山",
      "answer": "うらやま",
      "meaning": "mountain (or hill) behind a house, village, etc., side of a mountain that gets little sunshine, envi"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務員",
      "answer": "じむいん",
      "meaning": "clerk, office worker, office staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓挫",
      "answer": "とんざ",
      "meaning": "setback, deadlock, being at a standstill or impasse"
    },
    {
      "question": "涼む",
      "answer": "すずむ",
      "meaning": "to cool oneself, to cool off, to enjoy the cool air"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き置き",
      "answer": "かきおき",
      "meaning": "note (letter) left behind, will"
    },
    {
      "question": "下々",
      "answer": "しもじも,したじた",
      "meaning": "the lower classes, the common people"
    },
    {
      "question": "棄てる",
      "answer": "すてる",
      "meaning": "to throw away, to cast away, to dump, to discard, to abandon, to desert, to leave, to give up, to re"
    },
    {
      "question": "煌めき",
      "answer": "きらめき",
      "meaning": "glitter, glimmer, sparkle, twinkle"
    },
    {
      "question": "担保",
      "answer": "たんぽ",
      "meaning": "security, guarantee, collateral (e.g. mortgage)"
    },
    {
      "question": "思案顔",
      "answer": "しあんがお",
      "meaning": "pensive (or worried) look on one's face"
    },
    {
      "question": "向上心",
      "answer": "こうじょうしん",
      "meaning": "ambition, aspiration, desire to improve oneself"
    },
    {
      "question": "等分",
      "answer": "とうぶん",
      "meaning": "division into equal parts, equal parts"
    },
    {
      "question": "頓着",
      "answer": "とんちゃく,とんじゃく",
      "meaning": "being concerned about or mindful of"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏族",
      "answer": "しぞく",
      "meaning": "clan, family"
    },
    {
      "question": "府",
      "answer": "ふ",
      "meaning": "(metropolitan) prefecture (of Osaka and Kyoto), the centre or seat (of) (center), (government) offic"
    },
    {
      "question": "賠償",
      "answer": "ばいしょう",
      "meaning": "compensation, reparations, indemnity, damages"
    },
    {
      "question": "紙面",
      "answer": "しめん",
      "meaning": "space on a page (e.g. in a newspaper), surface of paper, letter, writings, document"
    },
    {
      "question": "手狭",
      "answer": "てぜま",
      "meaning": "narrow, small, cramped"
    },
    {
      "question": "例外的",
      "answer": "れいがいてき",
      "meaning": "exceptional"
    },
    {
      "question": "何々",
      "answer": "なになに",
      "meaning": "what, so-and-so, such and such, something (or other), what?, wait, hang on, well, well, let's see, n"
    },
    {
      "question": "規格",
      "answer": "きかく",
      "meaning": "standard, norm"
    },
    {
      "question": "万引き",
      "answer": "まんびき",
      "meaning": "shoplifting, shoplifter"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶菓子",
      "answer": "ちゃがし",
      "meaning": "cake served with tea, teacake"
    },
    {
      "question": "求愛",
      "answer": "きゅうあい",
      "meaning": "courting, wooing, making advances"
    },
    {
      "question": "似合い",
      "answer": "にあい",
      "meaning": "well-matched (esp. of a couple), becoming, suitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "前倒し",
      "answer": "まえだおし",
      "meaning": "moving forward (e.g. plans), acceleration (e.g. of payment schedule), front-loading"
    },
    {
      "question": "定評",
      "answer": "ていひょう",
      "meaning": "established reputation"
    },
    {
      "question": "仇敵",
      "answer": "きゅうてき",
      "meaning": "bitter enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "解任",
      "answer": "かいにん",
      "meaning": "dismissal (from a post), discharge, removal"
    },
    {
      "question": "節々",
      "answer": "ふしぶし",
      "meaning": "joints, points (of a speech)"
    },
    {
      "question": "冥府",
      "answer": "めいふ",
      "meaning": "realm of the dead, the other world, underworld, hell"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯ブラシ",
      "answer": "はブラシ",
      "meaning": "toothbrush"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜勤",
      "answer": "やきん",
      "meaning": "night shift"
    },
    {
      "question": "清水",
      "answer": "しみず,せいすい,きよみず",
      "meaning": "spring water, clear (pure) water"
    },
    {
      "question": "車窓",
      "answer": "しゃそう",
      "meaning": "train window, car window"
    },
    {
      "question": "働かす",
      "answer": "はたらかす",
      "meaning": "to put someone to work, to make someone work"
    },
    {
      "question": "金品",
      "answer": "きんぴん",
      "meaning": "money and goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "射手",
      "answer": "いて,しゃしゅ",
      "meaning": "archer, shooter, bowman"
    },
    {
      "question": "手形",
      "answer": "てがた",
      "meaning": "draft, draught, promissory note, bill, handprint, signed hand-print"
    },
    {
      "question": "賞味期限",
      "answer": "しょうみきげん",
      "meaning": "'best before' date (food), sell-by date"
    },
    {
      "question": "創造主",
      "answer": "そうぞうしゅ,そうぞうぬし",
      "meaning": "Creator"
    },
    {
      "question": "統計",
      "answer": "とうけい",
      "meaning": "statistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "相思相愛",
      "answer": "そうしそうあい",
      "meaning": "mutual love"
    },
    {
      "question": "燃費",
      "answer": "ねんぴ",
      "meaning": "fuel consumption, gas mileage"
    },
    {
      "question": "蓄え",
      "answer": "たくわえ",
      "meaning": "store, reserve, stock, savings"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫌疑",
      "answer": "けんぎ",
      "meaning": "suspicion"
    },
    {
      "question": "人工知能",
      "answer": "じんこうちのう",
      "meaning": "artificial intelligence, AI"
    },
    {
      "question": "各部",
      "answer": "かくぶ",
      "meaning": "all parts, various parts, every department"
    },
    {
      "question": "床板",
      "answer": "ゆかいた,しょうばん,とこいた",
      "meaning": "floorboard, alcove slab, wooden board placed in a tokonoma, baseboard, base plate"
    },
    {
      "question": "護送",
      "answer": "ごそう",
      "meaning": "escort (e.g. under guard), convoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "脚色",
      "answer": "きゃくしょく",
      "meaning": "dramatization (e.g. of a novel), dramatisation, adaptation, dramatization, embellishment, exaggerati"
    },
    {
      "question": "方程式",
      "answer": "ほうていしき",
      "meaning": "equation, formula, method for solving a problem, set way of achieving a particular result"
    },
    {
      "question": "作曲",
      "answer": "さっきょく",
      "meaning": "composition, setting (of music)"
    },
    {
      "question": "成り立ち",
      "answer": "なりたち",
      "meaning": "the way in which something came about, origin, structure, organization, the way something is constru"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢幻",
      "answer": "むげん,ゆめまぼろし",
      "meaning": "dreams, fantasy, visions"
    },
    {
      "question": "汚点",
      "answer": "おてん",
      "meaning": "stain, blot, flaw, disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "今朝方",
      "answer": "けさがた",
      "meaning": "this morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "棚上げ",
      "answer": "たなあげ",
      "meaning": "shelving, pigeonholing"
    },
    {
      "question": "危ぶむ",
      "answer": "あやぶむ",
      "meaning": "to fear, to doubt, to have misgivings about, to worry about, to be anxious about, to be apprehensive"
    },
    {
      "question": "扇ぐ",
      "answer": "あおぐ",
      "meaning": "to fan, to incite, to instigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "切手",
      "answer": "きって,きれて",
      "meaning": "stamp (postage), merchandise certificate, man of ability"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞬発力",
      "answer": "しゅんぱつりょく",
      "meaning": "high power, high power output, explosiveness, explosive power, instantaneous force"
    },
    {
      "question": "内股",
      "answer": "うちまた,うちもも",
      "meaning": "inner thigh, (walking) pigeon-toed, one's toes turned inward, uchimata (judo), throwing an opponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "必勝",
      "answer": "ひっしょう",
      "meaning": "certain victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "玉子",
      "answer": "たまご",
      "meaning": "(hen's) egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "悔恨",
      "answer": "かいこん",
      "meaning": "regret, remorse, repentance, contrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "値打ち",
      "answer": "ねうち",
      "meaning": "value, worth, merit, estimation, evaluation, appraisal"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷凍庫",
      "answer": "れいとうこ",
      "meaning": "freezer"
    },
    {
      "question": "走り込む",
      "answer": "はしりこむ",
      "meaning": "to run into (room, building, etc.), to go for long training runs"
    },
    {
      "question": "改築",
      "answer": "かいちく",
      "meaning": "structural alteration (of a building), reconstruction, rebuilding, remodelling, remodeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "家計",
      "answer": "かけい",
      "meaning": "household economy, family finances"
    },
    {
      "question": "試験官",
      "answer": "しけんかん",
      "meaning": "examiner"
    },
    {
      "question": "見落とし",
      "answer": "みおとし",
      "meaning": "oversight, omission, something overlooked, thing left unnoticed"
    },
    {
      "question": "預かり",
      "answer": "あずかり",
      "meaning": "under custody, under supervision, undecided match, draw, tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "花柄",
      "answer": "はながら,かへい",
      "meaning": "flower pattern, peduncle"
    },
    {
      "question": "窯",
      "answer": "かま",
      "meaning": "stove, furnace, kiln"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝陽",
      "answer": "ちょうよう",
      "meaning": "morning sun, sunrise"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆弾発言",
      "answer": "ばくだんはつげん",
      "meaning": "bombshell announcement (statement)"
    },
    {
      "question": "要所",
      "answer": "ようしょ",
      "meaning": "important point, important position"
    },
    {
      "question": "表層",
      "answer": "ひょうそう",
      "meaning": "surface, outer layer"
    },
    {
      "question": "首脳",
      "answer": "しゅのう",
      "meaning": "head, leader, top, important part"
    },
    {
      "question": "横幅",
      "answer": "よこはば",
      "meaning": "breadth, width"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋風",
      "answer": "ようふう",
      "meaning": "Western style"
    },
    {
      "question": "供える",
      "answer": "そなえる",
      "meaning": "to offer, to sacrifice, to dedicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭ごなし",
      "answer": "あたまごなし",
      "meaning": "unsparingly, without listening to the other party, without giving the other party a chance to explai"
    },
    {
      "question": "超す",
      "answer": "こす",
      "meaning": "to cross over (e.g. mountain), to go across, to get over (e.g. hardship), to pass time (e.g. a winte"
    },
    {
      "question": "太っ腹",
      "answer": "ふとっぱら",
      "meaning": "generous, magnanimous, big-hearted, broad-minded, big-bellied"
    },
    {
      "question": "攻守",
      "answer": "こうしゅ",
      "meaning": "offense and defense, offence and defence, batting and fielding"
    },
    {
      "question": "手芸",
      "answer": "しゅげい",
      "meaning": "handicrafts"
    },
    {
      "question": "表彰",
      "answer": "ひょうしょう",
      "meaning": "public acknowledgment, public acknowledgement, public recognition, commendation, awarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡し",
      "answer": "わたし",
      "meaning": "ferry (crossing), ferry(boat), delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "端整",
      "answer": "たんせい",
      "meaning": "handsome, shapely, clean-cut (features)"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻挫",
      "answer": "ねんざ",
      "meaning": "sprain, twist, wrench"
    },
    {
      "question": "広め",
      "answer": "ひろめ",
      "meaning": "making something widely known, introduction, debut, announcement, unveiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "足枷",
      "answer": "あしかせ",
      "meaning": "fetters, shackles, hobbles, encumbrance, hindrance, burden, trap"
    },
    {
      "question": "思考力",
      "answer": "しこうりょく",
      "meaning": "ability to think"
    },
    {
      "question": "武勇",
      "answer": "ぶゆう",
      "meaning": "bravery, military prowess, valour, valor"
    },
    {
      "question": "雇われ",
      "answer": "やとわれ",
      "meaning": "person working for someone else (followed by job title), hired"
    },
    {
      "question": "添付",
      "answer": "てんぷ",
      "meaning": "attaching (documents, etc.), appending, affixing"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み敷く",
      "answer": "くみしく",
      "meaning": "to press down, to hold down, to pin down"
    },
    {
      "question": "異端審問",
      "answer": "いたんしんもん",
      "meaning": "the Inquisition"
    },
    {
      "question": "白雪",
      "answer": "しらゆき,はくせつ",
      "meaning": "white snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕が立つ",
      "answer": "うでがたつ",
      "meaning": "to be talented, to be able"
    },
    {
      "question": "正方形",
      "answer": "せいほうけい",
      "meaning": "square"
    },
    {
      "question": "並走",
      "answer": "へいそう",
      "meaning": "running parallel (to), running side-by-side, keeping pace (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "機関銃",
      "answer": "きかんじゅう",
      "meaning": "machine gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "儀礼",
      "answer": "ぎれい",
      "meaning": "etiquette, courtesy"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳醇",
      "answer": "ほうじゅん",
      "meaning": "mellow (flavor or fragrance, esp. alcohol), rich, full-bodied, superior"
    },
    {
      "question": "紐解く",
      "answer": "ひもとく",
      "meaning": "to read (a book), to open (a book) to read, to unravel (e.g. a mystery), to discover (the truth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "人徳",
      "answer": "じんとく,にんとく",
      "meaning": "natural virtue, personal virtue"
    },
    {
      "question": "条件付き",
      "answer": "じょうけんつき",
      "meaning": "conditionally, with conditions attached"
    },
    {
      "question": "陶然",
      "answer": "とうぜん",
      "meaning": "intoxicated (by liquor or music), entranced, enraptured"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩師",
      "answer": "おんし",
      "meaning": "teacher (to whom one owes a debt of gratitude), mentor, one's former teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "特急",
      "answer": "とっきゅう",
      "meaning": "limited express (train for which a limited-express ticket is required), limited express (train makin"
    },
    {
      "question": "薙刀",
      "answer": "なぎなた",
      "meaning": "naginata, polearm with a curved single-edged blade (similar to a glaive), martial art of wielding th"
    },
    {
      "question": "持",
      "answer": "じ",
      "meaning": "draw (in go, poetry contest, etc.), tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "特段",
      "answer": "とくだん",
      "meaning": "special"
    },
    {
      "question": "無策",
      "answer": "むさく",
      "meaning": "lack of policy, having no measures, lacking means"
    },
    {
      "question": "狼煙",
      "answer": "のろし,ろうえん",
      "meaning": "beacon, skyrocket, signal fire, smoke signals, starting shot, starting signal"
    },
    {
      "question": "別状",
      "answer": "べつじょう",
      "meaning": "something unusual, something wrong, mishap, accident, serious condition (e.g. after an injury), diff"
    },
    {
      "question": "受け入れ",
      "answer": "うけいれ",
      "meaning": "receiving, acceptance, reception"
    },
    {
      "question": "遅延",
      "answer": "ちえん",
      "meaning": "delay, latency"
    },
    {
      "question": "因果関係",
      "answer": "いんがかんけい",
      "meaning": "consequence, causal relationship, nexus"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦前",
      "answer": "せんぜん",
      "meaning": "pre-war days, before the war"
    },
    {
      "question": "慧眼",
      "answer": "けいがん,えげん",
      "meaning": "discerning (quick) eye, keen insight, the wisdom eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍び足",
      "answer": "しのびあし",
      "meaning": "stealthy steps, soft steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "徳",
      "answer": "とく",
      "meaning": "virtue, benevolence, profit, benefit, advantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "甲殻",
      "answer": "こうかく",
      "meaning": "carapace, shell, crust"
    },
    {
      "question": "離陸",
      "answer": "りりく",
      "meaning": "takeoff"
    },
    {
      "question": "執念深い",
      "answer": "しゅうねんぶかい",
      "meaning": "vindictive, tenacious, persistent, spiteful, vengeful"
    },
    {
      "question": "系列",
      "answer": "けいれつ",
      "meaning": "series, sequence, system, succession, keiretsu (group), conglomeration of businesses linked by cross"
    },
    {
      "question": "教祖",
      "answer": "きょうそ",
      "meaning": "founder of a religious sect"
    },
    {
      "question": "満タン",
      "answer": "まんタン",
      "meaning": "full tank, filling up the tank"
    },
    {
      "question": "感電",
      "answer": "かんでん",
      "meaning": "receiving an electric shock"
    },
    {
      "question": "成金",
      "answer": "なりきん",
      "meaning": "upstart, nouveau riche, new money, new rich, coming into wealth suddenly, piece promoted to gold gen"
    },
    {
      "question": "話が合う",
      "answer": "はなしがあう",
      "meaning": "to see eye to eye, to be on the same wavelength, to talk the same language"
    },
    {
      "question": "水球",
      "answer": "すいきゅう",
      "meaning": "water polo"
    },
    {
      "question": "千万",
      "answer": "せんばん,せんまん,ちよろず",
      "meaning": "exceedingly, extremely, very many, indeed, 10,000,000, ten million, extremely large number, myriad,"
    },
    {
      "question": "心頭",
      "answer": "しんとう",
      "meaning": "heart, mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "芳香",
      "answer": "ほうこう",
      "meaning": "perfume, fragrance, aroma, balm, sweet scent"
    },
    {
      "question": "種明かし",
      "answer": "たねあかし",
      "meaning": "reveal of how a trick is done, disclosure of a secret (cause, source, etc.), exposure, explanation"
    },
    {
      "question": "左翼",
      "answer": "さよく",
      "meaning": "left-wing (politics), left wing (of a bird, aircraft, formation, etc.), left flank, left field"
    },
    {
      "question": "駅員",
      "answer": "えきいん",
      "meaning": "(train) station attendant, station employee, station staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "波打ち際",
      "answer": "なみうちぎわ",
      "meaning": "water's edge, beach, foreshore"
    },
    {
      "question": "家人",
      "answer": "かじん,けにん",
      "meaning": "occupant of a house, family member, household member (incl. servant), retainer, vassal, servant"
    },
    {
      "question": "驕る",
      "answer": "おごる",
      "meaning": "to give (someone) a treat, to be extravagant, to live luxuriously, to be proud, to be haughty"
    },
    {
      "question": "日帰り",
      "answer": "ひがえり",
      "meaning": "day trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "大馬鹿",
      "answer": "おおばか",
      "meaning": "extreme foolishness, grave stupidity, big fool, damn idiot, utter fool"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲間同士",
      "answer": "なかまどうし",
      "meaning": "peers, friends, fellow workers, comrades"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠縁",
      "answer": "とおえん",
      "meaning": "distant relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲み屋",
      "answer": "のみや",
      "meaning": "bar, saloon, pub, tavern, drinking establishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈴口",
      "answer": "すずぐち",
      "meaning": "entrance to a daimyo's mansion, glans (of the penis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "捕食者",
      "answer": "ほしょくしゃ",
      "meaning": "predator"
    },
    {
      "question": "決然",
      "answer": "けつぜん",
      "meaning": "decisive, resolute, determined"
    },
    {
      "question": "付け込む",
      "answer": "つけこむ",
      "meaning": "to take advantage of, to impose on, to make an entry (in an account book)"
    },
    {
      "question": "口端",
      "answer": "くちは,こうたん",
      "meaning": "gossip, corner of the mouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "下水道",
      "answer": "げすいどう",
      "meaning": "sewer, sewer system, sewerage, drain"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然界",
      "answer": "しぜんかい",
      "meaning": "nature, the natural world, realm of nature"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫉妬深い",
      "answer": "しっとぶかい",
      "meaning": "(deeply) jealous"
    },
    {
      "question": "精力",
      "answer": "せいりょく",
      "meaning": "energy, vigor, vigour, vitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾き出す",
      "answer": "はじきだす",
      "meaning": "to flick out, to spring out, to repel, to calculate, to work out, to expel (from a group), to drive"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰り着く",
      "answer": "かえりつく",
      "meaning": "to arrive home, to return"
    },
    {
      "question": "散弾",
      "answer": "さんだん",
      "meaning": "shot, buckshot"
    },
    {
      "question": "黙殺",
      "answer": "もくさつ",
      "meaning": "ignoring, disregarding, taking no notice of, refusing to comment on, turning a deaf ear to"
    },
    {
      "question": "中層",
      "answer": "ちゅうそう",
      "meaning": "middle part, medium depth (water), medium layer, middle lamella, medium-size, mid-level, medium-rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "両軍",
      "answer": "りょうぐん",
      "meaning": "both armies, both teams"
    },
    {
      "question": "大部屋",
      "answer": "おおべや",
      "meaning": "large room, green room, waiting room for performers when off stage, junior actor, actor of small par"
    },
    {
      "question": "届け物",
      "answer": "とどけもの",
      "meaning": "article to be delivered, present"
    },
    {
      "question": "疎通",
      "answer": "そつう",
      "meaning": "(mutual) understanding, communication, passing without obstruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "生命線",
      "answer": "せいめいせん",
      "meaning": "lifeline, matter of life or death, indispensable thing, life line (in palm reading)"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶解",
      "answer": "ようかい",
      "meaning": "dissolution, dissolving, solution (e.g. chemical), melting, liquefying, fusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "明快",
      "answer": "めいかい",
      "meaning": "clear, clear-cut, lucid, unequivocal, explicit"
    },
    {
      "question": "聞き耳",
      "answer": "ききみみ",
      "meaning": "straining one's ears"
    },
    {
      "question": "年越し",
      "answer": "としこし",
      "meaning": "New Year's Eve, end of the year"
    },
    {
      "question": "払い",
      "answer": "はらい",
      "meaning": "payment, bill, account, sweeping, clearing away, sweeping stroke (e.g. when writing kanji)"
    },
    {
      "question": "但し",
      "answer": "ただし",
      "meaning": "but, however, provided that"
    },
    {
      "question": "掠る",
      "answer": "かする",
      "meaning": "to graze (e.g. bullet), to scratch, to touch lightly, to take a percentage, to exploit, to squeeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "実際問題",
      "answer": "じっさいもんだい",
      "meaning": "practical question (problem), practical matter"
    },
    {
      "question": "三方",
      "answer": "さんぼう,さんぽう,さんかた",
      "meaning": "three sides, small offering stand, day laborer (in construction, etc.), day labourer"
    },
    {
      "question": "絵柄",
      "answer": "えがら",
      "meaning": "pattern, design"
    },
    {
      "question": "老齢",
      "answer": "ろうれい",
      "meaning": "advanced age, senility"
    },
    {
      "question": "待望",
      "answer": "たいぼう",
      "meaning": "waiting expectantly, waiting eagerly, looking forward to, long-awaited"
    },
    {
      "question": "治世",
      "answer": "ちせい,じせい",
      "meaning": "rule, reign, peaceful times"
    },
    {
      "question": "喩える",
      "answer": "たとえる",
      "meaning": "to compare (something) to, to liken, to speak figuratively, to use a simile, to use a metaphor"
    },
    {
      "question": "密林",
      "answer": "みつりん",
      "meaning": "close thicket, dense forest, jungle, amazon.com"
    },
    {
      "question": "気苦労",
      "answer": "きぐろう",
      "meaning": "worry, care, anxiety, mental exhaustion"
    },
    {
      "question": "義弟",
      "answer": "ぎてい,おとうと",
      "meaning": "brother-in-law (spouse's younger brother or younger sister's husband), younger stepbrother"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き方",
      "answer": "かきかた",
      "meaning": "way of writing, manner of writing, penmanship (esp. used in old textbooks), calligraphy, format (e.g"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒波",
      "answer": "あらなみ",
      "meaning": "raging waves, stormy seas, hardships, troubles, adversities"
    },
    {
      "question": "美麗",
      "answer": "びれい",
      "meaning": "beautiful, gorgeous"
    },
    {
      "question": "通勤",
      "answer": "つうきん",
      "meaning": "commuting to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち返す",
      "answer": "うちかえす",
      "meaning": "to return a blow repeat, to turn back, to rewhip, to plow up, to plough up, to come and retreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "呈する",
      "answer": "ていする",
      "meaning": "to present, to offer, to show, to display, to exhibit, to assume (e.g. a shape)"
    },
    {
      "question": "命題",
      "answer": "めいだい",
      "meaning": "proposition, thesis, notion, theory, problem, issue, challenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "無鉄砲",
      "answer": "むてっぽう",
      "meaning": "rash, reckless"
    },
    {
      "question": "総て",
      "answer": "すべて",
      "meaning": "everything, all, the whole, entirely, completely, wholly"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆境",
      "answer": "ぎゃっきょう",
      "meaning": "adverse circumstances, adversity"
    },
    {
      "question": "起爆",
      "answer": "きばく",
      "meaning": "ignition, detonation, triggering, explosion"
    },
    {
      "question": "不敬罪",
      "answer": "ふけいざい",
      "meaning": "lese majesty, lèse-majesté"
    },
    {
      "question": "工",
      "answer": "たくみ,こう",
      "meaning": "workman, artisan, mechanic, carpenter, craft, skill, means, idea, (factory) worker"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒状",
      "answer": "ぼうじょう",
      "meaning": "cylinder or rod-shaped"
    },
    {
      "question": "悉く",
      "answer": "ことごとく",
      "meaning": "altogether, entirely"
    },
    {
      "question": "動体視力",
      "answer": "どうたいしりょく",
      "meaning": "dynamic visual acuity, DVA, kinetic vision, ability to identify objects in motion"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼き殺す",
      "answer": "やきころす",
      "meaning": "to kill by burning to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "横腹",
      "answer": "よこばら",
      "meaning": "side, flank"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮き輪",
      "answer": "うきわ",
      "meaning": "swim ring, (rubber) swimming ring, life buoy, life belt, float"
    },
    {
      "question": "超常",
      "answer": "ちょうじょう",
      "meaning": "paranormality, anomalous phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "question": "盤石",
      "answer": "ばんじゃく",
      "meaning": "huge rock, firmness, solidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "表沙汰",
      "answer": "おもてざた",
      "meaning": "going public (with a matter), becoming public knowledge, recourse to litigation, taking (a matter) t"
    },
    {
      "question": "理想郷",
      "answer": "りそうきょう",
      "meaning": "ideal land, earthly paradise, Utopia, Arcadia"
    },
    {
      "question": "着火",
      "answer": "ちゃっか",
      "meaning": "ignition, catching fire, setting on fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "合法的",
      "answer": "ごうほうてき",
      "meaning": "legal, lawful, legitimate, law-abiding, in order"
    },
    {
      "question": "哀愁",
      "answer": "あいしゅう",
      "meaning": "pathos, sorrow, grief"
    },
    {
      "question": "裡",
      "answer": "り",
      "meaning": "in (e.g. secret), with (e.g. success)"
    },
    {
      "question": "恥ずべき",
      "answer": "はずべき",
      "meaning": "disgraceful, shameful"
    },
    {
      "question": "窺い知る",
      "answer": "うかがいしる",
      "meaning": "to perceive, to understand"
    },
    {
      "question": "婿入り",
      "answer": "むこいり",
      "meaning": "being adopted into the family of one's bride"
    },
    {
      "question": "銀糸",
      "answer": "ぎんし",
      "meaning": "silver thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "街路樹",
      "answer": "がいろじゅ",
      "meaning": "roadside trees"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦国時代",
      "answer": "せんごくじだい",
      "meaning": "Warring States period (of Japanese history, approx. 1467-1568 CE), Sengoku period, Warring States pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "河川敷",
      "answer": "かせんじき,かせんしき",
      "meaning": "flood plain, river terrace, riverside area, area between river and river bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "両面",
      "answer": "りょうめん,リャンメン",
      "meaning": "both sides, two sides, double-sided, double-sided wait (for one's last tile), wait for either of two"
    },
    {
      "question": "安全装置",
      "answer": "あんぜんそうち",
      "meaning": "safety device"
    },
    {
      "question": "喫する",
      "answer": "きっする",
      "meaning": "to eat, to drink, to smoke, to take, to suffer (e.g. defeat), to receive a blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "眇める",
      "answer": "すがめる",
      "meaning": "to scrutinize, to scrutinise"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼肉",
      "answer": "やきにく",
      "meaning": "yakiniku, Japanese dish of grilled meat similar to Korean barbecue, roasted meat, grill"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠匿",
      "answer": "いんとく",
      "meaning": "concealment"
    },
    {
      "question": "主席",
      "answer": "しゅせき",
      "meaning": "head, chief, chairman, governor, president, top seat, first desk (in orchestra)"
    },
    {
      "question": "辺鄙",
      "answer": "へんぴ",
      "meaning": "hard to reach place, remote place"
    },
    {
      "question": "一喜一憂",
      "answer": "いっきいちゆう",
      "meaning": "now rejoicing, now worrying, swinging from joy to sorrow, glad and sad by turns, alternating hope an"
    },
    {
      "question": "学会",
      "answer": "がっかい",
      "meaning": "learned society, scientific society, academy, academic meeting, academic conference"
    },
    {
      "question": "先約",
      "answer": "せんやく",
      "meaning": "previous engagement, prior contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "古今東西",
      "answer": "ここんとうざい",
      "meaning": "all times and places, all ages and countries"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶道",
      "answer": "さどう,ちゃどう",
      "meaning": "tea ceremony, Way of Tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "柑橘",
      "answer": "かんきつ",
      "meaning": "citrus, citrus fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "妨げ",
      "answer": "さまたげ",
      "meaning": "obstruction, hindrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "目利き",
      "answer": "めきき",
      "meaning": "judgement, judgment, connoisseur"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺し貫く",
      "answer": "さしつらぬく",
      "meaning": "to pierce"
    },
    {
      "question": "名札",
      "answer": "なふだ",
      "meaning": "name plate, name tag, label"
    },
    {
      "question": "待ち人",
      "answer": "まちびと",
      "meaning": "person being waited for, person who waits"
    },
    {
      "question": "太平洋",
      "answer": "たいへいよう",
      "meaning": "Pacific Ocean"
    },
    {
      "question": "海の家",
      "answer": "うみのいえ",
      "meaning": "beach hut, beachside clubhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "送還",
      "answer": "そうかん",
      "meaning": "sending home, repatriation, deportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "指揮者",
      "answer": "しきしゃ",
      "meaning": "(musical) conductor, commander, leader, director"
    },
    {
      "question": "見掛ける",
      "answer": "みかける",
      "meaning": "to (happen to) see, to notice, to catch sight of"
    },
    {
      "question": "供述",
      "answer": "きょうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "affidavit, deposition, testimony"
    },
    {
      "question": "手洗い",
      "answer": "てあらい",
      "meaning": "washing one's hands, water (or basin, etc.) for washing one's hands, restroom, lavatory, toilet, han"
    },
    {
      "question": "老女",
      "answer": "ろうじょ,おうな",
      "meaning": "elderly woman, senior lady-in-waiting"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇策",
      "answer": "きさく",
      "meaning": "bizarre plan, perplexing strategy, outlandish scheme"
    },
    {
      "question": "不浄",
      "answer": "ふじょう",
      "meaning": "uncleanliness, dirtiness, impurity, filthiness, defilement, menses, feces (faeces), bathroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "大挙",
      "answer": "たいきょ",
      "meaning": "in full force, in great numbers, in droves, large-scale project, grand plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "並外れる",
      "answer": "なみはずれる",
      "meaning": "to be uncommon"
    },
    {
      "question": "小振り",
      "answer": "こぶり",
      "meaning": "smallish, on the small side, somewhat small, undersized, small size, short swing of a bat, racquet,"
    },
    {
      "question": "協調性",
      "answer": "きょうちょうせい",
      "meaning": "cooperativeness, spirit of cooperation"
    },
    {
      "question": "特許",
      "answer": "とっきょ",
      "meaning": "patent, special permission, licence (license), concession, franchise, charter, proprietary"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱",
      "answer": "だつ",
      "meaning": "de- (indicating reversal, removal, etc.), post-"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙たい",
      "answer": "けむたい,けぶたい",
      "meaning": "smoky, awkward, ill at ease"
    },
    {
      "question": "混同",
      "answer": "こんどう",
      "meaning": "confusion, mixing, merger"
    },
    {
      "question": "回帰",
      "answer": "かいき",
      "meaning": "return (to), revolution, recurrence, regression"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り切れ",
      "answer": "うりきれ",
      "meaning": "sold-out"
    },
    {
      "question": "公衆電話",
      "answer": "こうしゅうでんわ",
      "meaning": "public telephone, pay phone"
    },
    {
      "question": "過小評価",
      "answer": "かしょうひょうか",
      "meaning": "underestimation, undervaluation"
    },
    {
      "question": "年度",
      "answer": "ねんど",
      "meaning": "fiscal year (usu. April 1 to March 31 in Japan), financial year, academic year, school year, product"
    },
    {
      "question": "見所",
      "answer": "みどころ,けんじょ,けんしょ",
      "meaning": "point worthy of note, highlight, high point, main attraction, thing to note, good prospects for the"
    },
    {
      "question": "羊飼い",
      "answer": "ひつじかい",
      "meaning": "shepherd, shepherdess"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を結ぶ",
      "answer": "てをむすぶ",
      "meaning": "to join hands, to join forces, to work in cooperation, to link up, to partner with"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾倉",
      "answer": "だんそう",
      "meaning": "magazine (of a firearm)"
    },
    {
      "question": "横殴り",
      "answer": "よこなぐり",
      "meaning": "striking on the side, side blow, slanting (rain, snow, etc.), driving"
    },
    {
      "question": "根強い",
      "answer": "ねづよい",
      "meaning": "firmly rooted, deep-seated"
    },
    {
      "question": "奮戦",
      "answer": "ふんせん",
      "meaning": "hard fighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "契機",
      "answer": "けいき",
      "meaning": "opportunity, chance, trigger, cause"
    },
    {
      "question": "妖気",
      "answer": "ようき",
      "meaning": "ghostly air, weird air, unearthly atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "渡りに船",
      "answer": "わたりにふね",
      "meaning": "godsend, lifesaver, timely offer, windfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒盛り",
      "answer": "さかもり",
      "meaning": "drinking bout, merrymaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い手",
      "answer": "かいて",
      "meaning": "buyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇姿",
      "answer": "ゆうし",
      "meaning": "brave figure, valiant figure, heroic figure, gallant figure"
    },
    {
      "question": "書架",
      "answer": "しょか",
      "meaning": "bookshelf, bookcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "横断歩道",
      "answer": "おうだんほどう",
      "meaning": "pedestrian crossing, crosswalk"
    },
    {
      "question": "陸路",
      "answer": "りくろ",
      "meaning": "land route, overland route, by land, overland"
    },
    {
      "question": "一に",
      "answer": "いつに",
      "meaning": "solely, entirely, only, or"
    },
    {
      "question": "再興",
      "answer": "さいこう",
      "meaning": "revival, restoration, resuscitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "惨い",
      "answer": "むごい",
      "meaning": "cruel, merciless, pitiless, brutal, atrocious, inhuman, tragic, horrible, terrible, dreadful, misera"
    },
    {
      "question": "名所",
      "answer": "めいしょ,などころ",
      "meaning": "famous place, name of a part (of an instrument, etc.), name and address"
    },
    {
      "question": "法衣",
      "answer": "ほうい,ほうえ",
      "meaning": "vestment, priest's robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "報せる",
      "answer": "しらせる",
      "meaning": "to notify, to advise, to inform"
    },
    {
      "question": "扇風機",
      "answer": "せんぷうき",
      "meaning": "electric fan"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮病",
      "answer": "けびょう",
      "meaning": "feigned illness"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子大生",
      "answer": "じょしだいせい",
      "meaning": "female university student, female college student"
    },
    {
      "question": "骨董品",
      "answer": "こっとうひん",
      "meaning": "curio, antique"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼門",
      "answer": "きもん",
      "meaning": "the northeastern (unlucky) direction, person or thing to be avoided, the demon's gate, weak point, A"
    },
    {
      "question": "補完",
      "answer": "ほかん",
      "meaning": "complementation, supplementation, completion"
    },
    {
      "question": "見飽きる",
      "answer": "みあきる",
      "meaning": "to be tired of looking at"
    },
    {
      "question": "小豆",
      "answer": "あずき,しょうず",
      "meaning": "adzuki bean (Vigna angularis)"
    },
    {
      "question": "他言",
      "answer": "たげん,たごん",
      "meaning": "telling others, revealing to others, letting out a secret"
    },
    {
      "question": "仲間意識",
      "answer": "なかまいしき",
      "meaning": "feeling of fellowship, fellow feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦々恐々",
      "answer": "せんせんきょうきょう",
      "meaning": "trembling with fear, filled with trepidation"
    },
    {
      "question": "凄絶",
      "answer": "せいぜつ",
      "meaning": "extremely gruesome, lurid, violent, bloody, fierce"
    },
    {
      "question": "割り箸",
      "answer": "わりばし",
      "meaning": "dispensable chopsticks, throwaway chopsticks"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰険",
      "answer": "いんけん",
      "meaning": "crafty, tricky, sly, wily, treacherous, underhand, sinister (look)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞社",
      "answer": "しんぶんしゃ",
      "meaning": "newspaper company"
    },
    {
      "question": "挿絵",
      "answer": "さしえ",
      "meaning": "illustration (e.g. book), picture"
    },
    {
      "question": "巻き毛",
      "answer": "まきげ",
      "meaning": "curl, curly hair, ringlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "牡丹",
      "answer": "ぼたん",
      "meaning": "tree peony (Paeonia suffruticosa), moutan, wild boar (meat)"
    },
    {
      "question": "従妹",
      "answer": "じゅうまい,いとこ",
      "meaning": "cousin (younger female)"
    },
    {
      "question": "見極め",
      "answer": "みきわめ",
      "meaning": "ascertainment"
    },
    {
      "question": "署長",
      "answer": "しょちょう",
      "meaning": "chief (of police), head (of office)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白骨",
      "answer": "はっこつ",
      "meaning": "white (bleached) bone, skeleton"
    },
    {
      "question": "満員",
      "answer": "まんいん",
      "meaning": "full house, no vacancy, sold out, standing room only, full (of people), crowded"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び人",
      "answer": "あそびにん",
      "meaning": "playboy, libertine, profligate, debauchee, (professional) gambler, person without a steady job, idle"
    },
    {
      "question": "不出来",
      "answer": "ふでき",
      "meaning": "bad job, poor workmanship, bungle"
    },
    {
      "question": "口下手",
      "answer": "くちべた",
      "meaning": "inarticulate, clumsy with words, poor at speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "私用",
      "answer": "しよう",
      "meaning": "personal use, private use, private business, personal business"
    },
    {
      "question": "非戦闘員",
      "answer": "ひせんとういん",
      "meaning": "non-combatant, civilian"
    },
    {
      "question": "女物",
      "answer": "おんなもの",
      "meaning": "women's goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "軋轢",
      "answer": "あつれき",
      "meaning": "friction, discord, strife"
    },
    {
      "question": "亜種",
      "answer": "あしゅ",
      "meaning": "subspecies"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲行き",
      "answer": "くもゆき",
      "meaning": "weather, look of the sky, situation, turn of affairs, signs, way the wind is blowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "語調",
      "answer": "ごちょう",
      "meaning": "tone (of voice), parlance, style, intonation, accent"
    },
    {
      "question": "裂傷",
      "answer": "れっしょう",
      "meaning": "laceration"
    },
    {
      "question": "右翼",
      "answer": "うよく",
      "meaning": "right-wing (politics), extreme right-wing group, right wing (bird, plane, etc.), right field, right"
    },
    {
      "question": "息つく",
      "answer": "いきつく",
      "meaning": "to take a breath, to take a short rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "積み荷",
      "answer": "つみに",
      "meaning": "load, freight, cargo"
    },
    {
      "question": "可動",
      "answer": "かどう",
      "meaning": "mobile, moveable"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩盤",
      "answer": "がんばん",
      "meaning": "bedrock"
    },
    {
      "question": "悟り",
      "answer": "さとり",
      "meaning": "comprehension, understanding, enlightenment, spiritual awakening, satori"
    },
    {
      "question": "追試",
      "answer": "ついし",
      "meaning": "supplementary examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄せ集め",
      "answer": "よせあつめ",
      "meaning": "mishmash, miscellany, medley, jumble, mixture, odds and ends"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑木林",
      "answer": "ぞうきばやし,ぞうぼくりん",
      "meaning": "grove of miscellaneous trees, copse, coppice, thicket"
    },
    {
      "question": "早馬",
      "answer": "はやうま",
      "meaning": "fast horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "山岳",
      "answer": "さんがく",
      "meaning": "mountains"
    },
    {
      "question": "下衆",
      "answer": "げす",
      "meaning": "low-life, sleazebag, boor, person of humble rank, humble person, peasant, menial, churl, petty offic"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴場",
      "answer": "あなば",
      "meaning": "little-known good place, good out-of-the-way place, well-kept secret place, hole-in-the-wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "災いする",
      "answer": "わざわいする",
      "meaning": "to be the ruin of (a person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "総毛立つ",
      "answer": "そうけだつ",
      "meaning": "to get goosebumps, to have one's hair stand on end, to shudder"
    },
    {
      "question": "手痛い",
      "answer": "ていたい",
      "meaning": "severe, hard"
    },
    {
      "question": "生る",
      "answer": "なる",
      "meaning": "to bear fruit"
    },
    {
      "question": "形式的",
      "answer": "けいしきてき",
      "meaning": "formal"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳粛",
      "answer": "げんしゅく",
      "meaning": "grave, solemn, serious, harsh (e.g. truth), hard, strict"
    },
    {
      "question": "代表的",
      "answer": "だいひょうてき",
      "meaning": "representative, exemplary, model"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤々",
      "answer": "あかあか",
      "meaning": "bright red, bright"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲身",
      "answer": "ほうしん",
      "meaning": "gun barrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "直角",
      "answer": "ちょっかく",
      "meaning": "right angle, perpendicular"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶交",
      "answer": "ぜっこう",
      "meaning": "breaking off a relationship, permanent breach of friendship, rupture"
    },
    {
      "question": "両開き",
      "answer": "りょうびらき",
      "meaning": "double (two-leaf) door"
    },
    {
      "question": "背広",
      "answer": "せびろ",
      "meaning": "business suit"
    },
    {
      "question": "弓術",
      "answer": "きゅうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) archery"
    },
    {
      "question": "船室",
      "answer": "せんしつ",
      "meaning": "stateroom, cabin"
    },
    {
      "question": "便り",
      "answer": "たより,だより",
      "meaning": "news, tidings, information, correspondence, letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "始終",
      "answer": "しじゅう",
      "meaning": "continuously, from beginning to end, from first to last"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝珠",
      "answer": "ほうじゅ,ほうしゅ",
      "meaning": "precious orb, Cintamani stone, wish-fulfilling jewel, hōju, uppermost spherical part of a pagoda fin"
    },
    {
      "question": "教本",
      "answer": "きょうほん",
      "meaning": "textbook, manual"
    },
    {
      "question": "指折り",
      "answer": "ゆびおり",
      "meaning": "leading, prominent, eminent, foremost, distinguished, counting on one's fingers"
    },
    {
      "question": "淫猥",
      "answer": "いんわい",
      "meaning": "obscenity, obscene"
    },
    {
      "question": "胡椒",
      "answer": "こしょう",
      "meaning": "pepper"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏敬",
      "answer": "いけい",
      "meaning": "reverence, awe, respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "挟撃",
      "answer": "きょうげき",
      "meaning": "pincer movement, pincer attack"
    },
    {
      "question": "予鈴",
      "answer": "よれい",
      "meaning": "bell signalling that work, class, etc. will formally begin shortly, first bell, warning bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "解せない",
      "answer": "げせない",
      "meaning": "inscrutable, incomprehensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "膨らます",
      "answer": "ふくらます",
      "meaning": "to swell, to expand, to inflate, to bulge"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼却",
      "answer": "しょうきゃく",
      "meaning": "incineration, destroy by fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "衛士",
      "answer": "えじ,えいし",
      "meaning": "gate guard (during the ritsuryo system), gate guardian, young forced labour (ritsuryo system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最果て",
      "answer": "さいはて",
      "meaning": "the farthest ends, the furthest ends"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り殺す",
      "answer": "きりころす",
      "meaning": "to kill with a sword (knife, dagger, etc.), to slay, to put to the sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し開き",
      "answer": "もうしひらき",
      "meaning": "excuse, explanation, justification, defense, defence"
    },
    {
      "question": "死に場所",
      "answer": "しにばしょ",
      "meaning": "place to die, place of death"
    },
    {
      "question": "注目の的",
      "answer": "ちゅうもくのまと",
      "meaning": "centre of attention, center of attention"
    },
    {
      "question": "中傷",
      "answer": "ちゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "slander, libel, defamation, calumny, smear"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫁ぎ先",
      "answer": "とつぎさき",
      "meaning": "family a woman has married into"
    },
    {
      "question": "好青年",
      "answer": "こうせいねん",
      "meaning": "good young man, agreeable youth"
    },
    {
      "question": "新月",
      "answer": "しんげつ",
      "meaning": "new moon, crescent moon"
    },
    {
      "question": "怜悧",
      "answer": "れいり",
      "meaning": "clever, bright, sharp, wise, intelligent, sagacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "途上",
      "answer": "とじょう",
      "meaning": "on the way, en route, in the process of (development, construction, etc.), in the middle of"
    },
    {
      "question": "描き出す",
      "answer": "えがきだす",
      "meaning": "to delineate, to draw, to express, to imagine"
    },
    {
      "question": "仙",
      "answer": "セント,せん",
      "meaning": "cent (monetary unit), hermit, wizard, wizardry"
    },
    {
      "question": "舞踏",
      "answer": "ぶとう",
      "meaning": "dance (esp. Western style), dancing"
    },
    {
      "question": "老朽化",
      "answer": "ろうきゅうか",
      "meaning": "aging, wearing out, deterioration"
    },
    {
      "question": "直轄",
      "answer": "ちょっかつ",
      "meaning": "direct control"
    },
    {
      "question": "啓示",
      "answer": "けいじ",
      "meaning": "(divine) revelation"
    },
    {
      "question": "半殺し",
      "answer": "はんごろし",
      "meaning": "half killed"
    },
    {
      "question": "律動",
      "answer": "りつどう",
      "meaning": "rhythm"
    },
    {
      "question": "披露宴",
      "answer": "ひろうえん",
      "meaning": "reception (e.g. wedding), banquet, celebration, party"
    },
    {
      "question": "口喧嘩",
      "answer": "くちげんか,くちけんか",
      "meaning": "quarrel, dispute, argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "捩る",
      "answer": "ねじる,よじる,もじる",
      "meaning": "to screw, to twist, to distort, to parody, to make a pun, to torture, to wrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "技法",
      "answer": "ぎほう",
      "meaning": "technique"
    },
    {
      "question": "枝分かれ",
      "answer": "えだわかれ",
      "meaning": "ramification, branch"
    },
    {
      "question": "類する",
      "answer": "るいする,たぐいする",
      "meaning": "to be similar to, to be equal to, to be as good as, to be a match for, to rival"
    },
    {
      "question": "希",
      "answer": "まれ,ぎ,き",
      "meaning": "rare, seldom, Greece, Greek, Greco-, dilute"
    },
    {
      "question": "不屈",
      "answer": "ふくつ",
      "meaning": "persistence, fortitude, indomitability"
    },
    {
      "question": "善行",
      "answer": "ぜんこう",
      "meaning": "good deed, good conduct, benevolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭苦しい",
      "answer": "せまくるしい",
      "meaning": "cramped"
    },
    {
      "question": "神像",
      "answer": "しんぞう",
      "meaning": "idol (i.e. carving or painting of a deity)"
    },
    {
      "question": "麗人",
      "answer": "れいじん",
      "meaning": "beautiful woman, beauty, belle"
    },
    {
      "question": "毛穴",
      "answer": "けあな",
      "meaning": "pore (of the skin)"
    },
    {
      "question": "神代",
      "answer": "かみよ,じんだい",
      "meaning": "ancient time, age of the gods"
    },
    {
      "question": "各人",
      "answer": "かくじん",
      "meaning": "each person"
    },
    {
      "question": "辱め",
      "answer": "はずかしめ",
      "meaning": "shame, disgrace, raping, rape"
    },
    {
      "question": "高原",
      "answer": "こうげん",
      "meaning": "tableland, plateau"
    },
    {
      "question": "秒針",
      "answer": "びょうしん",
      "meaning": "second hand (of clock)"
    },
    {
      "question": "枠組み",
      "answer": "わくぐみ",
      "meaning": "frame, framework, outline"
    },
    {
      "question": "割引",
      "answer": "わりびき",
      "meaning": "discount, reduction, rebate, tenths discounted, tenths reduced"
    },
    {
      "question": "先制",
      "answer": "せんせい",
      "meaning": "head start, initiative, preemption"
    },
    {
      "question": "轍",
      "answer": "わだち,てつ",
      "meaning": "rut, wheel track, furrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "翳り",
      "answer": "かげり",
      "meaning": "shadow or cloud (e.g. on someone's happiness), shade, gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "夢見心地",
      "answer": "ゆめみごこち",
      "meaning": "dreamy state of mind"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲酒",
      "answer": "いんしゅ,おんじゅ,おんしゅ",
      "meaning": "drinking alcohol (sake), consumption of alcohol (as prohibited by one of the Buddhist precepts), Bud"
    },
    {
      "question": "再発",
      "answer": "さいはつ",
      "meaning": "return, relapse, recurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "推進力",
      "answer": "すいしんりょく",
      "meaning": "propulsive power, driving force"
    },
    {
      "question": "碌に",
      "answer": "ろくに",
      "meaning": "(not) well, (not) enough, (im)properly, (in)sufficiently, (un)satisfactorily"
    },
    {
      "question": "門出",
      "answer": "かどで",
      "meaning": "leaving one's own house (e.g. when going to war), departure, setting out, starting a new life, start"
    },
    {
      "question": "胆力",
      "answer": "たんりょく",
      "meaning": "courage, nerve, grit"
    },
    {
      "question": "投げ返す",
      "answer": "なげかえす",
      "meaning": "to throw back"
    },
    {
      "question": "淀み",
      "answer": "よどみ",
      "meaning": "stagnation, deposit, sediment, backwater, faltering, hesitation, pause"
    },
    {
      "question": "弥生",
      "answer": "やよい,いやおい",
      "meaning": "third month of the lunar calendar, Yayoi period (ca. 300 BCE-300 CE), Yayoi culture, thick growth (o"
    },
    {
      "question": "刀剣",
      "answer": "とうけん",
      "meaning": "sword, dagger, knife, bayonet"
    },
    {
      "question": "辻褄",
      "answer": "つじつま",
      "meaning": "coherence, consistency"
    },
    {
      "question": "乳白色",
      "answer": "にゅうはくしょく",
      "meaning": "milk-white, milky"
    },
    {
      "question": "心証",
      "answer": "しんしょう",
      "meaning": "impression, strong belief, conviction"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り立つ",
      "answer": "きりたつ",
      "meaning": "to rise perpendicularly, to tower steeply"
    },
    {
      "question": "酩酊",
      "answer": "めいてい",
      "meaning": "drunkenness, intoxication"
    },
    {
      "question": "腹を括る",
      "answer": "はらをくくる",
      "meaning": "to prepare oneself for the worst, to strengthen one's resolve, to accept one's fate, to prepare ones"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇士",
      "answer": "ゆうし",
      "meaning": "brave warrior, hero, brave man"
    },
    {
      "question": "岩陰",
      "answer": "いわかげ",
      "meaning": "shade of a rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "通例",
      "answer": "つうれい",
      "meaning": "custom, general rule, convention, usually, generally, as a rule"
    },
    {
      "question": "加",
      "answer": "か",
      "meaning": "addition, increase, Canada"
    },
    {
      "question": "中型",
      "answer": "ちゅうがた",
      "meaning": "medium size"
    },
    {
      "question": "炊事",
      "answer": "すいじ",
      "meaning": "cooking, kitchen work"
    },
    {
      "question": "淡白",
      "answer": "たんぱく",
      "meaning": "light (color, colour, taste), simple, plain, frank, candid, ingenuous, indifferent"
    },
    {
      "question": "組み立て",
      "answer": "くみたて",
      "meaning": "construction, framework, erection, assembly, organization, organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "薙ぎ倒す",
      "answer": "なぎたおす",
      "meaning": "to mow down, to cut down, to knock down, to defeat, to beat"
    },
    {
      "question": "澄み切る",
      "answer": "すみきる",
      "meaning": "to be perfectly clear (water, air, etc.), to clear up"
    },
    {
      "question": "現れ",
      "answer": "あらわれ",
      "meaning": "embodiment, manifestation, materialization, materialisation, expression, indication"
    },
    {
      "question": "就活",
      "answer": "しゅうかつ",
      "meaning": "job hunting, job searching"
    },
    {
      "question": "寒空",
      "answer": "さむぞら",
      "meaning": "wintry sky, cold weather (in winter), wintry weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "風変わり",
      "answer": "ふうがわり",
      "meaning": "strange, eccentric"
    },
    {
      "question": "混血",
      "answer": "こんけつ",
      "meaning": "mixed race, mixed parentage"
    },
    {
      "question": "声帯",
      "answer": "せいたい",
      "meaning": "vocal cords"
    },
    {
      "question": "佳境",
      "answer": "かきょう",
      "meaning": "most interesting part (of a story), climax, good part, scenic spot, beautiful place"
    },
    {
      "question": "細切れ",
      "answer": "こまぎれ",
      "meaning": "small pieces, fragments, chopped meat, scraps (of beef, pork, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "好調",
      "answer": "こうちょう",
      "meaning": "favourable, favorable, promising, satisfactory, in good shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "専務",
      "answer": "せんむ",
      "meaning": "special duty, being in sole charge of a duty, senior managing director, executive director"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝剣",
      "answer": "ほうけん",
      "meaning": "treasured sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "聖戦",
      "answer": "せいせん",
      "meaning": "holy war, crusade"
    },
    {
      "question": "汎用",
      "answer": "はんよう",
      "meaning": "generic, general purpose, all-purpose"
    },
    {
      "question": "僻地",
      "answer": "へきち",
      "meaning": "remote place, backcountry, the sticks, hinterland"
    },
    {
      "question": "一枚岩",
      "answer": "いちまいいわ",
      "meaning": "monolith, large slab of rock"
    },
    {
      "question": "客足",
      "answer": "きゃくあし",
      "meaning": "customer traffic, customers, custom"
    },
    {
      "question": "純朴",
      "answer": "じゅんぼく",
      "meaning": "rustic simplicity, homeliness, unsophisticated, naive, honest, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "新入",
      "answer": "しんにゅう",
      "meaning": "newly arrived, newly joined, newly entered, newcomer"
    },
    {
      "question": "長寿",
      "answer": "ちょうじゅ",
      "meaning": "long life, longevity"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち聞き",
      "answer": "たちぎき",
      "meaning": "eavesdropping"
    },
    {
      "question": "延命",
      "answer": "えんめい,えんみょう",
      "meaning": "keeping alive longer, prolonging life, life extension, life-support"
    },
    {
      "question": "装丁",
      "answer": "そうてい",
      "meaning": "binding (of a book), design (of a book cover)"
    },
    {
      "question": "何卒",
      "answer": "なにとぞ,なにそつ",
      "meaning": "please, kindly, I beg of you, if it pleases you, by all means, without fail"
    },
    {
      "question": "男心",
      "answer": "おとこごころ",
      "meaning": "male instincts, male frivolity"
    },
    {
      "question": "衛生",
      "answer": "えいせい",
      "meaning": "hygiene, sanitation, health"
    },
    {
      "question": "百貨店",
      "answer": "ひゃっかてん",
      "meaning": "(department) store, (department) stores"
    },
    {
      "question": "艶かしい",
      "answer": "なまめかしい",
      "meaning": "charming, captivating, bewitching, seductive, coquettish"
    },
    {
      "question": "表情筋",
      "answer": "ひょうじょうきん",
      "meaning": "mimetic muscles"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人息子",
      "answer": "ひとりむすこ",
      "meaning": "only son"
    },
    {
      "question": "堕天使",
      "answer": "だてんし",
      "meaning": "fallen angel, Lucifer, demon, Satan"
    },
    {
      "question": "予報",
      "answer": "よほう",
      "meaning": "forecast, prediction"
    },
    {
      "question": "進呈",
      "answer": "しんてい",
      "meaning": "presentation (e.g. of a gift)"
    },
    {
      "question": "衰え",
      "answer": "おとろえ",
      "meaning": "weakening, emaciation, decline"
    },
    {
      "question": "帽",
      "answer": "ぼう",
      "meaning": "hat, cap"
    },
    {
      "question": "止す",
      "answer": "よす,さす",
      "meaning": "to cease, to desist, to cut it out, to lay off (an activity), to drop (a subject) to abolish, to res"
    },
    {
      "question": "農作物",
      "answer": "のうさくぶつ,のうさくもつ",
      "meaning": "crops, agricultural produce"
    },
    {
      "question": "将兵",
      "answer": "しょうへい",
      "meaning": "officers and men"
    },
    {
      "question": "西暦",
      "answer": "せいれき",
      "meaning": "Common Era, CE, Christian Era, anno domini, AD, Western (Gregorian) calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "罰金",
      "answer": "ばっきん",
      "meaning": "fine, penalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "見遣る",
      "answer": "みやる",
      "meaning": "to look at, to gaze, to stare at"
    },
    {
      "question": "助長",
      "answer": "じょちょう",
      "meaning": "promotion, encouragement, fostering, furtherance, unwanted help (usu. unintentionally harmful), unne"
    },
    {
      "question": "勇猛",
      "answer": "ゆうもう,ゆうみょう",
      "meaning": "daring, brave, bold, valiant, intrepid, dauntless"
    },
    {
      "question": "出鱈目",
      "answer": "でたらめ",
      "meaning": "nonsense, irresponsible remark, codswallop, hogwash, rubbish, random, haphazard, unsystematic"
    },
    {
      "question": "裁量",
      "answer": "さいりょう",
      "meaning": "discretion, judgement"
    },
    {
      "question": "庭先",
      "answer": "にわさき",
      "meaning": "part of the garden close to the house, nearby garden"
    },
    {
      "question": "気疲れ",
      "answer": "きづかれ",
      "meaning": "mental fatigue, worry, boredom"
    },
    {
      "question": "堪忍",
      "answer": "かんにん",
      "meaning": "patience, patient endurance, forbearance, tolerance, forgiveness, pardon"
    },
    {
      "question": "五分五分",
      "answer": "ごぶごぶ",
      "meaning": "as likely as not, 50-50, even match, tie"
    },
    {
      "question": "十一月",
      "answer": "じゅういちがつ",
      "meaning": "November, eleventh month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "隠し子",
      "answer": "かくしご",
      "meaning": "illegitimate child"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩知らず",
      "answer": "おんしらず",
      "meaning": "ungrateful"
    },
    {
      "question": "技巧",
      "answer": "ぎこう",
      "meaning": "technique, finesse"
    },
    {
      "question": "水源",
      "answer": "すいげん",
      "meaning": "source of river, fountainhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "癇に障る",
      "answer": "かんにさわる",
      "meaning": "to irritate one, to get on one's nerves"
    },
    {
      "question": "労る",
      "answer": "いたわる",
      "meaning": "to pity, to sympathize with, to sympathise with, to treat with sympathy, to console, to be kind to,"
    },
    {
      "question": "推理小説",
      "answer": "すいりしょうせつ",
      "meaning": "mystery novel, detective novel, whodunit"
    },
    {
      "question": "神剣",
      "answer": "しんけん",
      "meaning": "divine sword (one of the three sacred treasures)"
    },
    {
      "question": "底冷え",
      "answer": "そこびえ",
      "meaning": "penetrating cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "混在",
      "answer": "こんざい",
      "meaning": "existing alongside (each other), mixture, intermingling"
    },
    {
      "question": "激烈",
      "answer": "げきれつ",
      "meaning": "violence, vehemence, fury, fervour, fervor, severity, fierceness, keenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "心に残る",
      "answer": "こころにのこる",
      "meaning": "to stay in one's heart, to be enduringly memorable, to be unforgettable"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣舞",
      "answer": "けんぶ",
      "meaning": "sword dance"
    },
    {
      "question": "声明",
      "answer": "せいめい,しょうみょう",
      "meaning": "declaration, statement, proclamation, sabdavidya (ancient Indian linguistic and grammatical studies)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合点",
      "answer": "がてん,がってん",
      "meaning": "consent, assent, understanding, agreement, comprehension, grasp"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪路",
      "answer": "あくろ",
      "meaning": "bad road"
    },
    {
      "question": "水鉄砲",
      "answer": "みずでっぽう",
      "meaning": "water pistol, squirt gun, water gun"
    },
    {
      "question": "移転",
      "answer": "いてん",
      "meaning": "moving, relocation, change of address, transfer (of deeds, property, etc.), demise"
    },
    {
      "question": "音沙汰",
      "answer": "おとさた",
      "meaning": "news (from someone), word, contact"
    },
    {
      "question": "カツ丼",
      "answer": "カツどん",
      "meaning": "katsudon, pork cutlet served on top of a bowl of rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃部",
      "answer": "はいぶ",
      "meaning": "club disbandment"
    },
    {
      "question": "頁",
      "answer": "ページ,おおがい",
      "meaning": "page, kanji 'big shell' radical"
    },
    {
      "question": "守り神",
      "answer": "まもりがみ",
      "meaning": "guardian deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "民主主義",
      "answer": "みんしゅしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "democracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "全速",
      "answer": "ぜんそく",
      "meaning": "full speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "思慮",
      "answer": "しりょ",
      "meaning": "prudence, discretion, thought"
    },
    {
      "question": "円環",
      "answer": "えんかん",
      "meaning": "circle, ring, torus"
    },
    {
      "question": "沈没",
      "answer": "ちんぼつ",
      "meaning": "sinking, foundering, going down, submersion, getting dead drunk, having too much fun (esp. in a red-"
    },
    {
      "question": "未経験",
      "answer": "みけいけん",
      "meaning": "inexperienced"
    },
    {
      "question": "生物学",
      "answer": "せいぶつがく",
      "meaning": "biology"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然現象",
      "answer": "しぜんげんしょう",
      "meaning": "natural phenomenon (phenomena)"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫電",
      "answer": "しでん",
      "meaning": "purple lightning, flash, swordflash"
    },
    {
      "question": "東屋",
      "answer": "あずまや",
      "meaning": "arbor, arbour, bower, summer house, square gazebo"
    },
    {
      "question": "転勤",
      "answer": "てんきん",
      "meaning": "job transfer, job relocation, intra-company transfer"
    },
    {
      "question": "地の利",
      "answer": "ちのり",
      "meaning": "locational advantage, advantageous position"
    },
    {
      "question": "子羊",
      "answer": "こひつじ",
      "meaning": "lamb"
    },
    {
      "question": "生み",
      "answer": "うみ",
      "meaning": "production, bringing into the world, (physical) birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "失策",
      "answer": "しっさく",
      "meaning": "blunder, slip, error"
    },
    {
      "question": "解れる",
      "answer": "ほぐれる,ほつれる",
      "meaning": "to come untied, to come apart, to be softened, to be relaxed, to become frayed, to become loose"
    },
    {
      "question": "体表",
      "answer": "たいひょう",
      "meaning": "body surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "更地",
      "answer": "さらち",
      "meaning": "empty lot, vacant plot of land"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭け事",
      "answer": "かけごと",
      "meaning": "betting, gambling"
    },
    {
      "question": "能面",
      "answer": "のうめん",
      "meaning": "noh mask"
    },
    {
      "question": "折り紙",
      "answer": "おりがみ",
      "meaning": "origami, art of paper folding, hallmark, certificate of authenticity"
    },
    {
      "question": "私怨",
      "answer": "しえん",
      "meaning": "personal grudge, personal enmity"
    },
    {
      "question": "猊下",
      "answer": "げいか",
      "meaning": "your highness, your grace, your eminence"
    },
    {
      "question": "狼藉",
      "answer": "ろうぜき,ろうじゃく",
      "meaning": "disorder, confusion, violence, outrage, riot"
    },
    {
      "question": "機甲",
      "answer": "きこう",
      "meaning": "armour (e.g. tank), armor"
    },
    {
      "question": "土砂降り",
      "answer": "どしゃぶり",
      "meaning": "downpour, pouring rain, cloudburst, pelting rain, heavy rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "盟友",
      "answer": "めいゆう",
      "meaning": "sworn friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗船",
      "answer": "じょうせん",
      "meaning": "embarking (a ship), embarkation, boarding, ship (carrying someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤認",
      "answer": "ごにん",
      "meaning": "misrecognition, mistaking (x for y)"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉口",
      "answer": "へいこう",
      "meaning": "to be stumped, to be at a loss, to be at one's wits' end, to be nonplussed, to be fed up, to be tire"
    },
    {
      "question": "飲料",
      "answer": "いんりょう,のみりょう",
      "meaning": "beverage, drink, one's (portion of a) drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "先手必勝",
      "answer": "せんてひっしょう",
      "meaning": "victory goes to the one who makes the first move, being quick to take action leads to victory, the e"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄ら笑い",
      "answer": "うすらわらい",
      "meaning": "faint smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "触",
      "answer": "ふれ,そく",
      "meaning": "proclamation, official notice, touch, contact, tactile object, uncleanliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "伯父さん",
      "answer": "おじさん",
      "meaning": "uncle, old man, mister, manybar goatfish (Parupeneus multifasciatus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "定例",
      "answer": "ていれい,じょうれい",
      "meaning": "regular, ordinary (e.g. session of parliament), established usage, precedent, regular practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "無機物",
      "answer": "むきぶつ",
      "meaning": "inorganic substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘り",
      "answer": "ねばり",
      "meaning": "stickiness, viscosity, tenacity, persistence"
    },
    {
      "question": "濁り",
      "answer": "にごり",
      "meaning": "muddiness, murkiness, lack of clarity, impurity, Japanese voiced consonant mark, unrefined sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "羽目",
      "answer": "はめ",
      "meaning": "panel, wainscoting, wainscotting, plight, fix, bind, awkward situation, difficult situation, mess"
    },
    {
      "question": "少数精鋭",
      "answer": "しょうすうせいえい",
      "meaning": "elect (select) few"
    },
    {
      "question": "忠臣",
      "answer": "ちゅうしん",
      "meaning": "loyal retainer, loyal subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "調える",
      "answer": "ととのえる",
      "meaning": "to put in order, to arrange, to tidy up, to straighten, to adjust, to fix, to get ready, to prepare,"
    },
    {
      "question": "先行き",
      "answer": "さきゆき,さきいき",
      "meaning": "the future, future prospects"
    },
    {
      "question": "国産",
      "answer": "こくさん",
      "meaning": "domestic, domestically-produced, produced within a country"
    },
    {
      "question": "急襲",
      "answer": "きゅうしゅう",
      "meaning": "raid, assault, descent"
    },
    {
      "question": "風通し",
      "answer": "かぜとおし,かざとおし",
      "meaning": "ventilation, communication (within an organisation), openness"
    },
    {
      "question": "花粉",
      "answer": "かふん",
      "meaning": "pollen"
    },
    {
      "question": "周波数",
      "answer": "しゅうはすう",
      "meaning": "frequency (esp. of waveforms)"
    },
    {
      "question": "賃金",
      "answer": "ちんぎん,ちんきん",
      "meaning": "wages, pay, rental payment"
    },
    {
      "question": "放逐",
      "answer": "ほうちく",
      "meaning": "expulsion, ousting, ejection, dismissal, banishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜半",
      "answer": "やはん,よわ",
      "meaning": "midnight, dead of night"
    },
    {
      "question": "初歩",
      "answer": "しょほ",
      "meaning": "basics, rudiments, elements, ABCs of ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "切れ切れ",
      "answer": "きれぎれ",
      "meaning": "pieces, scraps, disconnected"
    },
    {
      "question": "群生",
      "answer": "ぐんせい,ぐんじょう",
      "meaning": "growing en masse in one location (of plants), living gregariously (of animals), living in flocks, he"
    },
    {
      "question": "詰所",
      "answer": "つめしょ",
      "meaning": "station, office, guardroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "女性的",
      "answer": "じょせいてき",
      "meaning": "feminine, effeminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "手打ち",
      "answer": "てうち",
      "meaning": "making noodles by hand, striking a deal, coming to an agreement, reconciliation, killing with bare h"
    },
    {
      "question": "株式会社",
      "answer": "かぶしきがいしゃ",
      "meaning": "public company, corporation, KK, formula for an incorporated public company"
    },
    {
      "question": "産地",
      "answer": "さんち",
      "meaning": "producing area"
    },
    {
      "question": "下賤",
      "answer": "げせん",
      "meaning": "low birth, humble origin, lowly, base, vulgar, coarse"
    },
    {
      "question": "何故に",
      "answer": "なぜに,なにゆえに",
      "meaning": "why, how"
    },
    {
      "question": "引越し",
      "answer": "ひっこし",
      "meaning": "moving (dwelling, office, etc.), changing residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "森羅万象",
      "answer": "しんらばんしょう",
      "meaning": "all things in nature, the whole creation"
    },
    {
      "question": "守秘義務",
      "answer": "しゅひぎむ",
      "meaning": "duty of confidentiality"
    },
    {
      "question": "子種",
      "answer": "こだね",
      "meaning": "child, offspring, issue, sperm, (one's) seed"
    },
    {
      "question": "細菌",
      "answer": "さいきん",
      "meaning": "bacterium, bacteria, germ"
    },
    {
      "question": "落第",
      "answer": "らくだい",
      "meaning": "failure (in an examination), failing to advance (to the next year), falling short of the standard, n"
    },
    {
      "question": "妻子",
      "answer": "さいし,つまこ,めこ",
      "meaning": "wife and children, wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "上京",
      "answer": "じょうきょう",
      "meaning": "proceeding to the capital (Tokyo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "昇天",
      "answer": "しょうてん",
      "meaning": "ascension (into heaven), the Ascension, death"
    },
    {
      "question": "根深い",
      "answer": "ねぶかい",
      "meaning": "deep-rooted, ingrained"
    },
    {
      "question": "芸能界",
      "answer": "げいのうかい",
      "meaning": "show business, entertainment industry, world of entertainment"
    },
    {
      "question": "睨み合い",
      "answer": "にらみあい",
      "meaning": "glaring at each other, confrontation, standoff, face-off"
    },
    {
      "question": "自意識",
      "answer": "じいしき",
      "meaning": "self-consciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "如月",
      "answer": "きさらぎ,じょげつ",
      "meaning": "second month of the lunar calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "全くする",
      "answer": "まったくする",
      "meaning": "to accomplish, to fulfill, to carry out"
    },
    {
      "question": "重複",
      "answer": "ちょうふく,じゅうふく",
      "meaning": "duplication, repetition, overlapping, redundancy, restoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "波立つ",
      "answer": "なみだつ",
      "meaning": "to be choppy (of waves), to be rough, to run high, to billow, to swell, to ripple, to wave (e.g. in"
    },
    {
      "question": "放射状",
      "answer": "ほうしゃじょう",
      "meaning": "radial, radiating"
    },
    {
      "question": "安置",
      "answer": "あんち",
      "meaning": "enshrinement, installation (of an image), safe area (in video games), safe zone, area where the play"
    },
    {
      "question": "熟考",
      "answer": "じゅっこう",
      "meaning": "careful consideration, deliberation, thinking over carefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "漬物",
      "answer": "つけもの",
      "meaning": "tsukemono, Japanese pickled vegetables"
    },
    {
      "question": "先達",
      "answer": "せんだつ,せんだち",
      "meaning": "leader, pioneer, precursor, senior figure, guide, leader (in Shugendō)"
    },
    {
      "question": "了",
      "answer": "りょう",
      "meaning": "finish, completion, the end, fact, truth, understanding, consideration"
    },
    {
      "question": "用を足す",
      "answer": "ようをたす",
      "meaning": "to take care of some business, to go on an errand, to relieve oneself, to do one's business, to go t"
    },
    {
      "question": "屁",
      "answer": "おなら,へ",
      "meaning": "wind, gas, fart, something worthless, something not worth considering"
    },
    {
      "question": "好敵手",
      "answer": "こうてきしゅ",
      "meaning": "worthy opponent, worthy rival, good match"
    },
    {
      "question": "合法",
      "answer": "ごうほう",
      "meaning": "legal, lawful, legitimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "体を壊す",
      "answer": "からだをこわす",
      "meaning": "to harm one's health"
    },
    {
      "question": "屋根裏",
      "answer": "やねうら",
      "meaning": "attic, loft"
    },
    {
      "question": "樫",
      "answer": "かし,かしい",
      "meaning": "evergreen oak"
    },
    {
      "question": "新興",
      "answer": "しんこう",
      "meaning": "rising, developing, emergent, burgeoning, new"
    },
    {
      "question": "物悲しい",
      "answer": "ものがなしい",
      "meaning": "sad, melancholy"
    },
    {
      "question": "惰性",
      "answer": "だせい",
      "meaning": "inertia, force of habit"
    },
    {
      "question": "布教",
      "answer": "ふきょう",
      "meaning": "propagation (e.g. a religion), proselytizing, missionary work"
    },
    {
      "question": "右端",
      "answer": "みぎはし,うたん",
      "meaning": "right end, right edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍重",
      "answer": "どんじゅう",
      "meaning": "thickheaded, slow-witted, phlegmatic, stolid, bovine, slow (of one's movements), sluggish"
    },
    {
      "question": "純血",
      "answer": "じゅんけつ",
      "meaning": "pure-bred (usu. animal), pure-blooded, thoroughbred"
    },
    {
      "question": "氏名",
      "answer": "しめい,うじな",
      "meaning": "(full) name, identity"
    },
    {
      "question": "過多",
      "answer": "かた",
      "meaning": "excess, surplus, superabundance"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち切り",
      "answer": "うちきり",
      "meaning": "end, close, finish, truncation, discontinuance, closure, cancellation, breaking off, aborting, end o"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち寄る",
      "answer": "もちよる",
      "meaning": "to gather (bringing something), to gather (to exchange something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "連隊",
      "answer": "れんたい",
      "meaning": "regiment"
    },
    {
      "question": "徴兵",
      "answer": "ちょうへい",
      "meaning": "conscription, recruitment, enlistment"
    },
    {
      "question": "上向き",
      "answer": "うわむき,うえむき",
      "meaning": "pointing up, pointing upward, upturn, uptrend, upward tendency"
    },
    {
      "question": "人語",
      "answer": "じんご",
      "meaning": "human speech"
    },
    {
      "question": "面構え",
      "answer": "つらがまえ",
      "meaning": "(facial) expression (esp. fierce, fearless, sinister, etc.), look"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐留",
      "answer": "ちゅうりゅう",
      "meaning": "stationing (e.g. of troops), garrison"
    },
    {
      "question": "大っきい",
      "answer": "おっきい",
      "meaning": "big, large, great"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯磨き",
      "answer": "はみがき",
      "meaning": "dental brushing, brushing one's teeth, dentifrice, toothpaste, tooth powder"
    },
    {
      "question": "第九",
      "answer": "だいく",
      "meaning": "the ninth, Beethoven's Ninth Symphony"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤ワイン",
      "answer": "あかワイン",
      "meaning": "red wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈み込む",
      "answer": "かがみこむ",
      "meaning": "to lean over, to lean in"
    },
    {
      "question": "配役",
      "answer": "はいやく",
      "meaning": "cast (of a play)"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻出",
      "answer": "ねんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "contriving (to raise funds, to find time, etc.), working out (a solution)"
    },
    {
      "question": "乗り継ぐ",
      "answer": "のりつぐ",
      "meaning": "to connect (with a different flight, train, etc.), to make a connection, to change (planes, trains,"
    },
    {
      "question": "看板娘",
      "answer": "かんばんむすめ",
      "meaning": "pretty girl who attracts customers to come inside a shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "脳波",
      "answer": "のうは",
      "meaning": "brain waves, electroencephalogram, EEG"
    },
    {
      "question": "手並み",
      "answer": "てなみ",
      "meaning": "skill"
    },
    {
      "question": "越",
      "answer": "えつ",
      "meaning": "Yue, kingdom in ancient China (6th C-334 BCE), Vietnam"
    },
    {
      "question": "暇人",
      "answer": "ひまじん",
      "meaning": "person with a lot of free time on their hands, person of leisure, idler, loafer"
    },
    {
      "question": "余所者",
      "answer": "よそもの",
      "meaning": "stranger, outsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "図形",
      "answer": "ずけい",
      "meaning": "figure, shape, graphic"
    },
    {
      "question": "性交",
      "answer": "せいこう",
      "meaning": "sexual intercourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "副産物",
      "answer": "ふくさんぶつ",
      "meaning": "by-product, spin-off, outgrowth, side effect, consequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "衝",
      "answer": "しょう",
      "meaning": "important point (e.g. on a route), important role (responsibility, etc.), opposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "三角関係",
      "answer": "さんかくかんけい",
      "meaning": "love triangle, eternal triangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "断崖",
      "answer": "だんがい",
      "meaning": "precipice, cliff, bluff"
    },
    {
      "question": "高速道路",
      "answer": "こうそくどうろ",
      "meaning": "highway, freeway, expressway, motorway"
    },
    {
      "question": "速まる",
      "answer": "はやまる",
      "meaning": "to quicken, to speed up, to gather speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "に於いて",
      "answer": "において",
      "meaning": "in, on, at (place), as for, regarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ正面",
      "answer": "まっしょうめん",
      "meaning": "directly opposite, right in front"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き渡し",
      "answer": "ひきわたし",
      "meaning": "delivery, handing over, turning over, extradition"
    },
    {
      "question": "人力",
      "answer": "じんりき,じんりょく",
      "meaning": "human power, human strength, human effort, human agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "籠絡",
      "answer": "ろうらく",
      "meaning": "inveigling, ensnaring, enticement, cajoling"
    },
    {
      "question": "前菜",
      "answer": "ぜんさい",
      "meaning": "hors d'oeuvre, appetizer, appetiser, starter"
    },
    {
      "question": "鎮火",
      "answer": "ちんか",
      "meaning": "extinguishing, dying out (of a fire), putting out"
    },
    {
      "question": "両翼",
      "answer": "りょうよく",
      "meaning": "both wings, both flanks"
    },
    {
      "question": "本館",
      "answer": "ほんかん",
      "meaning": "main building"
    },
    {
      "question": "疾駆",
      "answer": "しっく",
      "meaning": "riding fast, driving a horse fast"
    },
    {
      "question": "徒党",
      "answer": "ととう",
      "meaning": "conspirators, faction, cabal, clique"
    },
    {
      "question": "善戦",
      "answer": "ぜんせん",
      "meaning": "fighting a good fight, putting up a good fight, fighting bravely"
    },
    {
      "question": "幻惑",
      "answer": "げんわく",
      "meaning": "fascination, glamor, glamour, bewitching"
    },
    {
      "question": "教導",
      "answer": "きょうどう",
      "meaning": "instruction, teaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "癇癪",
      "answer": "かんしゃく",
      "meaning": "passion, temper, irritability"
    },
    {
      "question": "身が入る",
      "answer": "みがはいる",
      "meaning": "to give one's everything, to make one's best effort, to be enthused, to put your back into it"
    },
    {
      "question": "白虎",
      "answer": "びゃっこ,はっこ",
      "meaning": "White Tiger (god said to rule over the western heavens), seven mansions (Chinese constellations) of"
    },
    {
      "question": "粗雑",
      "answer": "そざつ",
      "meaning": "coarse, rough, crude"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆撫で",
      "answer": "さかなで,ぎゃくなで",
      "meaning": "rubbing the wrong way (e.g. a cat), irritating"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭目",
      "answer": "とうもく",
      "meaning": "chief, head, leader"
    },
    {
      "question": "賓客",
      "answer": "ひんきゃく,ひんかく",
      "meaning": "guest of honour, guest of honor, privileged guest, visitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "答案",
      "answer": "とうあん",
      "meaning": "examination paper, examination script, answer sheet, answer (to an exam question)"
    },
    {
      "question": "白亜",
      "answer": "はくあ",
      "meaning": "chalk (mineral), white wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "茫然自失",
      "answer": "ぼうぜんじしつ",
      "meaning": "stupor, stupefaction, trance, (being) dumbfounded"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き返す",
      "answer": "つきかえす",
      "meaning": "to deal a blow in return, to hit back, to punch back, to reject, to send back"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き身",
      "answer": "ぬきみ",
      "meaning": "naked sword, drawn sword, shellfish removed from the shell"
    },
    {
      "question": "提唱",
      "answer": "ていしょう",
      "meaning": "advocacy, proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒装束",
      "answer": "くろしょうぞく",
      "meaning": "black clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "無感動",
      "answer": "むかんどう",
      "meaning": "unimpressive, unimpressed"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭に来る",
      "answer": "あたまにくる",
      "meaning": "to get mad, to be highly offended, to get pissed off, to get angry, to lose one's cool"
    },
    {
      "question": "損得",
      "answer": "そんとく",
      "meaning": "loss and gain, advantage and disadvantage"
    },
    {
      "question": "体位",
      "answer": "たいい",
      "meaning": "physique, physical standard, posture, sexual position"
    },
    {
      "question": "交ざる",
      "answer": "まざる",
      "meaning": "to be mixed, to be blended with, to associate with, to mingle with, to join"
    },
    {
      "question": "談義",
      "answer": "だんぎ",
      "meaning": "discussion, discourse, lecture, sermon"
    },
    {
      "question": "並列",
      "answer": "へいれつ",
      "meaning": "arranging in a line, standing in a row, parallel (electronics, computing, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無法者",
      "answer": "むほうしゃ,むほうもの",
      "meaning": "outlaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "学部",
      "answer": "がくぶ",
      "meaning": "department of a university, undergraduate (course, program, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "図に乗る",
      "answer": "ずにのる",
      "meaning": "to get carried away, to become over-excited, to push one's luck, to push a good thing too far"
    },
    {
      "question": "先王",
      "answer": "せんおう,せんのう",
      "meaning": "the late king, the preceding king, good ancient kings"
    },
    {
      "question": "問い掛け",
      "answer": "といかけ",
      "meaning": "query, interrogation, enquiry, question, inquiry"
    },
    {
      "question": "均整",
      "answer": "きんせい",
      "meaning": "symmetry, balance, proportion, uniformity"
    },
    {
      "question": "病床",
      "answer": "びょうしょう",
      "meaning": "sickbed, (hospital) bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "精神年齢",
      "answer": "せいしんねんれい",
      "meaning": "mental age"
    },
    {
      "question": "紅玉",
      "answer": "こうぎょく",
      "meaning": "ruby, Jonathan apple"
    },
    {
      "question": "余生",
      "answer": "よせい",
      "meaning": "one's remaining years, the rest of one's life"
    },
    {
      "question": "再編",
      "answer": "さいへん",
      "meaning": "reorganization, reorganisation, reshuffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠅",
      "answer": "はえ",
      "meaning": "fly (any insect of infraorder Muscomorpha), person of no worth, pisher, scrub"
    },
    {
      "question": "高嶺の花",
      "answer": "たかねのはな",
      "meaning": "prize beyond one's reach, woman who is out of one's league, flower on a high peak"
    },
    {
      "question": "猟",
      "answer": "りょう",
      "meaning": "hunting, shooting, game, quarry"
    },
    {
      "question": "自軍",
      "answer": "じぐん",
      "meaning": "one's own army, one's own team"
    },
    {
      "question": "検知",
      "answer": "けんち",
      "meaning": "detection"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊感",
      "answer": "れいかん",
      "meaning": "inspiration, afflatus, ability to sense the supernatural (esp. ghosts, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "専任",
      "answer": "せんにん",
      "meaning": "full-time service"
    },
    {
      "question": "交替",
      "answer": "こうたい",
      "meaning": "alternation, change, relief, relay, shift, substitution (sports, etc.), taking turns"
    },
    {
      "question": "西日",
      "answer": "にしび,せいにち",
      "meaning": "westering sun, setting sun, Spanish-Japanese (gen. for translations and dictionaries)"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩場",
      "answer": "かりば",
      "meaning": "hunting ground, hunting preserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "落とし前",
      "answer": "おとしまえ",
      "meaning": "settlement for a dispute (esp. one caused by an affront or blunder), money paid to settle a dispute"
    },
    {
      "question": "側仕え",
      "answer": "そばづかえ",
      "meaning": "personal attendant, valet, maid"
    },
    {
      "question": "雷神",
      "answer": "らいじん",
      "meaning": "god of thunder"
    },
    {
      "question": "臓腑",
      "answer": "ぞうふ",
      "meaning": "entrails"
    },
    {
      "question": "新郎",
      "answer": "しんろう",
      "meaning": "bridegroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝杯",
      "answer": "しゅくはい",
      "meaning": "toast, congratulatory cup"
    },
    {
      "question": "記者会見",
      "answer": "きしゃかいけん",
      "meaning": "press conference"
    },
    {
      "question": "高飛車",
      "answer": "たかびしゃ",
      "meaning": "high-handed, domineering, on one's high horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "癒着",
      "answer": "ゆちゃく",
      "meaning": "adhesion, conglutination, collusion, collusive relationship"
    },
    {
      "question": "転覆",
      "answer": "てんぷく",
      "meaning": "overturning, capsizing, overthrow (e.g. of a government)"
    },
    {
      "question": "規則的",
      "answer": "きそくてき",
      "meaning": "systematic, regular, routine"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍色",
      "answer": "にびいろ",
      "meaning": "dark gray, dark grey"
    },
    {
      "question": "宙返り",
      "answer": "ちゅうがえり",
      "meaning": "somersault, looping-the-loop"
    },
    {
      "question": "濃縮",
      "answer": "のうしゅく",
      "meaning": "concentration (e.g. of a solution), enrichment, condensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "武勲",
      "answer": "ぶくん",
      "meaning": "deeds of arms"
    },
    {
      "question": "特待生",
      "answer": "とくたいせい",
      "meaning": "scholarship student"
    },
    {
      "question": "早業",
      "answer": "はやわざ",
      "meaning": "quick work, (clever) feat"
    },
    {
      "question": "信奉",
      "answer": "しんぽう",
      "meaning": "belief, faith, adherence, espousal"
    },
    {
      "question": "独房",
      "answer": "どくぼう",
      "meaning": "single cell, isolation cell, solitary cell, solitary confinement cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "三食",
      "answer": "さんしょく",
      "meaning": "three meals (a day)"
    },
    {
      "question": "製薬",
      "answer": "せいやく",
      "meaning": "medicine manufacture, drug manufacture"
    },
    {
      "question": "出奔",
      "answer": "しゅっぽん",
      "meaning": "flight, elopement, running away, absconding"
    },
    {
      "question": "地平",
      "answer": "ちへい",
      "meaning": "level ground, horizon, field of view"
    },
    {
      "question": "共謀",
      "answer": "きょうぼう",
      "meaning": "conspiracy, collusion, complicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "宇",
      "answer": "のき,う",
      "meaning": "eaves, narrow aisle surrounding the core of a temple building, counter for buildings, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "海風",
      "answer": "かいふう,うみかぜ",
      "meaning": "sea breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "模範的",
      "answer": "もはんてき",
      "meaning": "exemplary"
    },
    {
      "question": "電磁波",
      "answer": "でんじは",
      "meaning": "electromagnetic wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "混浴",
      "answer": "こんよく",
      "meaning": "mixed bathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "直下",
      "answer": "ちょっか",
      "meaning": "directly under, falling perpendicularly"
    },
    {
      "question": "惨事",
      "answer": "さんじ",
      "meaning": "disaster, tragedy, tragic incident, horrible accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "極大",
      "answer": "きょくだい",
      "meaning": "maximum, local maximum"
    },
    {
      "question": "小魚",
      "answer": "こざかな,いさな",
      "meaning": "small fish, fry"
    },
    {
      "question": "家格",
      "answer": "かかく",
      "meaning": "family status"
    },
    {
      "question": "教卓",
      "answer": "きょうたく",
      "meaning": "teacher's desk, teacher's lectern"
    },
    {
      "question": "送り主",
      "answer": "おくりぬし",
      "meaning": "sender, consignor, remitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "係長",
      "answer": "かかりちょう",
      "meaning": "subsection head, assistant manager, chief clerk"
    },
    {
      "question": "賢",
      "answer": "けん,かしこ",
      "meaning": "intelligence, genius, scholarship, virtue, yours sincerely, respectfully yours"
    },
    {
      "question": "囲い込む",
      "answer": "かこいこむ",
      "meaning": "to enclose, to impound, to cut off, to corral"
    },
    {
      "question": "物覚え",
      "answer": "ものおぼえ",
      "meaning": "memory, ability to learn"
    },
    {
      "question": "設える",
      "answer": "しつらえる",
      "meaning": "to provide, to arrange, to install"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋う",
      "answer": "こう",
      "meaning": "to love"
    },
    {
      "question": "葛",
      "answer": "くず,つづら,かずら",
      "meaning": "kudzu (Pueraria montana), Japanese arrowroot, Chinese moonseed (Sinomenium acutum), creeping plant,"
    },
    {
      "question": "農園",
      "answer": "のうえん",
      "meaning": "plantation"
    },
    {
      "question": "降格",
      "answer": "こうかく",
      "meaning": "demotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "重用",
      "answer": "じゅうよう,ちょうよう",
      "meaning": "appointing to a responsible post, making much of"
    },
    {
      "question": "偏り",
      "answer": "かたより",
      "meaning": "deviation, inclination, offset, bias, prejudice, polarization, polarisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "引っ付く",
      "answer": "ひっつく",
      "meaning": "to stick to, to cling to, to adhere to, to become intimate (of a man and woman), to get close, to ge"
    },
    {
      "question": "残り物",
      "answer": "のこりもの",
      "meaning": "leftovers (esp. food), remnants"
    },
    {
      "question": "富豪",
      "answer": "ふごう",
      "meaning": "wealthy person, millionaire"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏面",
      "answer": "りめん",
      "meaning": "back, reverse, other side, inside, tails (of coins), background"
    },
    {
      "question": "解毒剤",
      "answer": "げどくざい",
      "meaning": "antidote"
    },
    {
      "question": "情動",
      "answer": "じょうどう",
      "meaning": "emotion, affect"
    },
    {
      "question": "聴取",
      "answer": "ちょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "hearing (of a statement, opinion, explanation, etc.), asking, questioning (e.g. a suspect), enquiry,"
    },
    {
      "question": "昼時",
      "answer": "ひるどき",
      "meaning": "noon, lunch time"
    },
    {
      "question": "感応",
      "answer": "かんのう,かんおう",
      "meaning": "responsiveness, responding, sensitivity, sympathy, sympathizing, sympathising, divine response (e.g."
    },
    {
      "question": "滑走路",
      "answer": "かっそうろ",
      "meaning": "runway"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰宅部",
      "answer": "きたくぶ",
      "meaning": "pupils who are not members of any school club, go-home club"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂塵",
      "answer": "さじん",
      "meaning": "cloud of dust, sandstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "年収",
      "answer": "ねんしゅう",
      "meaning": "annual income"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪戦苦闘",
      "answer": "あくせんくとう",
      "meaning": "hard fighting, hard struggle, fighting against heavy odds"
    },
    {
      "question": "悲嘆",
      "answer": "ひたん",
      "meaning": "grief, sorrow, anguish, lamentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "為政者",
      "answer": "いせいしゃ",
      "meaning": "statesman, administrator, politician, policymaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "空元気",
      "answer": "からげんき",
      "meaning": "putting on a brave face, put-on cheeriness, pretending one is fine, show of courage, bravado, Dutch"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾頭",
      "answer": "だんとう",
      "meaning": "warhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "女体",
      "answer": "にょたい,じょたい",
      "meaning": "woman's body"
    },
    {
      "question": "等級",
      "answer": "とうきゅう",
      "meaning": "grade, class, degree, rank, rating, order, points, magnitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "魚雷",
      "answer": "ぎょらい",
      "meaning": "torpedo"
    },
    {
      "question": "激流",
      "answer": "げきりゅう",
      "meaning": "raging stream, rapids"
    },
    {
      "question": "巣くう",
      "answer": "すくう",
      "meaning": "to build (a nest), to nest, to haunt (a place), to hang out (somewhere)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下り坂",
      "answer": "くだりざか",
      "meaning": "downhill, downward slope, descent, decline, waning, ebb, (going) downhill"
    },
    {
      "question": "完売",
      "answer": "かんばい",
      "meaning": "selling out, being sold out"
    },
    {
      "question": "瞑目",
      "answer": "めいもく",
      "meaning": "closing one's eyes, passing away, dying peacefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "濡れ衣",
      "answer": "ぬれぎぬ",
      "meaning": "false accusations, unfounded suspicion, groundless charge, wet clothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "人間味",
      "answer": "にんげんみ",
      "meaning": "human kindness, human weakness"
    },
    {
      "question": "小間使い",
      "answer": "こまづかい",
      "meaning": "maid, handmaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち合い",
      "answer": "うちあい",
      "meaning": "exchange of blows, long rally"
    },
    {
      "question": "談",
      "answer": "だん",
      "meaning": "talk, story, conversation"
    },
    {
      "question": "御託",
      "answer": "ごたく",
      "meaning": "tedious talk, impertinent talk, repetitious talk, saucy speech, pretentious statement"
    },
    {
      "question": "交",
      "answer": "こもごも,こう",
      "meaning": "alternately, in succession, association, fellowship, change (of season, year, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り解く",
      "answer": "ふりほどく",
      "meaning": "to shake and untangle, to shake free from"
    },
    {
      "question": "面白半分",
      "answer": "おもしろはんぶん",
      "meaning": "for fun, half in jest"
    },
    {
      "question": "真白",
      "answer": "まっしろ,ましろ",
      "meaning": "pure white, blank (e.g. mind, paper)"
    },
    {
      "question": "湾曲",
      "answer": "わんきょく",
      "meaning": "curve, bend, crook"
    },
    {
      "question": "美容院",
      "answer": "びよういん",
      "meaning": "beauty parlour, beauty parlor, beauty salon, hairdressing salon"
    },
    {
      "question": "山小屋",
      "answer": "やまごや",
      "meaning": "hut (esp. on a mountain), shack, refuge, shanty"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り潰す",
      "answer": "とりつぶす",
      "meaning": "to disrupt, to ruin, to hinder, to thwart"
    },
    {
      "question": "作り置き",
      "answer": "つくりおき",
      "meaning": "pre-made (esp. food), prepared in advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "敷物",
      "answer": "しきもの",
      "meaning": "carpet, rug, matting, carpeting, mat, mattress, quilt etc. spread out on the floor (or ground) and u"
    },
    {
      "question": "本懐",
      "answer": "ほんかい",
      "meaning": "one's long-cherished desire"
    },
    {
      "question": "遵守",
      "answer": "じゅんしゅ",
      "meaning": "observance (of laws, rules, etc.), adherence, obeying, following, abiding by, compliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "強姦",
      "answer": "ごうかん",
      "meaning": "rape, sexual assault"
    },
    {
      "question": "脊髄",
      "answer": "せきずい",
      "meaning": "spinal cord"
    },
    {
      "question": "創立",
      "answer": "そうりつ",
      "meaning": "establishment, founding, organization, organisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠らす",
      "answer": "ねむらす",
      "meaning": "to put to sleep, to kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "学級",
      "answer": "がっきゅう",
      "meaning": "(school) class"
    },
    {
      "question": "睾丸",
      "answer": "こうがん",
      "meaning": "testicles, testes, balls"
    },
    {
      "question": "還す",
      "answer": "かえす",
      "meaning": "to send (someone) back, to send (someone) home"
    },
    {
      "question": "直通",
      "answer": "ちょくつう",
      "meaning": "direct line, direct communication, connecting directly, through service, nonstop service"
    },
    {
      "question": "行く先々",
      "answer": "ゆくさきざき,いくさきざき",
      "meaning": "everywhere, everywhere one goes, wherever one goes"
    },
    {
      "question": "包み紙",
      "answer": "つつみがみ",
      "meaning": "wrapping paper"
    },
    {
      "question": "始業",
      "answer": "しぎょう",
      "meaning": "start of work, commencement, opening"
    },
    {
      "question": "切磋琢磨",
      "answer": "せっさたくま",
      "meaning": "diligent application (to work or study), cultivating one's character by studying hard, mutual encour"
    },
    {
      "question": "義理堅い",
      "answer": "ぎりがたい",
      "meaning": "possessed of a strong sense of duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "神隠し",
      "answer": "かみかくし,かみがくし",
      "meaning": "mysterious disappearance, being spirited away"
    },
    {
      "question": "臀部",
      "answer": "でんぶ",
      "meaning": "buttocks, gluteal, rear"
    },
    {
      "question": "選考",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "selection, screening"
    },
    {
      "question": "引用",
      "answer": "いんよう",
      "meaning": "quotation, citation, reference"
    },
    {
      "question": "古本屋",
      "answer": "ふるほんや",
      "meaning": "secondhand bookshop, secondhand bookstore, secondhand bookseller"
    },
    {
      "question": "吊り橋",
      "answer": "つりばし,つりはし",
      "meaning": "suspension bridge, rope bridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "第六感",
      "answer": "だいろっかん",
      "meaning": "the sixth sense, intuition, hunch"
    },
    {
      "question": "流体",
      "answer": "りゅうたい",
      "meaning": "fluid"
    },
    {
      "question": "仔犬",
      "answer": "こいぬ",
      "meaning": "puppy, small dog"
    },
    {
      "question": "低級",
      "answer": "ていきゅう",
      "meaning": "low grade, vulgar, low class, cheap, low level"
    },
    {
      "question": "液晶",
      "answer": "えきしょう",
      "meaning": "liquid crystal"
    },
    {
      "question": "チラ見",
      "answer": "チラみ",
      "meaning": "glancing look"
    },
    {
      "question": "割増し",
      "answer": "わりまし",
      "meaning": "extra (charge, fare, etc.), premium, bonus, (after a number) tenths increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "亜麻色",
      "answer": "あまいろ",
      "meaning": "flax color, flax colour, beige, ecru"
    },
    {
      "question": "清涼",
      "answer": "せいりょう",
      "meaning": "cool, refreshing"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ只中",
      "answer": "まっただなか",
      "meaning": "right in the midst of, right at the height of"
    },
    {
      "question": "柚子",
      "answer": "ゆず",
      "meaning": "yuzu (Citrus ichangensis x C. reticulata)"
    },
    {
      "question": "気流",
      "answer": "きりゅう",
      "meaning": "atmospheric current, air current, airflow"
    },
    {
      "question": "品位",
      "answer": "ひんい",
      "meaning": "dignity, grace, nobility, grade, quality, fineness, carat, karat"
    },
    {
      "question": "便器",
      "answer": "べんき",
      "meaning": "toilet bowl, urinal, chamber pot, bedpan"
    },
    {
      "question": "机上",
      "answer": "きじょう",
      "meaning": "on the desk, theoretical, academic, armchair (e.g. plan), desktop, paper, not yet implemented"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れ残る",
      "answer": "うれのこる",
      "meaning": "to remain unsold, to be left on the shelf"
    },
    {
      "question": "親身",
      "answer": "しんみ",
      "meaning": "relation, relative, kind, cordial"
    },
    {
      "question": "石炭",
      "answer": "せきたん,いしずみ",
      "meaning": "coal"
    },
    {
      "question": "正統派",
      "answer": "せいとうは",
      "meaning": "orthodox school"
    },
    {
      "question": "血反吐",
      "answer": "ちへど",
      "meaning": "bloody vomit"
    },
    {
      "question": "本校",
      "answer": "ほんこう",
      "meaning": "main school, principal school, this school, our school"
    },
    {
      "question": "登城",
      "answer": "とじょう",
      "meaning": "attendance at a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "台頭",
      "answer": "たいとう",
      "meaning": "rise (e.g. of a movement), emergence, rearing one's head, gaining prominence, coming to the fore, ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "直近",
      "answer": "ちょっきん",
      "meaning": "latest, most recent, nearest (in time)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶縁",
      "answer": "ぜつえん",
      "meaning": "breaking off relations, disconnection, insulation (esp. electrical), isolation"
    },
    {
      "question": "傾倒",
      "answer": "けいとう",
      "meaning": "devoting oneself to, concentrating on, being an ardent admirer of, having great esteem for, tipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "五度",
      "answer": "ごど",
      "meaning": "fifth (interval)"
    },
    {
      "question": "後付け",
      "answer": "あとづけ",
      "meaning": "appendix, postscript, back matter, retrofit, post-installation, custom installation, giving a reason"
    },
    {
      "question": "手甲",
      "answer": "てっこう,てこう",
      "meaning": "covering for the back of the hand and wrist"
    },
    {
      "question": "今期",
      "answer": "こんき",
      "meaning": "the present term"
    },
    {
      "question": "血塗る",
      "answer": "ちぬる",
      "meaning": "to smear with blood, to kill"
    },
    {
      "question": "心情的",
      "answer": "しんじょうてき",
      "meaning": "sentimental, on an emotional level, in one's heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "園芸",
      "answer": "えんげい",
      "meaning": "horticulture, gardening"
    },
    {
      "question": "色を失う",
      "answer": "いろをうしなう",
      "meaning": "to turn pale, to lose color, to lose colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "白刃",
      "answer": "はくじん,しらは",
      "meaning": "drawn sword, naked sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "被験者",
      "answer": "ひけんしゃ",
      "meaning": "subject (of a medical experiment, etc.), test subject, trial subject, testee, examinee (of a full-bo"
    },
    {
      "question": "虚像",
      "answer": "きょぞう",
      "meaning": "virtual image, false image, pretense, pretence"
    },
    {
      "question": "装甲車",
      "answer": "そうこうしゃ",
      "meaning": "armoured vehicle, armored vehicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "入会",
      "answer": "にゅうかい,いりあい",
      "meaning": "admission, joining, enrollment, enrolment, common (e.g. fishery or hunting ground), commonage"
    },
    {
      "question": "終息",
      "answer": "しゅうそく",
      "meaning": "having ended, being resolved"
    },
    {
      "question": "破談",
      "answer": "はだん",
      "meaning": "breaking off (an engagement, negotiations, etc.), cancellation"
    },
    {
      "question": "頼みの綱",
      "answer": "たのみのつな",
      "meaning": "last ray of hope"
    },
    {
      "question": "直談判",
      "answer": "じかだんぱん,じきだんぱん",
      "meaning": "direct talks, direct negotiations, talking to somebody in person"
    },
    {
      "question": "世紀末",
      "answer": "せいきまつ",
      "meaning": "end of a century (esp. 19th), fin-de-siècle"
    },
    {
      "question": "世話焼き",
      "answer": "せわやき",
      "meaning": "helpful person, person who likes looking after others, overly helpful person, annoyingly helpful per"
    },
    {
      "question": "鱗粉",
      "answer": "りんぷん",
      "meaning": "(insectile, especially moth) scales"
    },
    {
      "question": "二世",
      "answer": "にせい,にせ",
      "meaning": "nisei, second-generation Japanese (or Korean, etc.), foreigner of Japanese parentage, the Second (ki"
    },
    {
      "question": "思い付き",
      "answer": "おもいつき",
      "meaning": "plan, idea, suggestion"
    },
    {
      "question": "道順",
      "answer": "みちじゅん",
      "meaning": "route, way, course, directions"
    },
    {
      "question": "屈める",
      "answer": "かがめる,こごめる",
      "meaning": "to stoop, to bend (e.g. one's knees)"
    },
    {
      "question": "練り歩く",
      "answer": "ねりあるく",
      "meaning": "to parade, to march, to walk in procession"
    },
    {
      "question": "跨がる",
      "answer": "またがる",
      "meaning": "to straddle, to sit astride, to mount, to extend over, to spread over, to span, to extend into"
    },
    {
      "question": "因果応報",
      "answer": "いんがおうほう",
      "meaning": "retribution, retributive justice, karma, just deserts, poetic justice, reward and punishment for one"
    },
    {
      "question": "伏し目",
      "answer": "ふしめ",
      "meaning": "downcast look"
    },
    {
      "question": "新兵",
      "answer": "しんぺい",
      "meaning": "new recruit, conscript"
    },
    {
      "question": "自粛",
      "answer": "じしゅく",
      "meaning": "self-restraint, voluntary restraint, self-imposed control, self-discipline"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍵盤",
      "answer": "けんばん",
      "meaning": "keyboard (piano, computer, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "操縦席",
      "answer": "そうじゅうせき",
      "meaning": "(pilot or driver's) seat, cockpit"
    },
    {
      "question": "厄介者",
      "answer": "やっかいもの",
      "meaning": "burden, nuisance, bother, troublemaker, hanger-on, dependent, parasite"
    },
    {
      "question": "我慢強い",
      "answer": "がまんづよい",
      "meaning": "(very) patient, persevering"
    },
    {
      "question": "憑き物",
      "answer": "つきもの",
      "meaning": "evil spirit, demon"
    },
    {
      "question": "長靴",
      "answer": "ながぐつ,ちょうか",
      "meaning": "leather boots, rubber boots, wellingtons, wellies, long boots, high boots"
    },
    {
      "question": "道化師",
      "answer": "どうけし",
      "meaning": "clown"
    },
    {
      "question": "領収書",
      "answer": "りょうしゅうしょ",
      "meaning": "simplified receipt with a blank line to be filled out with the customer's name (used specifically fo"
    },
    {
      "question": "弾圧",
      "answer": "だんあつ",
      "meaning": "oppression, suppression, pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "会心",
      "answer": "かいしん",
      "meaning": "congeniality, satisfaction, gratification"
    },
    {
      "question": "利己的",
      "answer": "りこてき",
      "meaning": "selfish, egoistic, self-serving, self-interested"
    },
    {
      "question": "車掌",
      "answer": "しゃしょう",
      "meaning": "(train) conductor"
    },
    {
      "question": "生肉",
      "answer": "せいにく,なまにく",
      "meaning": "raw meat, fresh meat"
    },
    {
      "question": "粉雪",
      "answer": "こなゆき,こゆき",
      "meaning": "powder snow, powdery snow"
    },
    {
      "question": "空気感",
      "answer": "くうきかん",
      "meaning": "atmosphere (esp. of a place or person), mood, vibe, ambience"
    },
    {
      "question": "起死回生",
      "answer": "きしかいせい",
      "meaning": "revival from the brink of death, recovering from a hopeless situation, resuscitation, revitalization"
    },
    {
      "question": "浅瀬",
      "answer": "あさせ",
      "meaning": "shoal, shallows, sand bar, ford"
    },
    {
      "question": "軟化",
      "answer": "なんか",
      "meaning": "softening, softening (of attitude), mollification, weakening (of the market), blanching (e.g. of veg"
    },
    {
      "question": "横抱き",
      "answer": "よこだき",
      "meaning": "carrying (child) under arm"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔女狩り",
      "answer": "まじょがり",
      "meaning": "witch hunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "卓球",
      "answer": "たっきゅう",
      "meaning": "table tennis, ping-pong"
    },
    {
      "question": "神威",
      "answer": "しんい",
      "meaning": "god's majesty, god's authority, might of Heaven"
    },
    {
      "question": "外殻",
      "answer": "がいかく",
      "meaning": "shell, crust"
    },
    {
      "question": "揶揄う",
      "answer": "からかう",
      "meaning": "to ridicule, to tease, to mock, to chaff, to razz, to banter with, to make fun of, to poke fun at, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱射",
      "answer": "らんしゃ",
      "meaning": "indiscriminate shooting, random shooting, firing blindly"
    },
    {
      "question": "主賓",
      "answer": "しゅひん",
      "meaning": "main guest, guest of honor, guest of honour"
    },
    {
      "question": "銘",
      "answer": "めい",
      "meaning": "inscription, epitaph, (manufacturer's) engraved signature, motto, maxim, precept"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤外線",
      "answer": "せきがいせん",
      "meaning": "infrared rays, infrared radiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "自作自演",
      "answer": "じさくじえん",
      "meaning": "performing a part in one's own play, playing a musical piece that one has written, doing everything"
    },
    {
      "question": "間接",
      "answer": "かんせつ",
      "meaning": "indirection, indirectness"
    },
    {
      "question": "女学生",
      "answer": "じょがくせい",
      "meaning": "schoolgirl, female student"
    },
    {
      "question": "田んぼ",
      "answer": "たんぼ",
      "meaning": "paddy field, farm"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱却",
      "answer": "だっきゃく",
      "meaning": "ridding oneself, freeing oneself of, growing out of, overcoming, outgrowing"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆発物",
      "answer": "ばくはつぶつ",
      "meaning": "explosive (material)"
    },
    {
      "question": "皇后",
      "answer": "こうごう",
      "meaning": "(Japanese) empress, queen"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔓延る",
      "answer": "はびこる",
      "meaning": "to become overgrown, to grow thick, to spread, to run rampant, to thrive, to prevail, to become powe"
    },
    {
      "question": "現行犯",
      "answer": "げんこうはん",
      "meaning": "flagrante delicto, caught red-handed"
    },
    {
      "question": "一物",
      "answer": "いちもつ,いちぶつ",
      "meaning": "plot, ulterior motive, secret intention, thing, article, penis"
    },
    {
      "question": "経験則",
      "answer": "けいけんそく",
      "meaning": "rule of thumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "奨学金",
      "answer": "しょうがくきん",
      "meaning": "scholarship, stipend, bursary, student loan"
    },
    {
      "question": "習い事",
      "answer": "ならいごと",
      "meaning": "accomplishment, lessons (in an art, skill, etc.), practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "底抜け",
      "answer": "そこぬけ",
      "meaning": "bottomless (bucket, etc.), unbounded (good nature, optimism, etc.), boundless, extreme, uninhibited,"
    },
    {
      "question": "豪胆",
      "answer": "ごうたん",
      "meaning": "boldness, hardihood, courage, valour, valor"
    },
    {
      "question": "文系",
      "answer": "ぶんけい",
      "meaning": "humanities, social sciences, and fine arts, liberal arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "泣く泣く",
      "answer": "なくなく",
      "meaning": "tearfully, with (in) tears, weeping, crying"
    },
    {
      "question": "士官学校",
      "answer": "しかんがっこう",
      "meaning": "military academy"
    },
    {
      "question": "師弟",
      "answer": "してい",
      "meaning": "teacher and student"
    },
    {
      "question": "拒絶反応",
      "answer": "きょぜつはんのう",
      "meaning": "(organ) rejection, unthinking dismissal, strong reaction (against)"
    },
    {
      "question": "値切る",
      "answer": "ねぎる",
      "meaning": "to drive a bargain, to beat down the price, to haggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "使い古す",
      "answer": "つかいふるす",
      "meaning": "to wear out (something)"
    },
    {
      "question": "故意",
      "answer": "こい",
      "meaning": "intent, intention, bad faith, mens rea (guilty mind)"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶対零度",
      "answer": "ぜったいれいど",
      "meaning": "absolute zero"
    },
    {
      "question": "精算",
      "answer": "せいさん",
      "meaning": "exact calculation, squaring of accounts, adjustment"
    },
    {
      "question": "値札",
      "answer": "ねふだ",
      "meaning": "price tag, price label"
    },
    {
      "question": "真っ昼間",
      "answer": "まっぴるま",
      "meaning": "broad daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "散布",
      "answer": "さんぷ",
      "meaning": "dissemination, scattering, sprinkling, spraying"
    },
    {
      "question": "奈落の底",
      "answer": "ならくのそこ",
      "meaning": "depths of Hell, abyss, inescapable situation"
    },
    {
      "question": "曇天",
      "answer": "どんてん",
      "meaning": "cloudy sky, overcast sky, cloudy weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "珍獣",
      "answer": "ちんじゅう",
      "meaning": "rare (or peculiar) animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "新緑",
      "answer": "しんりょく",
      "meaning": "fresh verdure, new green leaves"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝過ごす",
      "answer": "ねすごす",
      "meaning": "to oversleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "科学技術",
      "answer": "かがくぎじゅつ",
      "meaning": "science and technology, scientific technique"
    },
    {
      "question": "裸身",
      "answer": "らしん,はだかみ",
      "meaning": "naked body, naked sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "両の手",
      "answer": "りょうのて",
      "meaning": "both hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "海賊船",
      "answer": "かいぞくせん",
      "meaning": "pirate ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "堅固",
      "answer": "けんご",
      "meaning": "solid, strong, firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "官能的",
      "answer": "かんのうてき",
      "meaning": "sensual, voluptuous, sexy, arousing"
    },
    {
      "question": "辞さない",
      "answer": "じさない",
      "meaning": "willing to do, prepared"
    },
    {
      "question": "損壊",
      "answer": "そんかい",
      "meaning": "damage, destruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "関知",
      "answer": "かんち",
      "meaning": "concern, business"
    },
    {
      "question": "血眼",
      "answer": "ちまなこ,ちめ",
      "meaning": "bloodshot eyes, (doing something in a) frenzy"
    },
    {
      "question": "日記帳",
      "answer": "にっきちょう",
      "meaning": "diary"
    },
    {
      "question": "枯らす",
      "answer": "からす",
      "meaning": "to let dry, to kill (vegetation), to season (lumber)"
    },
    {
      "question": "満場一致",
      "answer": "まんじょういっち",
      "meaning": "unanimity"
    },
    {
      "question": "ソ連",
      "answer": "ソれん",
      "meaning": "Soviet Union, Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, USSR"
    },
    {
      "question": "大打撃",
      "answer": "だいだげき",
      "meaning": "serious damage, injury or loss, heavy blow"
    },
    {
      "question": "郵便",
      "answer": "ゆうびん",
      "meaning": "mail service, postal service, mail, post, postal matter, postal items"
    },
    {
      "question": "脅える",
      "answer": "おびえる",
      "meaning": "to become frightened, to be frightened (of), to be scared (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "先っちょ",
      "answer": "さきっちょ",
      "meaning": "end, tip, point"
    },
    {
      "question": "焼",
      "answer": "やき",
      "meaning": "cooking, esp. frying or stir-frying, heating, tempering, -ware"
    },
    {
      "question": "空軍",
      "answer": "くうぐん",
      "meaning": "air force"
    },
    {
      "question": "沿岸",
      "answer": "えんがん",
      "meaning": "coast, shore, littoral"
    },
    {
      "question": "臭み",
      "answer": "くさみ",
      "meaning": "bad smell, affectation, fulsomeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "処する",
      "answer": "しょする",
      "meaning": "to manage, to deal with, to cope with, to sentence, to condemn, to punish"
    },
    {
      "question": "船上",
      "answer": "せんじょう",
      "meaning": "on board a ship, aboard a ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "同盟国",
      "answer": "どうめいこく",
      "meaning": "ally (of another nation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "由々しい",
      "answer": "ゆゆしい",
      "meaning": "grave, serious, alarming"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽はずみ",
      "answer": "かるはずみ,かろはずみ",
      "meaning": "thoughtless, rash, hasty, imprudent"
    },
    {
      "question": "光量",
      "answer": "こうりょう",
      "meaning": "amount of light, quantity of light"
    },
    {
      "question": "作文",
      "answer": "さくぶん,さくもん",
      "meaning": "writing (an essay, prose, etc.), composition, formal writing with little real meaning, writing (poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "連勝",
      "answer": "れんしょう",
      "meaning": "consecutive victories, series of victories"
    },
    {
      "question": "去来",
      "answer": "きょらい",
      "meaning": "coming and going, recurring (esp. thoughts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "体形",
      "answer": "たいけい",
      "meaning": "figure, body shape, build, physique, form"
    },
    {
      "question": "与太話",
      "answer": "よたばなし",
      "meaning": "idle gossip, foolish talk, yarn"
    },
    {
      "question": "波風",
      "answer": "なみかぜ",
      "meaning": "wind and waves, strife, discord, dissension"
    },
    {
      "question": "目に余る",
      "answer": "めにあまる",
      "meaning": "to be intolerable, to be unpardonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵舎",
      "answer": "へいしゃ",
      "meaning": "barracks"
    },
    {
      "question": "規約",
      "answer": "きやく",
      "meaning": "agreement, rules, code, protocol, convention, bylaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "折檻",
      "answer": "せっかん",
      "meaning": "physical punishment, beating, smacking, spanking, severe scolding, chastisement, discipline"
    },
    {
      "question": "属す",
      "answer": "ぞくす,しょくす",
      "meaning": "to belong to, to come under, to be affiliated with, to be subject to, to entrust, to send (a message"
    },
    {
      "question": "品種",
      "answer": "ひんしゅ",
      "meaning": "kind (of goods), brand, (taxonomical) form, breed, cultivar"
    },
    {
      "question": "押し問答",
      "answer": "おしもんどう",
      "meaning": "arguing back and forth, bandying words, verbal tug-of-war"
    },
    {
      "question": "異邦人",
      "answer": "いほうじん",
      "meaning": "foreigner, stranger, gentile, goy, non-Jew"
    },
    {
      "question": "風上",
      "answer": "かざかみ",
      "meaning": "windward, upwind"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜気",
      "answer": "やき",
      "meaning": "night air, stillness of night, cool evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "見識",
      "answer": "けんしき",
      "meaning": "views, opinion, discernment, pride, self-respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "庶民的",
      "answer": "しょみんてき",
      "meaning": "popular, folksy, plebeian, ordinary, unpretentious"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴女",
      "answer": "ちじょ",
      "meaning": "female molester"
    },
    {
      "question": "威風堂々",
      "answer": "いふうどうどう",
      "meaning": "being majestic, with great pomp and circumstance, with an imposing air"
    },
    {
      "question": "拾い",
      "answer": "ひろい",
      "meaning": "picking up, someone who picks up things, type picking (letterpress printing), walking (of an aristoc"
    },
    {
      "question": "峡谷",
      "answer": "きょうこく",
      "meaning": "gorge, ravine, canyon, glen"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪友",
      "answer": "あくゆう",
      "meaning": "undesirable friend, bad company, bad companion, bad influence, partner-in-crime (i.e. good friend),"
    },
    {
      "question": "排水",
      "answer": "はいすい",
      "meaning": "drainage, draining, pumping out (water), sewerage, displacement"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉少な",
      "answer": "ことばずくな,ことばすくな,ことばずけな",
      "meaning": "laconic, of few words, reticent, quiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "震撼",
      "answer": "しんかん",
      "meaning": "shake, shock"
    },
    {
      "question": "残響",
      "answer": "ざんきょう",
      "meaning": "reverberation, echo"
    },
    {
      "question": "週明け",
      "answer": "しゅうあけ",
      "meaning": "beginning of next week (usu. Monday), early next week"
    },
    {
      "question": "目算",
      "answer": "もくさん",
      "meaning": "rough estimate, rough calculation, expectation, anticipation, plan"
    },
    {
      "question": "抜き打ち",
      "answer": "ぬきうち",
      "meaning": "drawing a katana and attacking in the same stroke, doing something suddenly, without warning"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪人",
      "answer": "ろうにん",
      "meaning": "ronin, masterless samurai, high school graduate waiting for another chance to enter university after"
    },
    {
      "question": "勅命",
      "answer": "ちょくめい",
      "meaning": "imperial command"
    },
    {
      "question": "回し",
      "answer": "まわし",
      "meaning": "mawashi, belt, loincloth, mantle, cape, gang rape"
    },
    {
      "question": "満席",
      "answer": "まんせき",
      "meaning": "full house, all seats occupied, fully occupied"
    },
    {
      "question": "持久力",
      "answer": "じきゅうりょく",
      "meaning": "stamina, tenacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "開演",
      "answer": "かいえん",
      "meaning": "curtain raising, starting (e.g. play, concert)"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜遊び",
      "answer": "よあそび",
      "meaning": "nightlife, night amusements"
    },
    {
      "question": "爆走",
      "answer": "ばくそう",
      "meaning": "roaring noisily around"
    },
    {
      "question": "押える",
      "answer": "おさえる",
      "meaning": "to pin down, to hold down, to press down, to cover (esp. a part of one's body with one's hand), to c"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷遇",
      "answer": "れいぐう",
      "meaning": "cold reception, inhospitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "相乗効果",
      "answer": "そうじょうこうか",
      "meaning": "synergy"
    },
    {
      "question": "大豆",
      "answer": "だいず",
      "meaning": "soya bean (Glycine max), soybean, soy"
    },
    {
      "question": "政略",
      "answer": "せいりゃく",
      "meaning": "politics, political manoeuvre, political maneuver"
    },
    {
      "question": "明察",
      "answer": "めいさつ",
      "meaning": "discernment, penetration, insight, intellectual acumen"
    },
    {
      "question": "産出",
      "answer": "さんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "production, output, turning out"
    },
    {
      "question": "未開",
      "answer": "みかい",
      "meaning": "uncivilized, uncivilised, primitive, savage, undeveloped (land), unexplored (territory, field, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "講じる",
      "answer": "こうじる",
      "meaning": "to take measures, to work out a plan, to lecture, to read aloud, to confer"
    },
    {
      "question": "責め苦",
      "answer": "せめく",
      "meaning": "torture, pains (of hell)"
    },
    {
      "question": "心象",
      "answer": "しんしょう",
      "meaning": "mental image, mental picture, image"
    },
    {
      "question": "一蓮托生",
      "answer": "いちれんたくしょう",
      "meaning": "sharing one's lot with another, being in the same boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "恒星",
      "answer": "こうせい",
      "meaning": "(fixed) star (i.e. not a planet, meteorite, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "壇",
      "answer": "だん",
      "meaning": "platform, podium, rostrum, pulpit, (ceremonial) mound, world (of haiku, art, etc.), (literary) circl"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶器",
      "answer": "ちゃき",
      "meaning": "tea utensils, container for powdered green tea (tea ceremony)"
    },
    {
      "question": "道を譲る",
      "answer": "みちをゆずる",
      "meaning": "to yield, to give way to, to make way for"
    },
    {
      "question": "官吏",
      "answer": "かんり",
      "meaning": "government official, clerk"
    },
    {
      "question": "農具",
      "answer": "のうぐ",
      "meaning": "farming implement, farm tools"
    },
    {
      "question": "各員",
      "answer": "かくいん",
      "meaning": "each one"
    },
    {
      "question": "安売り",
      "answer": "やすうり",
      "meaning": "bargain sale, selling cheaply, giving out freely"
    },
    {
      "question": "城主",
      "answer": "じょうしゅ",
      "meaning": "lord of a castle"
    },
    {
      "question": "虫歯",
      "answer": "むしば",
      "meaning": "cavity, tooth decay, decayed tooth, dental caries"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬り込む",
      "answer": "きりこむ",
      "meaning": "to cut deep into, to cut one's way into (an enemy position), to rush on, to raid, to attack, to pres"
    },
    {
      "question": "同色",
      "answer": "どうしょく",
      "meaning": "same color, same colour"
    },
    {
      "question": "静",
      "answer": "せい,しず",
      "meaning": "stillness, quiet, peacefulness, calm, still"
    },
    {
      "question": "高低",
      "answer": "こうてい,たかひく",
      "meaning": "high and low, rise and fall"
    },
    {
      "question": "救国",
      "answer": "きゅうこく",
      "meaning": "patriot devoted to the salvation of his country"
    },
    {
      "question": "恐喝",
      "answer": "きょうかつ",
      "meaning": "blackmail, extortion, threat (to extort money)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大勝利",
      "answer": "だいしょうり",
      "meaning": "huge win, overwhelming victory"
    },
    {
      "question": "医術",
      "answer": "いじゅつ",
      "meaning": "medicine, healing art"
    },
    {
      "question": "災禍",
      "answer": "さいか",
      "meaning": "disaster, accident, calamity, catastrophe"
    },
    {
      "question": "七夕",
      "answer": "たなばた,しちせき",
      "meaning": "Star Festival (held in July or August), Tanabata, Festival of the Weaver"
    },
    {
      "question": "拭い去る",
      "answer": "ぬぐいさる",
      "meaning": "to rub out, to clean off, to clear away, to efface, to erase"
    },
    {
      "question": "事務局",
      "answer": "じむきょく",
      "meaning": "secretariat, executive office"
    },
    {
      "question": "句",
      "answer": "く",
      "meaning": "section (i.e. of text), sentence, passage, paragraph, phrase, verse (of 5 or 7 mora in Japanese poet"
    },
    {
      "question": "刑罰",
      "answer": "けいばつ",
      "meaning": "(criminal) punishment, penalty, sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "不得手",
      "answer": "ふえて",
      "meaning": "weak point, unskillfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "審問",
      "answer": "しんもん",
      "meaning": "interrogation, hearing, trial"
    },
    {
      "question": "小刀",
      "answer": "こがたな,しょうとう",
      "meaning": "(small) knife, short sword, small sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "世辞",
      "answer": "せじ",
      "meaning": "flattery, compliment"
    },
    {
      "question": "肝要",
      "answer": "かんよう",
      "meaning": "extremely important, essential, vital, crucial"
    },
    {
      "question": "引き倒す",
      "answer": "ひきたおす",
      "meaning": "to pull down"
    },
    {
      "question": "師事",
      "answer": "しじ",
      "meaning": "studying under, looking up to, apprenticing oneself to"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛力",
      "answer": "ごうりき",
      "meaning": "herculean strength, mountain carrier-guide"
    },
    {
      "question": "父君",
      "answer": "ふくん,ちちぎみ",
      "meaning": "father"
    },
    {
      "question": "閉鎖的",
      "answer": "へいさてき",
      "meaning": "insular, closed, unsociable, exclusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "暫定",
      "answer": "ざんてい",
      "meaning": "provisional, temporary, tentative"
    },
    {
      "question": "続編",
      "answer": "ぞくへん",
      "meaning": "continuation, sequel"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺志",
      "answer": "いし",
      "meaning": "wishes of a deceased person, dying wish"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹き出る",
      "answer": "ふきでる",
      "meaning": "to blow out, to spout out"
    },
    {
      "question": "避妊",
      "answer": "ひにん",
      "meaning": "contraception"
    },
    {
      "question": "美声",
      "answer": "びせい",
      "meaning": "beautiful voice"
    },
    {
      "question": "情事",
      "answer": "じょうじ",
      "meaning": "love affair, liaison"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂場",
      "answer": "すなば",
      "meaning": "sandpit, sandbox"
    },
    {
      "question": "期待外れ",
      "answer": "きたいはずれ",
      "meaning": "disappointment, let-down"
    },
    {
      "question": "身に付く",
      "answer": "みにつく",
      "meaning": "to master (e.g. a skill), to become accustomed to (e.g. a lifestyle), to acquire (e.g. a habit), to"
    },
    {
      "question": "師範",
      "answer": "しはん",
      "meaning": "instructor, (fencing) teacher, model"
    },
    {
      "question": "癪に障る",
      "answer": "しゃくにさわる",
      "meaning": "to irritate, to grate on one's nerves, to aggravate, to be galling, to be invidious"
    },
    {
      "question": "老体",
      "answer": "ろうたい",
      "meaning": "old body, aged person, elderly person"
    },
    {
      "question": "下賜",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "grant, bestowal, giving something to someone of low social standing (by a person of very high social"
    },
    {
      "question": "共食い",
      "answer": "ともぐい",
      "meaning": "cannibalism (in animals), feeding on each other, mutually harmful competition, internecine struggle,"
    },
    {
      "question": "硝煙",
      "answer": "しょうえん",
      "meaning": "gunpowder smoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "盟主",
      "answer": "めいしゅ",
      "meaning": "leader (of an alliance), leading power"
    },
    {
      "question": "伏線",
      "answer": "ふくせん",
      "meaning": "foreshadowing, preparation, precautionary measures"
    },
    {
      "question": "得難い",
      "answer": "えがたい",
      "meaning": "hard to get, hard to come by"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦言",
      "answer": "くげん",
      "meaning": "candid advice, frank advice, honest opinion, exhortation, harsh but honest advice"
    },
    {
      "question": "専攻",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "major subject, special study"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒性",
      "answer": "どくせい",
      "meaning": "toxicity, virulence, toxic, virulent, poisonous"
    },
    {
      "question": "手回し",
      "answer": "てまわし",
      "meaning": "turning by hand, hand-turned, hand-cranked, preparations, arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "零時",
      "answer": "れいじ",
      "meaning": "twelve o'clock, midnight, noon"
    },
    {
      "question": "女子会",
      "answer": "じょしかい",
      "meaning": "girls-only gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "心を打つ",
      "answer": "こころをうつ",
      "meaning": "to touch (a person's) heart, to impress (a person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "上演",
      "answer": "じょうえん",
      "meaning": "performance (of a play, opera, etc.), staging, presentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "文化的",
      "answer": "ぶんかてき",
      "meaning": "cultural"
    },
    {
      "question": "論破",
      "answer": "ろんぱ",
      "meaning": "defeating an argument, winning an argument, refutation, confutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "安穏",
      "answer": "あんのん,あんおん",
      "meaning": "peace, quiet, tranquility, tranquillity"
    },
    {
      "question": "一気飲み",
      "answer": "いっきのみ",
      "meaning": "chugging (a glassful of) a drink in one go"
    },
    {
      "question": "九つ",
      "answer": "ここのつ",
      "meaning": "nine, nine years of age, twelve o'clock (old time system)"
    },
    {
      "question": "新設",
      "answer": "しんせつ",
      "meaning": "establishing, founding, setting up, organizing, establishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "加速度的",
      "answer": "かそくどてき",
      "meaning": "accelerated, accelerating, gathering speed"
    },
    {
      "question": "不得意",
      "answer": "ふとくい",
      "meaning": "one's weak point"
    },
    {
      "question": "古書",
      "answer": "こしょ",
      "meaning": "old book, rare book, classic, secondhand book, used book"
    },
    {
      "question": "物価",
      "answer": "ぶっか",
      "meaning": "prices of commodities, prices (in general), cost-of-living"
    },
    {
      "question": "抑え",
      "answer": "おさえ",
      "meaning": "weight (e.g. paperweight), pressing down, keeping control, exercising authority, having self-control"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄棒",
      "answer": "てつぼう,かなぼう",
      "meaning": "iron rod, iron bar, iron club, horizontal bar (gymnastics), metal rod, metal bar, crowbar, iron staf"
    },
    {
      "question": "存亡",
      "answer": "そんぼう",
      "meaning": "life or death, existence, destiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "土地勘",
      "answer": "とちかん",
      "meaning": "familiarity with the land, locality or terrain (usually associated with knowing or feeling the local"
    },
    {
      "question": "天井裏",
      "answer": "てんじょううら",
      "meaning": "above the ceiling"
    },
    {
      "question": "山間",
      "answer": "さんかん,やまあい,やまま",
      "meaning": "among the mountains, valley, ravine, glen, gorge"
    },
    {
      "question": "世話役",
      "answer": "せわやく",
      "meaning": "mediator, manager, caretaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "膿",
      "answer": "うみ,のう",
      "meaning": "pus, corruption, rot, evils"
    },
    {
      "question": "特異点",
      "answer": "とくいてん",
      "meaning": "singularity, singular point"
    },
    {
      "question": "急務",
      "answer": "きゅうむ",
      "meaning": "urgent business, pressing need, imperative"
    },
    {
      "question": "編隊",
      "answer": "へんたい",
      "meaning": "formation (e.g. of aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒屋",
      "answer": "さかや",
      "meaning": "liquor store, wine shop, bottle shop, sake dealer, liquor-store owner, brewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "壮麗",
      "answer": "そうれい",
      "meaning": "splendour, splendor, pompousness, magnificence"
    },
    {
      "question": "世知辛い",
      "answer": "せちがらい",
      "meaning": "hard (life), tough (world)"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱が入る",
      "answer": "ねつがはいる",
      "meaning": "to become keen on, to get passionate about"
    },
    {
      "question": "封書",
      "answer": "ふうしょ",
      "meaning": "sealed letter"
    },
    {
      "question": "食い意地",
      "answer": "くいいじ",
      "meaning": "gluttony"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒牙",
      "answer": "どくが",
      "meaning": "poison fang, sinister ways, crooked means, clutches, wily ways, dirty trick"
    },
    {
      "question": "二十日",
      "answer": "はつか",
      "meaning": "twentieth day of the month, twenty days"
    },
    {
      "question": "救世",
      "answer": "きゅうせい,ぐぜ,くせ",
      "meaning": "salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "煙る",
      "answer": "けむる,けぶる",
      "meaning": "to smoke (e.g. fire), to billow smoke, to smoulder, to smolder, to be hazy, to look dim"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁句",
      "answer": "きんく",
      "meaning": "taboo word"
    },
    {
      "question": "清々",
      "answer": "せいせい",
      "meaning": "feeling refreshed, feeling relieved"
    },
    {
      "question": "鮫",
      "answer": "さめ",
      "meaning": "shark"
    },
    {
      "question": "喉笛",
      "answer": "のどぶえ",
      "meaning": "windpipe"
    },
    {
      "question": "大漁",
      "answer": "たいりょう,たいぎょ",
      "meaning": "big catch (fishing), good haul"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れっ子",
      "answer": "うれっこ",
      "meaning": "popular figure, person in demand, favorite, favourite"
    },
    {
      "question": "引火",
      "answer": "いんか",
      "meaning": "ignition, catching fire"
    },
    {
      "question": "死活問題",
      "answer": "しかつもんだい",
      "meaning": "matter of life or death, life-and-death problem"
    },
    {
      "question": "摘み取る",
      "answer": "つみとる,つまみとる",
      "meaning": "to pluck, to pick, to nip off"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪循環",
      "answer": "あくじゅんかん",
      "meaning": "vicious circle, vicious cycle"
    },
    {
      "question": "不変",
      "answer": "ふへん",
      "meaning": "eternal, everlasting, unchangeable, immutable, immovable, constant, permanent, indestructible, invar"
    },
    {
      "question": "末席",
      "answer": "まっせき,ばっせき",
      "meaning": "lowest seat, foot of the table, seat furthest from the seat of honour, lowest rank, bottom (e.g. of"
    },
    {
      "question": "福音",
      "answer": "ふくいん",
      "meaning": "good news, gospel (teachings or revelations of Jesus Christ)"
    },
    {
      "question": "株価",
      "answer": "かぶか",
      "meaning": "stock prices"
    },
    {
      "question": "親心",
      "answer": "おやごころ",
      "meaning": "parental love or affection"
    },
    {
      "question": "一報",
      "answer": "いっぽう",
      "meaning": "information, (brief) notice, letting someone know, dropping a line, first report, initial report"
    },
    {
      "question": "身一つ",
      "answer": "みひとつ",
      "meaning": "one's body alone, having nothing except one's body, just oneself (with no belongings)"
    },
    {
      "question": "計略",
      "answer": "けいりゃく",
      "meaning": "plan, trick, plot, stratagem, scheme, trap"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り仰ぐ",
      "answer": "ふりあおぐ",
      "meaning": "to look up"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵機",
      "answer": "てっき,てきき",
      "meaning": "enemy plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "冬場",
      "answer": "ふゆば",
      "meaning": "the winter season"
    },
    {
      "question": "売上",
      "answer": "うりあげ",
      "meaning": "amount sold, sales, proceeds, takings, turnover"
    },
    {
      "question": "旨み",
      "answer": "うまみ",
      "meaning": "good flavor (flavour), good taste, deliciousness, umami (fifth category of taste in food), skill, cl"
    },
    {
      "question": "元カノ",
      "answer": "もとカノ",
      "meaning": "former girlfriend, ex-girlfriend"
    },
    {
      "question": "植え込み",
      "answer": "うえこみ",
      "meaning": "thick growth of plants, plantation, shrubbery, thicket"
    },
    {
      "question": "許容量",
      "answer": "きょようりょう",
      "meaning": "maximum permissible level or dosage"
    },
    {
      "question": "重点",
      "answer": "じゅうてん",
      "meaning": "important point, emphasis, stress, importance, priority, iteration mark, colon (punctuation)"
    },
    {
      "question": "唐辛子",
      "answer": "とうがらし,とんがらし",
      "meaning": "capsicum (Capsicum annuum, esp. the cultivated chili peppers), chili pepper (chile, chilli), cayenne"
    },
    {
      "question": "評議会",
      "answer": "ひょうぎかい",
      "meaning": "council (consultatory, advisory), board of trustees"
    },
    {
      "question": "虐め",
      "answer": "いじめ",
      "meaning": "bullying, teasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "先々",
      "answer": "さきざき",
      "meaning": "distant future, inevitable future, places one goes to"
    },
    {
      "question": "溢す",
      "answer": "こぼす",
      "meaning": "to spill, to drop, to shed (tears), to grumble, to complain, to let one's feelings show"
    },
    {
      "question": "火照り",
      "answer": "ほてり",
      "meaning": "a glow, heat, burning sensation, hot flash"
    },
    {
      "question": "履歴書",
      "answer": "りれきしょ",
      "meaning": "personal history, curriculum vitae, resume"
    },
    {
      "question": "論じる",
      "answer": "ろんじる",
      "meaning": "to discuss, to talk about, to deal with (a topic), to argue, to dispute, to take into consideration,"
    },
    {
      "question": "典型",
      "answer": "てんけい",
      "meaning": "type, pattern, model, epitome, exemplar, archetype, perfect example"
    },
    {
      "question": "意地張る",
      "answer": "いじばる,いじはる",
      "meaning": "to be stubborn, to be obstinate, to be perverse, to not give in"
    },
    {
      "question": "美丈夫",
      "answer": "びじょうふ",
      "meaning": "good-looking man, fine figure of a man"
    },
    {
      "question": "平成",
      "answer": "へいせい",
      "meaning": "Heisei era (1989.1.8-2019.4.30)"
    },
    {
      "question": "摘発",
      "answer": "てきはつ",
      "meaning": "exposing, unmasking, laying bare"
    },
    {
      "question": "床下",
      "answer": "ゆかした",
      "meaning": "under the floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "筐体",
      "answer": "きょうたい",
      "meaning": "case (of a machine, computer, etc.), casing, housing, enclosure, cabinet, chassis, frame"
    },
    {
      "question": "水臭い",
      "answer": "みずくさい",
      "meaning": "stand-offish, distant, not frank, reserved, watery (alcohol, coffee, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛気臭い",
      "answer": "しんきくさい",
      "meaning": "irritating, annoying, tedious (work, person, etc.), boring, depressing, dark (e.g. story)"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳が違う",
      "answer": "わけがちがう",
      "meaning": "to be incomparable, to be completely different matters, to be completely different things"
    },
    {
      "question": "剛直",
      "answer": "ごうちょく",
      "meaning": "integrity, moral courage, rigidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "国交",
      "answer": "こっこう",
      "meaning": "diplomatic relations"
    },
    {
      "question": "二流",
      "answer": "にりゅう",
      "meaning": "second-rate, inferior"
    },
    {
      "question": "輸血",
      "answer": "ゆけつ",
      "meaning": "blood transfusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "警鐘",
      "answer": "けいしょう",
      "meaning": "alarm bell, fire bell, warning, wake-up call"
    },
    {
      "question": "知己",
      "answer": "ちき",
      "meaning": "acquaintance, appreciative friend"
    },
    {
      "question": "欄干",
      "answer": "らんかん",
      "meaning": "railing, guard rail, handrail, banister, balustrade, parapet, (shining) brightly (of the moon or sta"
    },
    {
      "question": "眼中",
      "answer": "がんちゅう",
      "meaning": "(one's) consideration, (taking) notice, interest, attention, within the eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "早う",
      "answer": "はよう",
      "meaning": "early"
    },
    {
      "question": "円柱",
      "answer": "えんちゅう,まるばしら",
      "meaning": "column, shaft, cylinder, round pillar (esp. in buildings)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御子",
      "answer": "みこ,おこ",
      "meaning": "Son of God (in Christianity), child of an emperor, (someone else's) child"
    },
    {
      "question": "醒ます",
      "answer": "さます",
      "meaning": "to awaken, to arouse from sleep, to bring to one's senses, to disabuse (someone of), to sober up, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "本店",
      "answer": "ほんてん,ほんだな",
      "meaning": "head office, main office, main store, flagship store, this store, our store"
    },
    {
      "question": "小袋",
      "answer": "こぶくろ",
      "meaning": "small bag"
    },
    {
      "question": "額面",
      "answer": "がくめん",
      "meaning": "face value, par"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮行",
      "answer": "ばんこう",
      "meaning": "act of barbarity, barbarism, brutality, savagery"
    },
    {
      "question": "立体的",
      "answer": "りったいてき",
      "meaning": "three-dimensional"
    },
    {
      "question": "不詳",
      "answer": "ふしょう",
      "meaning": "unknown, unidentified, unspecified"
    },
    {
      "question": "及び腰",
      "answer": "およびごし",
      "meaning": "bent back, indecisive attitude, timidity, lack of nerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "勿体",
      "answer": "もったい",
      "meaning": "superior airs, air of importance, overemphasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "年数",
      "answer": "ねんすう",
      "meaning": "number of years"
    },
    {
      "question": "一言一句",
      "answer": "いちごんいっく",
      "meaning": "every single word and phrase, word by word"
    },
    {
      "question": "性感",
      "answer": "せいかん",
      "meaning": "sexual feelings"
    },
    {
      "question": "自画自賛",
      "answer": "じがじさん",
      "meaning": "singing one's own praises, praising one's own wares"
    },
    {
      "question": "眠り姫",
      "answer": "ねむりひめ",
      "meaning": "Sleeping Beauty (fairy tale)"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち運び",
      "answer": "もちはこび",
      "meaning": "carrying"
    },
    {
      "question": "白木",
      "answer": "しらき",
      "meaning": "plain wood, unfinished woodwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "肴",
      "answer": "さかな",
      "meaning": "appetizer or snack served with drinks, performance to liven up a bar, conversation to liven up a par"
    },
    {
      "question": "妙齢",
      "answer": "みょうれい",
      "meaning": "young (usu. of a woman), blooming, in the prime of youth, marriageable, with a charm appropriate to"
    },
    {
      "question": "快挙",
      "answer": "かいきょ",
      "meaning": "brilliant achievement, spectacular feat, splendid accomplishment, remarkable deed"
    },
    {
      "question": "上を行く",
      "answer": "うえをいく",
      "meaning": "to be ahead of"
    },
    {
      "question": "学歴",
      "answer": "がくれき",
      "meaning": "academic background"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵艦",
      "answer": "てきかん",
      "meaning": "enemy ship"
    },
    {
      "question": "組織的",
      "answer": "そしきてき",
      "meaning": "systematic, organized, organizational"
    },
    {
      "question": "隻眼",
      "answer": "せきがん",
      "meaning": "one eye, eye (for pictures, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "志向",
      "answer": "しこう",
      "meaning": "intention, aim, preference (for), orientation (towards a goal)"
    },
    {
      "question": "縁起",
      "answer": "えんぎ,いんえん",
      "meaning": "omen, sign of luck, origin, history, causation, dependent arising, doctrine that everything has a ca"
    },
    {
      "question": "防備",
      "answer": "ぼうび",
      "meaning": "defense, defence, defensive preparations"
    },
    {
      "question": "詠む",
      "answer": "よむ",
      "meaning": "to compose (a Japanese poem), to write, to use as the theme of a poem, to recite (e.g. a poem), to c"
    },
    {
      "question": "品種改良",
      "answer": "ひんしゅかいりょう",
      "meaning": "selective breeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "電光石火",
      "answer": "でんこうせっか",
      "meaning": "flash, instant, lightning (speed)"
    },
    {
      "question": "集中砲火",
      "answer": "しゅうちゅうほうか",
      "meaning": "concentrated fire, intense criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "脈拍",
      "answer": "みゃくはく",
      "meaning": "pulse, pulse rate, pulsation, stroke of pulse"
    },
    {
      "question": "生殺し",
      "answer": "なまごろし",
      "meaning": "half-dead, state of uncertainty, limbo, leaving unfinished with the intention of inflicting sufferin"
    },
    {
      "question": "図式",
      "answer": "ずしき",
      "meaning": "diagram, graph, schema"
    },
    {
      "question": "夏服",
      "answer": "なつふく",
      "meaning": "summer clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸共",
      "answer": "もろとも",
      "meaning": "(all) together"
    },
    {
      "question": "古臭い",
      "answer": "ふるくさい",
      "meaning": "stale, old fashioned, hackneyed, trite, antiquated, obsolete, musty, outdated"
    },
    {
      "question": "作製",
      "answer": "さくせい",
      "meaning": "manufacture, production"
    },
    {
      "question": "荒くれ者",
      "answer": "あらくれもの",
      "meaning": "ruffian, rowdy (person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一足飛び",
      "answer": "いっそくとび",
      "meaning": "(at) one bound"
    },
    {
      "question": "配線",
      "answer": "はいせん",
      "meaning": "wiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "下水",
      "answer": "げすい,したみず",
      "meaning": "drainage, ditch, gutter, sewerage, sewage, black water, water flowing underneath, one's true feeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "半島",
      "answer": "はんとう",
      "meaning": "peninsula, Korea"
    },
    {
      "question": "最適化",
      "answer": "さいてきか",
      "meaning": "optimization, optimisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "応え",
      "answer": "こたえ,いらえ,ごたえ",
      "meaning": "answer, reply, response, solution, feeling, worth ...ing, worthwhile ...ing, satisfying to ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "一個人",
      "answer": "いっこじん,いちこじん",
      "meaning": "private person, individual"
    },
    {
      "question": "強請る",
      "answer": "ねだる,ゆする",
      "meaning": "to beg, to pester, to plead, to coax, to hound, to importune, to solicit, to demand, to extort"
    },
    {
      "question": "絞め殺す",
      "answer": "しめころす",
      "meaning": "to strangle to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "直伝",
      "answer": "じきでん",
      "meaning": "direct transmission (of mystery, skill, secret, etc.), initiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "超人的",
      "answer": "ちょうじんてき",
      "meaning": "superhuman"
    },
    {
      "question": "立方体",
      "answer": "りっぽうたい",
      "meaning": "cube"
    },
    {
      "question": "九九",
      "answer": "くく",
      "meaning": "multiplication table, times table"
    },
    {
      "question": "織物",
      "answer": "おりもの",
      "meaning": "textile, fabric"
    },
    {
      "question": "十八番",
      "answer": "おはこ,じゅうはちばん",
      "meaning": "one's favourite party trick (favorite), one's specialty, one's forte, No. 18, eighteenth, repertoire"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び火",
      "answer": "とびひ",
      "meaning": "leaping flames, flying sparks, spread of fire (due to leaping flames), repercussions in unanticipate"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥を塗る",
      "answer": "どろをぬる",
      "meaning": "to besmirch, to sully"
    },
    {
      "question": "順風満帆",
      "answer": "じゅんぷうまんぱん,じゅんぷうまんぽ",
      "meaning": "smooth sailing"
    },
    {
      "question": "文脈",
      "answer": "ぶんみゃく",
      "meaning": "context"
    },
    {
      "question": "通り名",
      "answer": "とおりな",
      "meaning": "one's common name, one's popular name, alias, house name"
    },
    {
      "question": "微苦笑",
      "answer": "びくしょう",
      "meaning": "faint, ironic or bittersweet smile"
    },
    {
      "question": "眦",
      "answer": "まなじり",
      "meaning": "corner of the eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "算出",
      "answer": "さんしゅつ",
      "meaning": "calculation, computation"
    },
    {
      "question": "位階",
      "answer": "いかい",
      "meaning": "court rank"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬学",
      "answer": "やくがく",
      "meaning": "(study of) pharmacy, pharmaceutics"
    },
    {
      "question": "透過",
      "answer": "とうか",
      "meaning": "penetration, permeation, transmission"
    },
    {
      "question": "相談役",
      "answer": "そうだんやく",
      "meaning": "counselor, counsellor, adviser, advisor"
    },
    {
      "question": "疫病神",
      "answer": "やくびょうがみ,えきびょうがみ",
      "meaning": "god of pestilence, god who spreads infectious diseases, jinx, hoodoo, pest, odious person, plague, a"
    },
    {
      "question": "英雄譚",
      "answer": "えいゆうたん",
      "meaning": "epic, heroic tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔境",
      "answer": "まきょう",
      "meaning": "demon-infested place, ominous place, mysterious, unfrequented area, den of iniquity"
    },
    {
      "question": "海苔",
      "answer": "のり",
      "meaning": "nori, laver, edible seaweed, usu. Porphyra yezoensis or P. tenera, usu. dried and pressed into sheet"
    },
    {
      "question": "色味",
      "answer": "いろみ",
      "meaning": "shade, tone, tinge, hue, colour, color, tint"
    },
    {
      "question": "清純",
      "answer": "せいじゅん",
      "meaning": "purity, innocence"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆算",
      "answer": "ぎゃくさん",
      "meaning": "counting backwards, calculating backwards, inverse operation, reverse operation"
    },
    {
      "question": "持ち出し",
      "answer": "もちだし",
      "meaning": "taking something out, carrying out, providing money oneself, paying with one's own money, corbel, st"
    },
    {
      "question": "水柱",
      "answer": "みずばしら,すいちゅう",
      "meaning": "column of water, water column"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄拳",
      "answer": "てっけん",
      "meaning": "tightly clenched fist"
    },
    {
      "question": "湿布",
      "answer": "しっぷ",
      "meaning": "(wet) compress, poultice, fomentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "聳える",
      "answer": "そびえる",
      "meaning": "to rise, to tower, to soar"
    },
    {
      "question": "天体",
      "answer": "てんたい",
      "meaning": "heavenly body, celestial body, astronomical object"
    },
    {
      "question": "腕が鳴る",
      "answer": "うでがなる",
      "meaning": "to be itching to put one's skills to use"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛散",
      "answer": "ひさん",
      "meaning": "scattering (e.g. dust in the wind, enemies before an assault), dispersal, flying off (in all directi"
    },
    {
      "question": "前庭",
      "answer": "ぜんてい,まえにわ",
      "meaning": "front garden, front yard, vestibule (of the ear)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩分",
      "answer": "えんぶん",
      "meaning": "salt, salt content"
    },
    {
      "question": "惚れ込む",
      "answer": "ほれこむ",
      "meaning": "to be charmed by"
    },
    {
      "question": "落札",
      "answer": "らくさつ,おちふだ",
      "meaning": "successful bid, winning a tender, prize-winning ticket, winning lottery ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "切腹",
      "answer": "せっぷく",
      "meaning": "seppuku, harakiri, ritual suicide by disembowelment, seppuku as a death penalty (where the convict i"
    },
    {
      "question": "神罰",
      "answer": "しんばつ",
      "meaning": "divine punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "度外視",
      "answer": "どがいし",
      "meaning": "disregarding, taking no account of, ignoring, overlooking"
    },
    {
      "question": "策謀",
      "answer": "さくぼう",
      "meaning": "strategy, artifice"
    },
    {
      "question": "錠剤",
      "answer": "じょうざい",
      "meaning": "pill, lozenge, tablet"
    },
    {
      "question": "心を砕く",
      "answer": "こころをくだく",
      "meaning": "to take great pains, to make every effort, to rack one's brains, to be concerned, to worry"
    },
    {
      "question": "手付き",
      "answer": "てつき",
      "meaning": "manner of using one's hands"
    },
    {
      "question": "標高",
      "answer": "ひょうこう",
      "meaning": "elevation, height above sea level"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳罰",
      "answer": "げんばつ",
      "meaning": "severe punishment, rigorous measures"
    },
    {
      "question": "壁画",
      "answer": "へきが",
      "meaning": "fresco, mural, wall painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "曲芸",
      "answer": "きょくげい",
      "meaning": "acrobatics"
    },
    {
      "question": "勘繰る",
      "answer": "かんぐる",
      "meaning": "to be suspicious of (someone's motives), to suspect (that)"
    },
    {
      "question": "破天荒",
      "answer": "はてんこう",
      "meaning": "unheard-of, unprecedented"
    },
    {
      "question": "万感",
      "answer": "ばんかん",
      "meaning": "flood of emotions, many thoughts"
    },
    {
      "question": "分け前",
      "answer": "わけまえ",
      "meaning": "share, portion, quota, cut"
    },
    {
      "question": "野暮用",
      "answer": "やぼよう",
      "meaning": "minor business"
    },
    {
      "question": "斗",
      "answer": "ます,と,とます",
      "meaning": "measuring container, measure, box (seating at a theatre, etc.), square on a grid, cell of a grid, sq"
    },
    {
      "question": "読み方",
      "answer": "よみかた",
      "meaning": "pronunciation, reading (e.g. of a kanji), way of reading (out loud), interpretation (e.g. of a text)"
    },
    {
      "question": "海岸線",
      "answer": "かいがんせん",
      "meaning": "coastline, shoreline, coastal railway"
    },
    {
      "question": "指を折る",
      "answer": "ゆびをおる",
      "meaning": "to count on one's fingers"
    },
    {
      "question": "素人目",
      "answer": "しろうとめ",
      "meaning": "inexpert or untrained eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "参道",
      "answer": "さんどう",
      "meaning": "road approaching a shrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "血が騒ぐ",
      "answer": "ちがさわぐ",
      "meaning": "to get excited, to be roused (to action), to get the itch (to do)"
    },
    {
      "question": "下山",
      "answer": "げざん,げさん",
      "meaning": "descending (mountain)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一役買う",
      "answer": "ひとやくかう",
      "meaning": "to take on a role, to take part"
    },
    {
      "question": "調律",
      "answer": "ちょうりつ",
      "meaning": "tuning (musical)"
    },
    {
      "question": "半眼",
      "answer": "はんがん",
      "meaning": "with eyes half-closed"
    },
    {
      "question": "増",
      "answer": "ぞう",
      "meaning": "increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛み止め",
      "answer": "いたみどめ",
      "meaning": "painkiller"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝ち組",
      "answer": "かちぐみ",
      "meaning": "winners (those who have succeeded socially, economically, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "美食",
      "answer": "びしょく",
      "meaning": "gourmet food, delicious food, dining on gourmet food, following a lavish diet, living as an epicure"
    },
    {
      "question": "飢餓",
      "answer": "きが",
      "meaning": "starvation, famine, hunger"
    },
    {
      "question": "明記",
      "answer": "めいき",
      "meaning": "clear writing, specification"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い様",
      "answer": "いいよう,いいざま",
      "meaning": "manner of speaking, mode of expression, way of saying something, at the same time as speaking, as on"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃避行",
      "answer": "とうひこう",
      "meaning": "flight, elopement"
    },
    {
      "question": "深部",
      "answer": "しんぶ",
      "meaning": "depths, deep part"
    },
    {
      "question": "弟妹",
      "answer": "ていまい",
      "meaning": "younger brother and sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉欲",
      "answer": "にくよく",
      "meaning": "lust, lusts of the flesh, animal passions, carnal desires"
    },
    {
      "question": "一欠片",
      "answer": "ひとかけら",
      "meaning": "fragment, piece"
    },
    {
      "question": "腫れ",
      "answer": "はれ",
      "meaning": "swelling, boil"
    },
    {
      "question": "不景気",
      "answer": "ふけいき",
      "meaning": "economic slump, hard times, depression, recession, poor (business), dull, slack, inactive, gloomy, c"
    },
    {
      "question": "配する",
      "answer": "はいする",
      "meaning": "to distribute, to arrange, to allot (to a position of authority, etc.), to lay out (as in decorating"
    },
    {
      "question": "不登校",
      "answer": "ふとうこう",
      "meaning": "truancy, school non-attendance"
    },
    {
      "question": "横流し",
      "answer": "よこながし",
      "meaning": "diversion into illegal channels, putting on the black market, selling through illegal channels"
    },
    {
      "question": "増員",
      "answer": "ぞういん",
      "meaning": "increasing the number of staff, hiring more people"
    },
    {
      "question": "曜日",
      "answer": "ようび",
      "meaning": "day of the week"
    },
    {
      "question": "貸し出し",
      "answer": "かしだし",
      "meaning": "lending, loaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "送り迎え",
      "answer": "おくりむかえ",
      "meaning": "seeing (or dropping) off, then later picking up or going to meet (the same person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き埋め",
      "answer": "いきうめ",
      "meaning": "burying alive"
    },
    {
      "question": "元手",
      "answer": "もとで",
      "meaning": "capital, funds, seed money, asset"
    },
    {
      "question": "対空",
      "answer": "たいくう",
      "meaning": "anti-aircraft, antiaircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "東北",
      "answer": "とうほく,ひがしきた",
      "meaning": "north-east, Tōhoku (northernmost six prefectures of Honshu), Tohoku"
    },
    {
      "question": "介在",
      "answer": "かいざい",
      "meaning": "existing (between), interposition, intervention, involvement"
    },
    {
      "question": "板挟み",
      "answer": "いたばさみ",
      "meaning": "being stuck between a rock and a hard place, being in a dilemma, being torn between conflicting dema"
    },
    {
      "question": "活字",
      "answer": "かつじ",
      "meaning": "printing type, movable type, printed text, print"
    },
    {
      "question": "受諾",
      "answer": "じゅだく",
      "meaning": "acceptance"
    },
    {
      "question": "織り込む",
      "answer": "おりこむ",
      "meaning": "to weave into, to interweave, to be incorporated in, to be factored in"
    },
    {
      "question": "運河",
      "answer": "うんが",
      "meaning": "(navigable) canal, waterway"
    },
    {
      "question": "川辺",
      "answer": "かわべ",
      "meaning": "riverside, edge of a river"
    },
    {
      "question": "最古",
      "answer": "さいこ",
      "meaning": "the oldest"
    },
    {
      "question": "均一",
      "answer": "きんいつ,きんいち",
      "meaning": "uniformity, equality"
    },
    {
      "question": "北極",
      "answer": "ほっきょく",
      "meaning": "North Pole, the Arctic"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩漬け",
      "answer": "しおづけ",
      "meaning": "pickling in salt, leaving unchanged, leaving unused"
    },
    {
      "question": "占有",
      "answer": "せんゆう",
      "meaning": "possession, occupation, occupancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "丸っこい",
      "answer": "まるっこい",
      "meaning": "round, spherical, circular"
    },
    {
      "question": "憂慮",
      "answer": "ゆうりょ",
      "meaning": "anxiety, concern, fear"
    },
    {
      "question": "完全無欠",
      "answer": "かんぜんむけつ",
      "meaning": "flawless, absolute perfection"
    },
    {
      "question": "深度",
      "answer": "しんど",
      "meaning": "depth"
    },
    {
      "question": "新天地",
      "answer": "しんてんち",
      "meaning": "new land, new world, new sphere of activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "劣悪",
      "answer": "れつあく",
      "meaning": "inferior, coarse, poor quality, inadequate, deteriorated"
    },
    {
      "question": "布巾",
      "answer": "ふきん",
      "meaning": "tea-towel, dish cloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "大の男",
      "answer": "だいのおとこ",
      "meaning": "adult man"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊気",
      "answer": "れいき",
      "meaning": "mysterious presence, mysterious atmosphere, aura of mystery"
    },
    {
      "question": "唄",
      "answer": "うた",
      "meaning": "song"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱病",
      "answer": "ねつびょう",
      "meaning": "fever, febrile disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "捏ねる",
      "answer": "こねる",
      "meaning": "to knead, to mix with fingers, to quibble, to argue for argument's sake"
    },
    {
      "question": "幕引き",
      "answer": "まくひき",
      "meaning": "putting an end to"
    },
    {
      "question": "口が滑る",
      "answer": "くちがすべる",
      "meaning": "to make a slip of the tongue, to let something slip"
    },
    {
      "question": "別働隊",
      "answer": "べつどうたい",
      "meaning": "flying column, detached force"
    },
    {
      "question": "走り書き",
      "answer": "はしりがき",
      "meaning": "scribbling, scrawl, hasty writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "倒錯",
      "answer": "とうさく",
      "meaning": "perversion, inversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "猪突猛進",
      "answer": "ちょとつもうしん",
      "meaning": "headlong rush, rushing recklessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "石材",
      "answer": "せきざい",
      "meaning": "(building) stone"
    },
    {
      "question": "泰然",
      "answer": "たいぜん",
      "meaning": "calm, composed, self-possessed, firm"
    },
    {
      "question": "変調",
      "answer": "へんちょう",
      "meaning": "change of tone, variation (music), irregularity, anomaly, abnormality, modulation (in radio)"
    },
    {
      "question": "上っ面",
      "answer": "うわっつら",
      "meaning": "surface, appearances"
    },
    {
      "question": "当方",
      "answer": "とうほう",
      "meaning": "I, we, our part"
    },
    {
      "question": "煎餅",
      "answer": "せんべい",
      "meaning": "rice cracker, Japanese cracker, rice cookie, wafer"
    },
    {
      "question": "写メ",
      "answer": "しゃメ",
      "meaning": "email with attached photos sent from a mobile phone, photo taken with a mobile phone, taking a photo"
    },
    {
      "question": "撥ねる",
      "answer": "はねる",
      "meaning": "to hit (e.g. to have a car hit someone), to run into, to reject, to deny, to refuse, to eliminate, t"
    },
    {
      "question": "仄暗い",
      "answer": "ほのぐらい",
      "meaning": "gloomy, obscure"
    },
    {
      "question": "只今",
      "answer": "ただいま,しこん",
      "meaning": "Here I am, I'm home!, presently, right away, right now, just now"
    },
    {
      "question": "収まり",
      "answer": "おさまり",
      "meaning": "conclusion, end, settlement"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り返し",
      "answer": "きりかえし",
      "meaning": "railway switchback, twisting backward knee trip"
    },
    {
      "question": "嫡子",
      "answer": "ちゃくし",
      "meaning": "legitimate child"
    },
    {
      "question": "三種",
      "answer": "さんしゅ",
      "meaning": "three kinds, three varieties"
    },
    {
      "question": "弔い",
      "answer": "とむらい,とぶらい,ともらい",
      "meaning": "funeral, burial, condolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "南北",
      "answer": "なんぼく",
      "meaning": "north and south, north to south, South Korea and North Korea"
    },
    {
      "question": "最年長",
      "answer": "さいねんちょう",
      "meaning": "eldest"
    },
    {
      "question": "興す",
      "answer": "おこす",
      "meaning": "to vitalize (e.g. an industry), to invigorate, to energize, to revive, to promote, to make prosperou"
    },
    {
      "question": "垢",
      "answer": "あか,く",
      "meaning": "dirt, filth, grime, account (e.g. online service), klesha (polluting thoughts such as greed, hatred"
    },
    {
      "question": "先ずは",
      "answer": "まずは",
      "meaning": "first of all, to begin with, before anything else, probably, most likely, almost certainly, virtuall"
    },
    {
      "question": "寄り付く",
      "answer": "よりつく",
      "meaning": "to approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "編み物",
      "answer": "あみもの",
      "meaning": "knitting, knitted material, crochet"
    },
    {
      "question": "人格者",
      "answer": "じんかくしゃ",
      "meaning": "person of character, man of character"
    },
    {
      "question": "激動",
      "answer": "げきどう",
      "meaning": "violent shock, agitation, turbulence, turmoil, upheaval, excitement"
    },
    {
      "question": "重量感",
      "answer": "じゅうりょうかん",
      "meaning": "thick and heavy"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜叉",
      "answer": "やしゃ",
      "meaning": "yaksha (Buddhist guardian deities sometimes depicted as demonic warriors)"
    },
    {
      "question": "全権",
      "answer": "ぜんけん",
      "meaning": "plenipotentiary powers, full authority"
    },
    {
      "question": "結婚指輪",
      "answer": "けっこんゆびわ",
      "meaning": "wedding ring, wedding band"
    },
    {
      "question": "貴金属",
      "answer": "ききんぞく",
      "meaning": "precious metal"
    },
    {
      "question": "武者震い",
      "answer": "むしゃぶるい",
      "meaning": "trembling with excitement"
    },
    {
      "question": "長持ち",
      "answer": "ながもち",
      "meaning": "long-lasting, long-wearing, wears well, nagamochi, large oblong chest (for clothing, personal effect"
    },
    {
      "question": "石垣",
      "answer": "いしがき",
      "meaning": "stone wall"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔方陣",
      "answer": "まほうじん",
      "meaning": "magic square"
    },
    {
      "question": "周年",
      "answer": "しゅうねん",
      "meaning": "whole year, entire year, n-th year anniversary"
    },
    {
      "question": "今年度",
      "answer": "こんねんど",
      "meaning": "this year, this fiscal year, this school year"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦もなく",
      "answer": "くもなく",
      "meaning": "easily, without effort"
    },
    {
      "question": "有頂天",
      "answer": "うちょうてん",
      "meaning": "ecstasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳守",
      "answer": "げんしゅ",
      "meaning": "strict observance, rigid adherence, scrupulous compliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "無茶振り",
      "answer": "むちゃぶり",
      "meaning": "unreasonable request, asking for something unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "子守歌",
      "answer": "こもりうた",
      "meaning": "lullaby"
    },
    {
      "question": "飽き飽き",
      "answer": "あきあき",
      "meaning": "getting tired of, getting sick of, getting bored with, getting fed up with"
    },
    {
      "question": "怪鳥",
      "answer": "かいちょう,けちょう",
      "meaning": "mysterious bird, strange bird, eerie bird, monster that has taken the form of a bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "本丸",
      "answer": "ほんまる",
      "meaning": "inner citadel, core, center, centre, focus, crux"
    },
    {
      "question": "介する",
      "answer": "かいする",
      "meaning": "to use as an intermediary, to worry, to mind, to care"
    },
    {
      "question": "交友",
      "answer": "こうゆう",
      "meaning": "friend, companion, acquaintance, friendship, companionship"
    },
    {
      "question": "生き甲斐",
      "answer": "いきがい",
      "meaning": "reason for living, something one lives for, purpose in life, raison d'être"
    },
    {
      "question": "錯綜",
      "answer": "さくそう",
      "meaning": "complication, intricacy, involution, to become complicated, to get entangled"
    },
    {
      "question": "飢え死に",
      "answer": "うえじに,かつえじに",
      "meaning": "(death from) starvation, starving to death"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩気",
      "answer": "しおけ",
      "meaning": "saltiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "庁舎",
      "answer": "ちょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "government office building"
    },
    {
      "question": "我知らず",
      "answer": "われしらず",
      "meaning": "involuntarily, instinctively, without realizing, unconsciously"
    },
    {
      "question": "間中",
      "answer": "あいだじゅう",
      "meaning": "during"
    },
    {
      "question": "司法",
      "answer": "しほう",
      "meaning": "administration of justice"
    },
    {
      "question": "暗視",
      "answer": "あんし",
      "meaning": "night vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯切れ",
      "answer": "はぎれ",
      "meaning": "feel when biting, manner of enunciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "布く",
      "answer": "しく",
      "meaning": "to spread out, to lay out, to take a position, to impose widely (e.g. over a city)"
    },
    {
      "question": "風雨",
      "answer": "ふうう",
      "meaning": "wind and rain, rainstorm"
    },
    {
      "question": "事故る",
      "answer": "じこる",
      "meaning": "to have an accident (esp. traffic accident), to cause an accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "葡萄",
      "answer": "ぶどう,えび",
      "meaning": "grape, grapevine"
    },
    {
      "question": "大海原",
      "answer": "おおうなばら",
      "meaning": "the ocean, the great deep"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱中症",
      "answer": "ねっちゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "heatstroke"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛妾",
      "answer": "あいしょう",
      "meaning": "beloved concubine, favourite concubine (e.g. of the shogun)"
    },
    {
      "question": "煎じる",
      "answer": "せんじる",
      "meaning": "to boil, to decoct, to infuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "木登り",
      "answer": "きのぼり",
      "meaning": "tree climbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "人食い",
      "answer": "ひとくい",
      "meaning": "cannibalism, biting (someone), man-eating (e.g. tiger), cannibalistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "盤上",
      "answer": "ばんじょう",
      "meaning": "on the board (shogi, go, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "撫子",
      "answer": "なでしこ",
      "meaning": "pink (any flower of genus Dianthus, esp. the fringed pink, Dianthus superbus), lovable, caressable g"
    },
    {
      "question": "籠手",
      "answer": "こて",
      "meaning": "gauntlet (used in Kendo), bracer, fencing glove"
    },
    {
      "question": "発情期",
      "answer": "はつじょうき",
      "meaning": "mating season, estrus (oestrus), estrum, the rut"
    },
    {
      "question": "職種",
      "answer": "しょくしゅ",
      "meaning": "type of occupation, occupational category"
    },
    {
      "question": "診療",
      "answer": "しんりょう",
      "meaning": "diagnosis and treatment, medical care"
    },
    {
      "question": "離反",
      "answer": "りはん",
      "meaning": "estrangement, alienation, disaffection"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥酔",
      "answer": "でいすい",
      "meaning": "being dead drunk, drunken stupor"
    },
    {
      "question": "性感帯",
      "answer": "せいかんたい",
      "meaning": "erogenous zone"
    },
    {
      "question": "名言",
      "answer": "めいげん",
      "meaning": "wise saying, famous saying"
    },
    {
      "question": "泥臭い",
      "answer": "どろくさい",
      "meaning": "smelling of mud or earth, unrefined, uncouth"
    },
    {
      "question": "討論",
      "answer": "とうろん",
      "meaning": "debate, discussion"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻白む",
      "answer": "はなしらむ,はなじろむ,はなじらむ",
      "meaning": "to look daunted, to look embarrassed, to be disappointed"
    },
    {
      "question": "所用",
      "answer": "しょよう",
      "meaning": "engagement, business, affair, use, need"
    },
    {
      "question": "再起",
      "answer": "さいき",
      "meaning": "comeback, recovery, restoration, rally, reflexive (in grammar)"
    },
    {
      "question": "謂れ",
      "answer": "いわれ",
      "meaning": "reason, cause, history, origin"
    },
    {
      "question": "和気藹々",
      "answer": "わきあいあい",
      "meaning": "harmonious, peaceful, congenial, friendly, happy"
    },
    {
      "question": "終戦",
      "answer": "しゅうせん",
      "meaning": "end of war, cessation of hostilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "滋養",
      "answer": "じよう",
      "meaning": "nourishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "請求書",
      "answer": "せいきゅうしょ",
      "meaning": "bill, job invoice"
    },
    {
      "question": "仇なす",
      "answer": "あだなす",
      "meaning": "to do (someone) a wrong, to do (someone) an ill turn, to take revenge, to resent, to bear a grudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "御する",
      "answer": "ぎょする",
      "meaning": "to drive (e.g. horse, carriage), to control, to manage"
    },
    {
      "question": "具現",
      "answer": "ぐげん",
      "meaning": "incarnation, embodiment, realization, giving concrete form (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "感じ入る",
      "answer": "かんじいる",
      "meaning": "to be impressed, to greatly admire"
    },
    {
      "question": "淡泊",
      "answer": "たんぱく",
      "meaning": "light (color, colour, taste), simple, plain, frank, candid, ingenuous, indifferent"
    },
    {
      "question": "堂に入る",
      "answer": "どうにいる",
      "meaning": "to become an expert, to be master at"
    },
    {
      "question": "入賞",
      "answer": "にゅうしょう",
      "meaning": "winning a prize or place (in a contest)"
    },
    {
      "question": "小休止",
      "answer": "しょうきゅうし",
      "meaning": "short break, breather"
    },
    {
      "question": "換装",
      "answer": "かんそう",
      "meaning": "exchanging parts or equipment to effect a change in performance"
    },
    {
      "question": "建材",
      "answer": "けんざい",
      "meaning": "building material"
    },
    {
      "question": "虎視眈々",
      "answer": "こしたんたん",
      "meaning": "(watching) vigilantly for an opportunity to prey upon, with an eagle eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "哨戒",
      "answer": "しょうかい",
      "meaning": "patrolling (esp. using ships or aircraft)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一座",
      "answer": "いちざ",
      "meaning": "the whole company, the party, all those present, everyone in attendance, attendance (at a gathering)"
    },
    {
      "question": "放映",
      "answer": "ほうえい",
      "meaning": "televising, broadcasting, airing"
    },
    {
      "question": "辛口",
      "answer": "からくち",
      "meaning": "dry taste (e.g. sake, wine), a liking for sake, one who likes sake, salty (taste), harsh, scathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "停留所",
      "answer": "ていりゅうじょ",
      "meaning": "stop (bus, tram, etc.), station, stopping place"
    },
    {
      "question": "透明度",
      "answer": "とうめいど",
      "meaning": "transparency, degree of clearness"
    },
    {
      "question": "斉射",
      "answer": "せいしゃ",
      "meaning": "volley, fusillade"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦時",
      "answer": "せんじ",
      "meaning": "wartime"
    },
    {
      "question": "漁船",
      "answer": "ぎょせん",
      "meaning": "fishing boat"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒素",
      "answer": "どくそ",
      "meaning": "toxin, poisonous substance"
    },
    {
      "question": "競技場",
      "answer": "きょうぎじょう",
      "meaning": "field, sports stadium, arena"
    },
    {
      "question": "家電",
      "answer": "かでん,いえでん",
      "meaning": "consumer electronics, consumer electrical appliances, home telephone, home phone number"
    },
    {
      "question": "外泊",
      "answer": "がいはく",
      "meaning": "staying somewhere else (overnight), spending the night away (e.g. from home), going home (e.g. from"
    },
    {
      "question": "消灯",
      "answer": "しょうとう",
      "meaning": "putting out the light, switching off the light"
    },
    {
      "question": "闘技",
      "answer": "とうぎ",
      "meaning": "competition, contest"
    },
    {
      "question": "不和",
      "answer": "ふわ",
      "meaning": "friction, discord, trouble, dissension, disagreement"
    },
    {
      "question": "育ち盛り",
      "answer": "そだちざかり",
      "meaning": "growth period (in children)"
    },
    {
      "question": "韓国",
      "answer": "かんこく,からくに",
      "meaning": "South Korea, Republic of Korea, Korean Empire (1897-1910), China, Korea"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴",
      "answer": "ぼう",
      "meaning": "violence, force"
    },
    {
      "question": "無駄口",
      "answer": "むだぐち",
      "meaning": "chatter, idle talk"
    },
    {
      "question": "授業料",
      "answer": "じゅぎょうりょう",
      "meaning": "tuition fee, course fee"
    },
    {
      "question": "一足",
      "answer": "いっそく,ひとあし",
      "meaning": "pair (footwear), a step, short distance, short time"
    },
    {
      "question": "神業",
      "answer": "かみわざ,かむわざ,かんわざ",
      "meaning": "divine work, miracle, superhuman feat, Shinto ritual"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝落ち",
      "answer": "ねおち",
      "meaning": "dozing off in the middle of doing something (esp. in an online chat or during an online game), becom"
    },
    {
      "question": "蔑み",
      "answer": "さげすみ",
      "meaning": "contempt"
    },
    {
      "question": "罰当たり",
      "answer": "ばちあたり",
      "meaning": "damned, cursed, accursed"
    },
    {
      "question": "外縁",
      "answer": "がいえん",
      "meaning": "brink, outer edge"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び",
      "answer": "とび",
      "meaning": "flying, leaping, flight, leap, zero, naught, oh, flying fish (esp. the Japanese flying fish, Cypselu"
    },
    {
      "question": "上り",
      "answer": "のぼり",
      "meaning": "ascent, climbing, ascending (path), climb, up-train, train heading toward the starting point of its"
    },
    {
      "question": "櫓",
      "answer": "やぐら,ろ",
      "meaning": "turret, watchtower, high wooden stage, scaffolding, wooden frame (of a kotatsu), yagura, fortress, w"
    },
    {
      "question": "御の字",
      "answer": "おんのじ",
      "meaning": "most satisfactory"
    },
    {
      "question": "異星人",
      "answer": "いせいじん",
      "meaning": "alien (from another planet)"
    },
    {
      "question": "色欲",
      "answer": "しきよく",
      "meaning": "lust, sexual appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "貯蔵",
      "answer": "ちょぞう",
      "meaning": "storage, preservation"
    },
    {
      "question": "主義者",
      "answer": "しゅぎしゃ",
      "meaning": "advocate (of a theory or principle), ideologist, ideologue, -ist (i.e. adherent to a belief system),"
    },
    {
      "question": "糸目",
      "answer": "いとめ",
      "meaning": "fine line, weight of thread, slit-eyed"
    },
    {
      "question": "着付け",
      "answer": "きつけ",
      "meaning": "dressing (esp. in kimono), fitting, helping someone get dressed, outer garment (in kabuki)"
    },
    {
      "question": "参拝",
      "answer": "さんぱい",
      "meaning": "visit to a shrine or temple, paying homage at a shrine or temple"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞紙",
      "answer": "しんぶんし,しんぶんがみ",
      "meaning": "newsprint, newspaper used for wrapping, packing, etc., newspaper"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛇行",
      "answer": "だこう,じゃこう",
      "meaning": "meandering, snaking, zigzagging"
    },
    {
      "question": "未定",
      "answer": "みてい",
      "meaning": "not yet fixed, undecided, pending"
    },
    {
      "question": "送迎",
      "answer": "そうげい",
      "meaning": "seeing off and meeting on return"
    },
    {
      "question": "入門",
      "answer": "にゅうもん",
      "meaning": "entering an institution, beginning training, primer, manual, introduction (to)"
    },
    {
      "question": "問屋",
      "answer": "とんや,といや",
      "meaning": "wholesale store, wholesale dealer, wholesaler"
    },
    {
      "question": "昏睡",
      "answer": "こんすい",
      "meaning": "coma, dead sleep"
    },
    {
      "question": "人身売買",
      "answer": "じんしんばいばい",
      "meaning": "slave trade, white-slave trade, human trafficking"
    },
    {
      "question": "漫然",
      "answer": "まんぜん",
      "meaning": "aimless, rambling, desultory, casual"
    },
    {
      "question": "手繰る",
      "answer": "たぐる",
      "meaning": "to haul in (hand over hand), to pull in, to draw in, to reel in, to trace (history, threads of a sto"
    },
    {
      "question": "半円",
      "answer": "はんえん",
      "meaning": "semicircle"
    },
    {
      "question": "新曲",
      "answer": "しんきょく",
      "meaning": "new (musical) composition, new piece, new song"
    },
    {
      "question": "仔猫",
      "answer": "こねこ",
      "meaning": "kitten, small cat"
    },
    {
      "question": "乱心",
      "answer": "らんしん",
      "meaning": "mental derangement, madness, insanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "掛け持ち",
      "answer": "かけもち",
      "meaning": "holding two or more positions concurrently"
    },
    {
      "question": "風穴",
      "answer": "かざあな,かぜあな,ふうけつ",
      "meaning": "air hole, windhole, ventilator, cave from which cold wind blows"
    },
    {
      "question": "一挙一動",
      "answer": "いっきょいちどう",
      "meaning": "one's every action, every single move"
    },
    {
      "question": "結果論",
      "answer": "けっかろん",
      "meaning": "hindsight-based opinion"
    },
    {
      "question": "磁力",
      "answer": "じりょく",
      "meaning": "magnetism, magnetic force"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄菓子",
      "answer": "だがし",
      "meaning": "cheap sweets"
    },
    {
      "question": "祭典",
      "answer": "さいてん",
      "meaning": "festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "不評",
      "answer": "ふひょう",
      "meaning": "bad reputation, disgrace, unpopularity"
    },
    {
      "question": "序の口",
      "answer": "じょのくち",
      "meaning": "the beginning (as in 'this is only the beginning'), lowest division in sumo"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯痒い",
      "answer": "はがゆい",
      "meaning": "impatient, tantalized, tantalised, irritated, chagrined, chagrinned, vexed"
    },
    {
      "question": "齎す",
      "answer": "もたらす",
      "meaning": "to bring, to take, to bring about"
    },
    {
      "question": "板張り",
      "answer": "いたばり",
      "meaning": "boarding, wooden floor"
    },
    {
      "question": "防波堤",
      "answer": "ぼうはてい",
      "meaning": "breakwater, mole"
    },
    {
      "question": "過失",
      "answer": "かしつ",
      "meaning": "accident (caused by negligence), error, blunder, fault, defect"
    },
    {
      "question": "目の保養",
      "answer": "めのほよう",
      "meaning": "feast for one's eyes"
    },
    {
      "question": "合併",
      "answer": "がっぺい",
      "meaning": "merger (of companies, towns, etc.), combination, union, amalgamation, consolidation, coalition, fusi"
    },
    {
      "question": "食べ歩き",
      "answer": "たべあるき",
      "meaning": "trying the food at various restaurants, eating tour, walking while eating, eating while walking"
    },
    {
      "question": "貯蓄",
      "answer": "ちょちく",
      "meaning": "savings"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩梅",
      "answer": "えんばい,あんばい",
      "meaning": "seasoning, flavour, flavor, serving one's lord well (of a retainer), taste, condition, state, situat"
    },
    {
      "question": "国籍",
      "answer": "こくせき",
      "meaning": "nationality, citizenship, nationality (ship, airplane, etc.), registration, flag"
    },
    {
      "question": "厳然",
      "answer": "げんぜん",
      "meaning": "grave, solemn, stern, authoritative, hard (e.g. fact)"
    },
    {
      "question": "本殿",
      "answer": "ほんでん",
      "meaning": "main shrine, inner sanctuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "究明",
      "answer": "きゅうめい",
      "meaning": "investigation (esp. in academic and scientific contexts)"
    },
    {
      "question": "競馬",
      "answer": "けいば,くらべうま",
      "meaning": "horse racing, traditional horse-racing, originally two horses head-to-head or ten at a time, esp. Ma"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒔く",
      "answer": "まく",
      "meaning": "to sow, to plant, to seed, to sprinkle (gold or silver powder on lacquerware)"
    },
    {
      "question": "超常現象",
      "answer": "ちょうじょうげんしょう",
      "meaning": "supernatural phenomenon, paranormal phenomenon, anomalous phenomenon"
    },
    {
      "question": "広々",
      "answer": "ひろびろ,こうこう",
      "meaning": "extensive, spacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "光速",
      "answer": "こうそく",
      "meaning": "speed of light"
    },
    {
      "question": "八日",
      "answer": "ようか",
      "meaning": "eighth day of the month, eight days"
    },
    {
      "question": "ドイツ語",
      "answer": "ドイツご",
      "meaning": "German (language)"
    },
    {
      "question": "利き腕",
      "answer": "ききうで",
      "meaning": "one's dominant arm"
    },
    {
      "question": "偶に",
      "answer": "たまに",
      "meaning": "occasionally, once in a while, now and then, rarely, seldom"
    },
    {
      "question": "光点",
      "answer": "こうてん",
      "meaning": "luminous point"
    },
    {
      "question": "基礎的",
      "answer": "きそてき",
      "meaning": "fundamental, basic"
    },
    {
      "question": "異母",
      "answer": "いぼ",
      "meaning": "different mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅団",
      "answer": "りょだん",
      "meaning": "brigade"
    },
    {
      "question": "拳骨",
      "answer": "げんこつ",
      "meaning": "(clenched) fist, knuckles"
    },
    {
      "question": "逆行",
      "answer": "ぎゃっこう,ぎゃくこう",
      "meaning": "reverse movement, retrogression, going backwards, moving in the wrong direction, running counter to"
    },
    {
      "question": "哲学的",
      "answer": "てつがくてき",
      "meaning": "philosophical"
    },
    {
      "question": "不似合い",
      "answer": "ふにあい",
      "meaning": "unbecoming, improper, unsuitable, ill-matched, unworthy of"
    },
    {
      "question": "一騎当千",
      "answer": "いっきとうせん",
      "meaning": "being a match for a thousand, being a mighty warrior (combatant, player)"
    },
    {
      "question": "喧伝",
      "answer": "けんでん",
      "meaning": "spreading around (news, etc.), talking about widely"
    },
    {
      "question": "駐在",
      "answer": "ちゅうざい",
      "meaning": "residence, stay, (job) posting, being stationed (overseas, etc.), residential police box, residentia"
    },
    {
      "question": "突貫",
      "answer": "とっかん",
      "meaning": "charging (at the enemy) with a shout, rush, rushing (an activity), working at full speed, penetratio"
    },
    {
      "question": "不発",
      "answer": "ふはつ",
      "meaning": "misfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗物",
      "answer": "ぞくぶつ",
      "meaning": "worldly-minded person, materialist, uncultured person, philistine, vulgar person, snob"
    },
    {
      "question": "疑り深い",
      "answer": "うたぐりぶかい",
      "meaning": "doubting, distrustful, incredulous, suspicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "後期",
      "answer": "こうき",
      "meaning": "latter period, second half, late stage, third trimester, second semester"
    },
    {
      "question": "狭量",
      "answer": "きょうりょう",
      "meaning": "narrow-minded, intolerant, petty"
    },
    {
      "question": "召還",
      "answer": "しょうかん",
      "meaning": "recall (esp. of an envoy or an ambassador), calling someone back, summons (home)"
    },
    {
      "question": "切り株",
      "answer": "きりかぶ",
      "meaning": "stump, stubble"
    },
    {
      "question": "心理学",
      "answer": "しんりがく",
      "meaning": "psychology"
    },
    {
      "question": "諸島",
      "answer": "しょとう",
      "meaning": "archipelago, group of islands"
    },
    {
      "question": "家庭科",
      "answer": "かていか",
      "meaning": "home economics"
    },
    {
      "question": "赤裸々",
      "answer": "せきらら",
      "meaning": "naked, nude, unvarnished (e.g. truth), plain (e.g. fact), frank, candid, outspoken"
    },
    {
      "question": "自腹",
      "answer": "じばら",
      "meaning": "paying one's own way"
    },
    {
      "question": "一門",
      "answer": "いちもん",
      "meaning": "family, clan, kin, sect, school, adherents, followers, disciples, group of related sumo stables"
    },
    {
      "question": "一騎",
      "answer": "いっき",
      "meaning": "one horseman"
    },
    {
      "question": "有料",
      "answer": "ゆうりょう",
      "meaning": "fee-charging, paid, not free, toll road"
    },
    {
      "question": "愚民",
      "answer": "ぐみん",
      "meaning": "ignorant people"
    },
    {
      "question": "混成",
      "answer": "こんせい",
      "meaning": "mixed (e.g. team, chorus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "月末",
      "answer": "げつまつ,つきずえ",
      "meaning": "end of the month"
    },
    {
      "question": "属",
      "answer": "ぞく",
      "meaning": "genus, generic"
    },
    {
      "question": "習わし",
      "answer": "ならわし",
      "meaning": "custom, habit, customary practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "無敗",
      "answer": "むはい",
      "meaning": "undefeated"
    },
    {
      "question": "現わす",
      "answer": "あらわす",
      "meaning": "to represent, to signify, to stand for, to reveal, to show, to display, to express, to make widely k"
    },
    {
      "question": "理系",
      "answer": "りけい",
      "meaning": "science"
    },
    {
      "question": "間が悪い",
      "answer": "まがわるい",
      "meaning": "embarrassed, awkward, unlucky, inopportune"
    },
    {
      "question": "反比例",
      "answer": "はんぴれい",
      "meaning": "inverse proportion"
    },
    {
      "question": "手荷物",
      "answer": "てにもつ",
      "meaning": "hand luggage, hand baggage"
    },
    {
      "question": "青山",
      "answer": "せいざん,あおやま",
      "meaning": "lush mountain, green mountain, grave, burial place"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕度",
      "answer": "したく",
      "meaning": "preparation, arrangements"
    },
    {
      "question": "自家製",
      "answer": "じかせい",
      "meaning": "homemade"
    },
    {
      "question": "倫理的",
      "answer": "りんりてき",
      "meaning": "ethical"
    },
    {
      "question": "影が差す",
      "answer": "かげがさす",
      "meaning": "to cast a shadow, to appear, to loom (of a threat, etc.), to manifest (of symptoms, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "騒乱",
      "answer": "そうらん",
      "meaning": "disturbance, riot, mayhem"
    },
    {
      "question": "固辞",
      "answer": "こじ",
      "meaning": "firm refusal"
    },
    {
      "question": "起す",
      "answer": "おこす",
      "meaning": "to raise, to raise up, to set up, to pick up, to wake, to wake up, to waken, to awaken, to cause, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "区分",
      "answer": "くぶん",
      "meaning": "division, section, demarcation, partition, segmentation, subdivision, (traffic) lane, compartment, c"
    },
    {
      "question": "食らわす",
      "answer": "くらわす",
      "meaning": "to make someone eat, to deal (a blow), to play (a trick)"
    },
    {
      "question": "固め",
      "answer": "かため",
      "meaning": "hardening, fortifying, pledge, vow, defense, defence, guarding, hardness, firmness"
    },
    {
      "question": "口汚い",
      "answer": "くちぎたない",
      "meaning": "foul-mouthed, abusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "日持ち",
      "answer": "ひもち",
      "meaning": "length of time which food products will keep, to keep a long time"
    },
    {
      "question": "催し物",
      "answer": "もよおしもの,もようしもの",
      "meaning": "(program of) entertainments, special events, exhibitions, amusements, attractions"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹っ切る",
      "answer": "ふっきる",
      "meaning": "to get over, to forget"
    },
    {
      "question": "尤も",
      "answer": "もっとも,もとも",
      "meaning": "most, extremely, but then, although, though, reasonable, natural, just"
    },
    {
      "question": "励み",
      "answer": "はげみ",
      "meaning": "(act of) encouragement, stimulus, incentive"
    },
    {
      "question": "注力",
      "answer": "ちゅうりょく",
      "meaning": "pouring one's energy into, focusing one's efforts on, concentrating on, committing oneself to"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガラス窓",
      "answer": "ガラスまど",
      "meaning": "glass window"
    },
    {
      "question": "前座",
      "answer": "ぜんざ",
      "meaning": "opening performance, opening act, curtain raiser, minor performer, minor storyteller, subordinate pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "度し難い",
      "answer": "どしがたい",
      "meaning": "beyond help, past salvation, incorrigible, irredeemable"
    },
    {
      "question": "悪運",
      "answer": "あくうん",
      "meaning": "undeserved good luck, luck of the devil, dumb luck, bad luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "吉報",
      "answer": "きっぽう",
      "meaning": "good news"
    },
    {
      "question": "豆粒",
      "answer": "まめつぶ",
      "meaning": "speck"
    },
    {
      "question": "煮詰まる",
      "answer": "につまる",
      "meaning": "to be boiled down, to come to a standstill, to reach an impasse, to approach a conclusion (of a disc"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜怒哀楽",
      "answer": "きどあいらく",
      "meaning": "human emotions (joy, anger, grief and pleasure)"
    },
    {
      "question": "観葉植物",
      "answer": "かんようしょくぶつ",
      "meaning": "decorative plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "方向音痴",
      "answer": "ほうこうおんち",
      "meaning": "(person with) no sense of direction, poor sense of locality"
    },
    {
      "question": "言い辛い",
      "answer": "いいづらい",
      "meaning": "difficult to speak about"
    },
    {
      "question": "式場",
      "answer": "しきじょう",
      "meaning": "ceremonial hall (e.g. wedding, funeral), hall for ceremonies, place of ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "阿",
      "answer": "くま,あ",
      "meaning": "corner, nook, recess, shade, shadow, dark area, dark circles (under the eyes), dark rings, shading,"
    },
    {
      "question": "避難民",
      "answer": "ひなんみん",
      "meaning": "evacuees, displaced persons, refugees"
    },
    {
      "question": "指向性",
      "answer": "しこうせい",
      "meaning": "directionality, directivity"
    },
    {
      "question": "書き残す",
      "answer": "かきのこす",
      "meaning": "to leave a note or document behind, to leave half-written, to leave out"
    },
    {
      "question": "極太",
      "answer": "ごくぶと",
      "meaning": "very thick, something extremely thick, thick, heavy thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "計器",
      "answer": "けいき",
      "meaning": "meter, gauge"
    },
    {
      "question": "流水",
      "answer": "りゅうすい",
      "meaning": "running water, stream"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い場",
      "answer": "あらいば",
      "meaning": "washing place (e.g. for laundry or tableware), place for washing oneself in a bathroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄華",
      "answer": "えいが",
      "meaning": "prosperity, glory, splendour, splendor, majesty, luxury"
    },
    {
      "question": "奇特",
      "answer": "きとく,きどく",
      "meaning": "praiseworthy, commendable, benevolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "不透明",
      "answer": "ふとうめい",
      "meaning": "opaque, obscure, murky, turbid, opacity, obscurity, unclear, unpredictable, uncertain"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶世",
      "answer": "ぜっせい",
      "meaning": "peerless, matchless, unrivaled, unrivalled, unequaled, unequalled, unsurpassed"
    },
    {
      "question": "自由奔放",
      "answer": "じゆうほんぽう",
      "meaning": "free and uncontrolled, behaving with abandon, freewheeling"
    },
    {
      "question": "極悪",
      "answer": "ごくあく",
      "meaning": "heinous"
    },
    {
      "question": "球状",
      "answer": "きゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "shape of a globe, globe shape, spherical"
    },
    {
      "question": "便宜上",
      "answer": "べんぎじょう",
      "meaning": "for convenience, as a matter of convenience"
    },
    {
      "question": "大晦日",
      "answer": "おおみそか",
      "meaning": "New Year's Eve, December 31"
    },
    {
      "question": "注",
      "answer": "ちゅう",
      "meaning": "annotation, explanatory note, comment"
    },
    {
      "question": "削減",
      "answer": "さくげん",
      "meaning": "cut, reduction, curtailment"
    },
    {
      "question": "さん付け",
      "answer": "さんづけ",
      "meaning": "attaching the polite suffix '-san' to somebody's name"
    },
    {
      "question": "極意",
      "answer": "ごくい",
      "meaning": "innermost secrets (of an art or skill), mysteries, essence, heart"
    },
    {
      "question": "纏",
      "answer": "まとい",
      "meaning": "battle standard decorated with hanging strips of paper or leather, fireman's standard (Edo period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "低学年",
      "answer": "ていがくねん",
      "meaning": "lower grades of primary school (first, second, and sometimes third grades)"
    },
    {
      "question": "塗り込む",
      "answer": "ぬりこむ",
      "meaning": "to paint over heavily, to plaster up"
    },
    {
      "question": "盲目的",
      "answer": "もうもくてき",
      "meaning": "blind (devotion, faith, etc.), reckless"
    },
    {
      "question": "釣り竿",
      "answer": "つりざお",
      "meaning": "fishing rod"
    },
    {
      "question": "袋叩き",
      "answer": "ふくろだたき",
      "meaning": "beating someone up by ganging up on them, facing a barrage of criticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "口先",
      "answer": "くちさき",
      "meaning": "lip service, mere words, professions, lips, mouth, snout, proboscis"
    },
    {
      "question": "新聞記者",
      "answer": "しんぶんきしゃ",
      "meaning": "newspaper reporter, print journalist"
    },
    {
      "question": "神域",
      "answer": "しんいき",
      "meaning": "Shinto shrine precincts, holy precincts, sanctuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "手馴れる",
      "answer": "てなれる",
      "meaning": "to get used (to), to get familiar with, to get skillful with"
    },
    {
      "question": "継承者",
      "answer": "けいしょうしゃ",
      "meaning": "successor"
    },
    {
      "question": "作り手",
      "answer": "つくりて",
      "meaning": "maker, builder, creator, tenant farmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "半目",
      "answer": "はんめ,はんもく",
      "meaning": "half-open eyes, half a point (esp. in go)"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱皮",
      "answer": "だっぴ",
      "meaning": "ecdysis, shedding (of skin), sloughing, molting, moulting, casting off, freeing oneself, breaking wi"
    },
    {
      "question": "置き土産",
      "answer": "おきみやげ",
      "meaning": "parting gift, remembrance, aftereffect"
    },
    {
      "question": "覇権",
      "answer": "はけん",
      "meaning": "hegemony"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮初め",
      "answer": "かりそめ",
      "meaning": "temporary, transient, trifling, slight, negligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "優",
      "answer": "やさ,ゆう",
      "meaning": "gentle, affectionate, Excellent (grade), A, superiority, excellence, graceful, elegant, skillful"
    },
    {
      "question": "万死",
      "answer": "ばんし",
      "meaning": "certain death"
    },
    {
      "question": "近所迷惑",
      "answer": "きんじょめいわく",
      "meaning": "neighborhood nuisance, neighbourhood nuisance"
    },
    {
      "question": "砲塔",
      "answer": "ほうとう",
      "meaning": "gun turret"
    },
    {
      "question": "園内",
      "answer": "えんない",
      "meaning": "inside the garden (park)"
    },
    {
      "question": "節目",
      "answer": "ふしめ",
      "meaning": "turning point, critical juncture, knot (in a tree, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "耐え忍ぶ",
      "answer": "たえしのぶ",
      "meaning": "to put up with, to endure, to bear patiently"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦闘員",
      "answer": "せんとういん",
      "meaning": "combatant, fighter"
    },
    {
      "question": "腱",
      "answer": "けん",
      "meaning": "tendon"
    },
    {
      "question": "小島",
      "answer": "こじま,しょうとう,おじま",
      "meaning": "small island, islet"
    },
    {
      "question": "八百屋",
      "answer": "やおや",
      "meaning": "greengrocer, fruit and vegetable shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き倒れ",
      "answer": "いきだおれ,ゆきだおれ",
      "meaning": "person collapsed and dying (dead) in the street"
    },
    {
      "question": "桔梗",
      "answer": "ききょう",
      "meaning": "Chinese bellflower (Platycodon grandiflorus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "盛り込む",
      "answer": "もりこむ",
      "meaning": "to incorporate, to include, to fill (a vessel) with"
    },
    {
      "question": "炭化",
      "answer": "たんか",
      "meaning": "carbonization, carbonisation"
    },
    {
      "question": "野草",
      "answer": "のぐさ,やそう",
      "meaning": "wild grasses, field grass, wildflowers"
    },
    {
      "question": "主たる",
      "answer": "しゅたる",
      "meaning": "main, principal, major"
    },
    {
      "question": "前金",
      "answer": "まえきん,ぜんきん",
      "meaning": "advance payment, money paid in advance"
    },
    {
      "question": "藍",
      "answer": "あい",
      "meaning": "dyer's knotweed (Persicaria tinctoria, used to produce indigo dye), indigo (dye), indigo (colour)"
    },
    {
      "question": "青少年",
      "answer": "せいしょうねん",
      "meaning": "youth, young person"
    },
    {
      "question": "翁",
      "answer": "おう,おきな",
      "meaning": "old man, venerable gentleman, venerable, old, father"
    },
    {
      "question": "長命",
      "answer": "ちょうめい",
      "meaning": "long life"
    },
    {
      "question": "手懐ける",
      "answer": "てなずける,てなづける",
      "meaning": "to tame, to win over"
    },
    {
      "question": "柔",
      "answer": "やわ,やわら,じゅう",
      "meaning": "soft, fragile, weak, poorly built, insubstantial, judo, jujutsu, softness, gentleness, weakness"
    },
    {
      "question": "広島",
      "answer": "ひろしま",
      "meaning": "Hiroshima (city, prefecture)"
    },
    {
      "question": "些事",
      "answer": "さじ",
      "meaning": "something small, something petty, trifle"
    },
    {
      "question": "踏み抜く",
      "answer": "ふみぬく",
      "meaning": "to tread (a nail) into the sole of one's foot, to tread through (the floor)"
    },
    {
      "question": "知らん顔",
      "answer": "しらんかお",
      "meaning": "feigned ignorance, pretending not to recognize (somebody), unconcerned air, indifference"
    },
    {
      "question": "木目",
      "answer": "きめ,もくめ",
      "meaning": "texture (e.g. skin, fabric), grain (e.g. wood), detail, grain (of wood)"
    },
    {
      "question": "懐妊",
      "answer": "かいにん",
      "meaning": "pregnancy, conception"
    },
    {
      "question": "戦時中",
      "answer": "せんじちゅう",
      "meaning": "during the war"
    },
    {
      "question": "楼",
      "answer": "ろう",
      "meaning": "tower, tall building, belvedere, turret, lookout, watchtower, brothel"
    },
    {
      "question": "向こう岸",
      "answer": "むこうぎし",
      "meaning": "opposite bank, farther shore"
    },
    {
      "question": "母君",
      "answer": "ははぎみ",
      "meaning": "mother"
    },
    {
      "question": "集大成",
      "answer": "しゅうたいせい",
      "meaning": "(large) compilation, culmination (of hard work)"
    },
    {
      "question": "品性",
      "answer": "ひんせい",
      "meaning": "character"
    },
    {
      "question": "予行演習",
      "answer": "よこうえんしゅう",
      "meaning": "dry run, rehearsal"
    },
    {
      "question": "着崩す",
      "answer": "きくずす",
      "meaning": "to wear (formal clothing) in a casual fashion"
    },
    {
      "question": "良家",
      "answer": "りょうけ,りょうか",
      "meaning": "good family, respectable family, decent family"
    },
    {
      "question": "転じて",
      "answer": "てんじて",
      "meaning": "by the way, meanwhile, on the other hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "今し方",
      "answer": "いましがた",
      "meaning": "a moment ago, just now"
    },
    {
      "question": "言伝",
      "answer": "ことづて",
      "meaning": "(oral) message, declaration, hearsay, rumour, rumor"
    },
    {
      "question": "今一つ",
      "answer": "いまひとつ",
      "meaning": "one more, another, the other, not quite, not very good, lacking"
    },
    {
      "question": "鈍痛",
      "answer": "どんつう",
      "meaning": "dull pain"
    },
    {
      "question": "後妻",
      "answer": "ごさい,こうさい,うわなり",
      "meaning": "second wife, later wife, concubine, jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "保温",
      "answer": "ほおん",
      "meaning": "retaining warmth, keeping heat in, heat insulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝込み",
      "answer": "ねこみ,ねごみ",
      "meaning": "asleep (in bed), sick in bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "連れ添う",
      "answer": "つれそう",
      "meaning": "to become a couple, to be man and wife, to be married to"
    },
    {
      "question": "刺し",
      "answer": "さし",
      "meaning": "grain thief, sharpened tube for testing rice in bags, sashimi (sliced raw fish), stabbing, piercing,"
    },
    {
      "question": "共用",
      "answer": "きょうよう",
      "meaning": "common use, communal use, sharing"
    },
    {
      "question": "川原",
      "answer": "かわら",
      "meaning": "dry riverbed, river beach"
    },
    {
      "question": "穴埋め",
      "answer": "あなうめ",
      "meaning": "filling (up) a hole, filling in (for a gap, vacancy, etc.), stopgap, filler (e.g. article), making u"
    },
    {
      "question": "門扉",
      "answer": "もんぴ",
      "meaning": "door(s) of a gate"
    },
    {
      "question": "金剛",
      "answer": "こんごう",
      "meaning": "vajra (indestructible substance), diamond, adamantine, thunderbolt, Indra's weapon, Buddhist symbol"
    },
    {
      "question": "除け",
      "answer": "よけ",
      "meaning": "protection, repellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "植木",
      "answer": "うえき",
      "meaning": "garden shrubs, trees, potted plant"
    },
    {
      "question": "鏡台",
      "answer": "きょうだい",
      "meaning": "dresser"
    },
    {
      "question": "居",
      "answer": "きょ,い",
      "meaning": "residence, being (somewhere), sitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "貨物",
      "answer": "かもつ,かぶつ",
      "meaning": "cargo, freight, money or assets"
    },
    {
      "question": "万力",
      "answer": "まんりき",
      "meaning": "vise, jack, capstan"
    },
    {
      "question": "眉唾",
      "answer": "まゆつば",
      "meaning": "dubious tale, cock-and-bull story, questionable information, taking care not to be fooled"
    },
    {
      "question": "重役",
      "answer": "じゅうやく,おもやく",
      "meaning": "(company) director, executive, top management, important post, role with heavy responsibilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬剤",
      "answer": "やくざい",
      "meaning": "medicine, drug, chemical"
    },
    {
      "question": "目を配る",
      "answer": "めをくばる",
      "meaning": "to keep an eye on, to keep a watchful eye on"
    },
    {
      "question": "直腸",
      "answer": "ちょくちょう",
      "meaning": "rectum"
    },
    {
      "question": "整形",
      "answer": "せいけい",
      "meaning": "orthopedics, plastic surgery, cosmetic surgery, smoothing (bursty traffic, etc.), shaping, fairing"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕方無い",
      "answer": "しかたない",
      "meaning": "there's no (other) way, cannot be helped, unavoidable, inevitable, (there's) nothing one can do, hav"
    },
    {
      "question": "奏者",
      "answer": "そうしゃ",
      "meaning": "instrumentalist, player"
    },
    {
      "question": "唄う",
      "answer": "うたう",
      "meaning": "to sing, to sing (one's praises in a poem, etc.), to compose a poem, to recite a poem"
    },
    {
      "question": "条例",
      "answer": "じょうれい",
      "meaning": "regulations, rules, (local) regulation, ordinance, bylaw, law"
    },
    {
      "question": "盃",
      "answer": "さかずき,さかづき,はい",
      "meaning": "sake cup, cup for alcoholic beverages, counter for cupfuls, bowlfuls, spoonfuls, etc., counter for b"
    },
    {
      "question": "割愛",
      "answer": "かつあい",
      "meaning": "omitting, leaving out, sparing, giving something up reluctantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "複雑怪奇",
      "answer": "ふくざつかいき",
      "meaning": "complicated and mysterious"
    },
    {
      "question": "新任",
      "answer": "しんにん",
      "meaning": "newly appointed, inaugural"
    },
    {
      "question": "登り",
      "answer": "のぼり",
      "meaning": "ascent, climbing, ascending (path), climb, upbound (esp. toward Tokyo)"
    },
    {
      "question": "免罪符",
      "answer": "めんざいふ",
      "meaning": "indulgence (esp. in the Catholic Church), excuse, justification, rationalization"
    },
    {
      "question": "動脈",
      "answer": "どうみゃく",
      "meaning": "artery"
    },
    {
      "question": "共倒れ",
      "answer": "ともだおれ",
      "meaning": "falling together, mutual destruction, joint bankruptcy"
    },
    {
      "question": "曝す",
      "answer": "さらす,さぼす",
      "meaning": "to expose (to the sun, public, danger, etc.), to bleach, to refine, to rinse (vegetables), to soak,"
    },
    {
      "question": "私共",
      "answer": "わたくしども,わたしども",
      "meaning": "we, us, I, me, my store (business, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "作中",
      "answer": "さくちゅう",
      "meaning": "within the story (of a book, play, movie, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "喪服",
      "answer": "もふく",
      "meaning": "mourning dress"
    },
    {
      "question": "吹かす",
      "answer": "ふかす",
      "meaning": "to smoke (a cigarette), to behave as ..., to accelerate, to rev up"
    },
    {
      "question": "手振り",
      "answer": "てぶり",
      "meaning": "(hand) gesture, movement of the hand"
    },
    {
      "question": "実地",
      "answer": "じっち",
      "meaning": "practice (as opposed to theory), actual practice, actual site, (at) the scene, (on) the spot"
    },
    {
      "question": "煩う",
      "answer": "わずらう",
      "meaning": "to be ill, to suffer from, to worry about, to be concerned about, to have trouble doing ..., to be u"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯軋り",
      "answer": "はぎしり",
      "meaning": "involuntary nocturnal tooth grinding, bruxism, grinding one's teeth out of anger or vexation"
    },
    {
      "question": "連敗",
      "answer": "れんぱい",
      "meaning": "consecutive defeats, series of defeats"
    },
    {
      "question": "宅配",
      "answer": "たくはい",
      "meaning": "home delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰唇",
      "answer": "いんしん",
      "meaning": "the labium, labia"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒐集",
      "answer": "しゅうしゅう",
      "meaning": "collecting, accumulating, gathering, collection (of art, stamps, insects, etc.), garbage collection,"
    },
    {
      "question": "大舞台",
      "answer": "おおぶたい,だいぶたい",
      "meaning": "large stage, grand stage, the big stage, grand setting"
    },
    {
      "question": "昔々",
      "answer": "むかしむかし",
      "meaning": "long ago, once upon a time"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸焼け",
      "answer": "むねやけ,むなやけ",
      "meaning": "heartburn, sour stomach"
    },
    {
      "question": "山分け",
      "answer": "やまわけ",
      "meaning": "equal division (of profits, prize money, etc.), equal split"
    },
    {
      "question": "目処",
      "answer": "めど",
      "meaning": "aim, goal, prospect, outlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "高望み",
      "answer": "たかのぞみ",
      "meaning": "aiming too high"
    },
    {
      "question": "武器庫",
      "answer": "ぶきこ",
      "meaning": "armory, armoury, ordnance department"
    },
    {
      "question": "休止",
      "answer": "きゅうし",
      "meaning": "pause, cessation, rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "補償",
      "answer": "ほしょう",
      "meaning": "compensation, reparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "存在理由",
      "answer": "そんざいりゆう",
      "meaning": "reason for being, raison d'être"
    },
    {
      "question": "融ける",
      "answer": "とける",
      "meaning": "to melt, to thaw, to fuse, to dissolve"
    },
    {
      "question": "訛り",
      "answer": "なまり",
      "meaning": "accent (of one's speech), dialect, provincialism, patois, corrupted form (e.g. of word), mispronunci"
    },
    {
      "question": "証明書",
      "answer": "しょうめいしょ",
      "meaning": "certificate (usually of proof of something), credentials"
    },
    {
      "question": "初仕事",
      "answer": "はつしごと",
      "meaning": "first day returning to work after the New Years holiday, first task at a new job, newcomer's first j"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁煙",
      "answer": "きんえん",
      "meaning": "abstaining from smoking, quitting smoking, No Smoking!, Smoking Prohibited!"
    },
    {
      "question": "船酔い",
      "answer": "ふなよい",
      "meaning": "seasickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "大商人",
      "answer": "おおあきんど",
      "meaning": "major dealer, wealthy merchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "景",
      "answer": "かげ,けい",
      "meaning": "shadow, silhouette, figure, shape, reflection, image, ominous sign, light (stars, moon), trace, shad"
    },
    {
      "question": "烙印",
      "answer": "らくいん",
      "meaning": "brand, mark"
    },
    {
      "question": "狂暴",
      "answer": "きょうぼう",
      "meaning": "rage, frenzy"
    },
    {
      "question": "魔除け",
      "answer": "まよけ",
      "meaning": "charm against evil spirits, talisman, amulet"
    },
    {
      "question": "大助かり",
      "answer": "おおだすかり",
      "meaning": "great help"
    },
    {
      "question": "鏡面",
      "answer": "きょうめん",
      "meaning": "mirror surface, lens surface"
    },
    {
      "question": "継ぎ目",
      "answer": "つぎめ",
      "meaning": "joint, seam, joining point"
    },
    {
      "question": "大名",
      "answer": "だいみょう",
      "meaning": "daimyo (Japanese feudal lord)"
    },
    {
      "question": "集計",
      "answer": "しゅうけい",
      "meaning": "totalization, totalisation, aggregation, tally (e.g. of votes), adding up, summing up"
    },
    {
      "question": "度数",
      "answer": "どすう,たびかず",
      "meaning": "frequency, number of times, incidence, degree (e.g. temperature), strength (e.g. alcohol, lens, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "土木",
      "answer": "どぼく",
      "meaning": "engineering works, civil engineering, public works"
    },
    {
      "question": "傍受",
      "answer": "ぼうじゅ",
      "meaning": "interception, monitoring, tapping"
    },
    {
      "question": "買い付け",
      "answer": "かいつけ",
      "meaning": "buying, purchasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "顔付き",
      "answer": "かおつき",
      "meaning": "(outward) looks, features, face, countenance, expression"
    },
    {
      "question": "養分",
      "answer": "ようぶん",
      "meaning": "nourishment, nutrient"
    },
    {
      "question": "誰何",
      "answer": "すいか",
      "meaning": "challenging (an unknown person), asking a person's identity"
    },
    {
      "question": "木片",
      "answer": "もくへん,こっぱ",
      "meaning": "block (of wood), chip, splinter, wood chip, worthless thing, worthless person"
    },
    {
      "question": "天文",
      "answer": "てんもん,てんぶん",
      "meaning": "astronomy, Tenbun era (1532.7.29-1555.10.23)"
    },
    {
      "question": "線香",
      "answer": "せんこう",
      "meaning": "incense stick"
    },
    {
      "question": "神楽",
      "answer": "かぐら",
      "meaning": "ancient Shinto music and dancing"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠕動",
      "answer": "ぜんどう",
      "meaning": "vermiculation, peristalsis, crawling like a worm"
    },
    {
      "question": "牽引",
      "answer": "けんいん",
      "meaning": "traction, towing, hauling, pulling, drawing, driving (e.g. economic growth)"
    },
    {
      "question": "過",
      "answer": "か",
      "meaning": "surplus-, excess-, over-, per- (chemical with more of a certain element than found in other compound"
    },
    {
      "question": "遺恨",
      "answer": "いこん",
      "meaning": "grudge, ill will, enmity"
    },
    {
      "question": "被告",
      "answer": "ひこく",
      "meaning": "defendant, the accused"
    },
    {
      "question": "級友",
      "answer": "きゅうゆう",
      "meaning": "classmate"
    },
    {
      "question": "仁",
      "answer": "じん,にん",
      "meaning": "benevolence (esp. as a virtue of Confucianism), consideration, compassion, humanity, charity, human,"
    },
    {
      "question": "槍術",
      "answer": "そうじゅつ",
      "meaning": "spearmanship"
    },
    {
      "question": "通帳",
      "answer": "つうちょう",
      "meaning": "passbook, bankbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "子守唄",
      "answer": "こもりうた",
      "meaning": "lullaby"
    },
    {
      "question": "総統",
      "answer": "そうとう",
      "meaning": "supreme ruler, generalissimo, president (of Taiwan), führer, fuehrer"
    },
    {
      "question": "賭博",
      "answer": "とばく",
      "meaning": "gambling"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗜好品",
      "answer": "しこうひん",
      "meaning": "luxury grocery item (e.g. alcohol, coffee, tea, tobacco), indulgence, something consumed for taste o"
    },
    {
      "question": "実装",
      "answer": "じっそう",
      "meaning": "implementation (e.g. of a feature), installation (of equipment), mounting, packaging"
    },
    {
      "question": "返品",
      "answer": "へんぴん",
      "meaning": "returned goods, returning purchased goods"
    },
    {
      "question": "黒曜石",
      "answer": "こくようせき",
      "meaning": "obsidian"
    },
    {
      "question": "課程",
      "answer": "かてい",
      "meaning": "course, curriculum"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮力",
      "answer": "ふりょく",
      "meaning": "buoyancy, floating power"
    },
    {
      "question": "宅配便",
      "answer": "たくはいびん",
      "meaning": "express home delivery service, express home delivery parcel (box, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "三国",
      "answer": "さんごく",
      "meaning": "three countries, Japan, China and India, Japan, Korea and China, all the world, Three Kingdoms (in C"
    },
    {
      "question": "申し入れ",
      "answer": "もうしいれ",
      "meaning": "proposal, offer, report, proposition, notice, request"
    },
    {
      "question": "全面戦争",
      "answer": "ぜんめんせんそう",
      "meaning": "total war, all-out war"
    },
    {
      "question": "供養",
      "answer": "くよう",
      "meaning": "memorial service for the dead, holding a service"
    },
    {
      "question": "顎髭",
      "answer": "あごひげ",
      "meaning": "beard (esp. on the chin), goatee"
    },
    {
      "question": "立て直し",
      "answer": "たてなおし",
      "meaning": "revamping, reshaping, rearranging, reorganizing"
    },
    {
      "question": "語学",
      "answer": "ごがく",
      "meaning": "study of foreign languages, linguistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "異音",
      "answer": "いおん",
      "meaning": "allophone, strange noise"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪玉",
      "answer": "ゆきだま",
      "meaning": "snowball"
    },
    {
      "question": "子飼い",
      "answer": "こがい",
      "meaning": "rearing from infancy, training from an early age (e.g. an apprentice), teaching from an early stage"
    },
    {
      "question": "箱入り",
      "answer": "はこいり",
      "meaning": "cased, boxed, precious, cherished, girl who has been sheltered from the world, one's special talent"
    },
    {
      "question": "時計台",
      "answer": "とけいだい",
      "meaning": "clock tower"
    },
    {
      "question": "患部",
      "answer": "かんぶ",
      "meaning": "affected part, diseased part, wound"
    },
    {
      "question": "悼む",
      "answer": "いたむ",
      "meaning": "to grieve over, to mourn, to lament"
    },
    {
      "question": "客層",
      "answer": "きゃくそう",
      "meaning": "clientele, customer stratum"
    },
    {
      "question": "面倒見",
      "answer": "めんどうみ",
      "meaning": "taking care of someone"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨水",
      "answer": "あまみず,うすい",
      "meaning": "rain water, 'rain water' solar term (approx. February 19)"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝礼",
      "answer": "ちょうれい",
      "meaning": "morning assembly (at a company, school, etc.), morning gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "電動",
      "answer": "でんどう",
      "meaning": "electric"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘密結社",
      "answer": "ひみつけっしゃ",
      "meaning": "secret society"
    },
    {
      "question": "忍法",
      "answer": "にんぽう",
      "meaning": "ninja arts"
    },
    {
      "question": "料亭",
      "answer": "りょうてい",
      "meaning": "ryotei, traditional Japanese restaurant (esp. a luxurious one)"
    },
    {
      "question": "個所",
      "answer": "かしょ",
      "meaning": "place, point, part, spot, area, passage, portion, counter for places, parts, passages, etc."
    },
    {
      "question": "捻り",
      "answer": "ひねり",
      "meaning": "twist, spin, ingenuity, sophistication (e.g. of writing style), wrapped offering (of money), twistin"
    },
    {
      "question": "我こそは",
      "answer": "われこそは",
      "meaning": "I, as for me"
    },
    {
      "question": "揺るぎ",
      "answer": "ゆるぎ",
      "meaning": "shaking, swaying"
    },
    {
      "question": "植木鉢",
      "answer": "うえきばち",
      "meaning": "flowerpot, plant pot"
    },
    {
      "question": "蒸れる",
      "answer": "むれる",
      "meaning": "to be stuffy, to moulder, to molder"
    },
    {
      "question": "欲深い",
      "answer": "よくぶかい",
      "meaning": "greedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "排する",
      "answer": "はいする",
      "meaning": "to push aside, to overcome (e.g. difficulties), to reject, to align, to put in order, to push open"
    },
    {
      "question": "純愛",
      "answer": "じゅんあい",
      "meaning": "pure love"
    },
    {
      "question": "金貸し",
      "answer": "かねかし",
      "meaning": "moneylending, moneylender"
    },
    {
      "question": "豊作",
      "answer": "ほうさく",
      "meaning": "abundant harvest, bumper crop"
    },
    {
      "question": "破門",
      "answer": "はもん",
      "meaning": "expulsion (of a pupil), excommunication, anathema"
    },
    {
      "question": "塩焼き",
      "answer": "しおやき",
      "meaning": "grilling (fish) with salt, broiling with salt, boiling seawater to get salt"
    },
    {
      "question": "洋食",
      "answer": "ようしょく",
      "meaning": "Western cooking, Western-style meal, Western-style food, Japanized Western cuisine"
    },
    {
      "question": "神子",
      "answer": "みこ",
      "meaning": "miko, shrine maiden, young girl or woman (trad. an unmarried virgin) who assists priests at shrines,"
    },
    {
      "question": "局員",
      "answer": "きょくいん",
      "meaning": "clerk, (bureau, post-office) staff"
    },
    {
      "question": "話半分",
      "answer": "はなしはんぶん",
      "meaning": "taking a story with a grain of salt, discounting half the story"
    },
    {
      "question": "発電",
      "answer": "はつでん",
      "meaning": "generation (e.g. power), sending a telegram, telegraphing"
    },
    {
      "question": "東西南北",
      "answer": "とうざいなんぼく",
      "meaning": "east, west, south and north"
    },
    {
      "question": "見積もり",
      "answer": "みつもり",
      "meaning": "estimate, estimation, valuation, quotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "全幅",
      "answer": "ぜんぷく",
      "meaning": "full, wholehearted, utmost, all, every, overall width"
    },
    {
      "question": "染",
      "answer": "そめ",
      "meaning": "dyeing, printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗜虐的",
      "answer": "しぎゃくてき",
      "meaning": "sadistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "霊薬",
      "answer": "れいやく",
      "meaning": "miraculous medicine, miracle drug, wonder drug"
    },
    {
      "question": "気体",
      "answer": "きたい",
      "meaning": "gas, vapour, vapor, gaseous body"
    },
    {
      "question": "炊飯器",
      "answer": "すいはんき",
      "meaning": "rice cooker"
    },
    {
      "question": "処す",
      "answer": "しょす",
      "meaning": "to manage, to deal with, to cope with, to sentence, to condemn, to punish"
    },
    {
      "question": "自堕落",
      "answer": "じだらく",
      "meaning": "self-indulgent, undisciplined, slovenly, debauched, negligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "忙殺",
      "answer": "ぼうさつ",
      "meaning": "being extremely busy, being swamped with work"
    },
    {
      "question": "遠路",
      "answer": "えんろ",
      "meaning": "long road, journey, detour"
    },
    {
      "question": "集束",
      "answer": "しゅうそく",
      "meaning": "focusing (e.g. light), convergence"
    },
    {
      "question": "決起",
      "answer": "けっき",
      "meaning": "rising to action, standing up against, jumping to one's feet"
    },
    {
      "question": "歯茎",
      "answer": "はぐき",
      "meaning": "gums, teethridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "目測",
      "answer": "もくそく",
      "meaning": "eye measurement, measure with eye"
    },
    {
      "question": "一辺倒",
      "answer": "いっぺんとう",
      "meaning": "complete devotion (to), total commitment (to), unvarying support (for), unwavering fixation (on), ri"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜襲",
      "answer": "やしゅう",
      "meaning": "night attack, nocturnal assault"
    },
    {
      "question": "余人",
      "answer": "よじん,よにん",
      "meaning": "others, other people"
    },
    {
      "question": "畏れ多い",
      "answer": "おそれおおい",
      "meaning": "awesome, awe-inspiring, august, discourteous (to a superior), lacking due respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱っぽい",
      "answer": "ねつっぽい",
      "meaning": "feverish, enthusiastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "将来性",
      "answer": "しょうらいせい",
      "meaning": "future prospects, promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "名代",
      "answer": "みょうだい,なだい",
      "meaning": "proxy, representative, well-known, fame"
    },
    {
      "question": "報じる",
      "answer": "ほうじる",
      "meaning": "to inform, to report"
    },
    {
      "question": "変則的",
      "answer": "へんそくてき",
      "meaning": "irregular, atypical, anomalous, anomalistic, abnormal"
    },
    {
      "question": "愛馬",
      "answer": "あいば",
      "meaning": "favourite horse, favorite horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "篝火",
      "answer": "かがりび",
      "meaning": "fire built in an iron basket (watch fire, fishing fire, etc.), bonfire, campfire, brothel-keeper (Ed"
    },
    {
      "question": "天窓",
      "answer": "てんまど,てんそう",
      "meaning": "skylight, head"
    },
    {
      "question": "光年",
      "answer": "こうねん",
      "meaning": "light year"
    },
    {
      "question": "大儀",
      "answer": "たいぎ",
      "meaning": "state ceremony, laborious, troublesome, irksome, arduous"
    },
    {
      "question": "後腐れ",
      "answer": "あとくされ,あとぐされ",
      "meaning": "future trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "逃げ腰",
      "answer": "にげごし",
      "meaning": "preparing to flee, being ready to run away"
    },
    {
      "question": "曝け出す",
      "answer": "さらけだす",
      "meaning": "to expose, to disclose, to lay bare, to confess"
    },
    {
      "question": "女湯",
      "answer": "おんなゆ",
      "meaning": "women's bath, women's section in a public bath"
    },
    {
      "question": "副業",
      "answer": "ふくぎょう",
      "meaning": "side job, sideline, subsidiary business"
    },
    {
      "question": "年代物",
      "answer": "ねんだいもの",
      "meaning": "antique, vintage item"
    },
    {
      "question": "季節外れ",
      "answer": "きせつはずれ",
      "meaning": "unseasonable, out of season"
    },
    {
      "question": "長屋",
      "answer": "ながや",
      "meaning": "tenement house, row house"
    },
    {
      "question": "国際的",
      "answer": "こくさいてき",
      "meaning": "international"
    },
    {
      "question": "桁が違う",
      "answer": "けたがちがう",
      "meaning": "to be wildly different, to be on a completely different scale, to be in a different league, to be po"
    },
    {
      "question": "切れ者",
      "answer": "きれもの",
      "meaning": "sharp and able person"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝相",
      "answer": "ねぞう",
      "meaning": "sleeping posture"
    },
    {
      "question": "浪漫",
      "answer": "ろうまん",
      "meaning": "romance (e.g. Arthurian romances), heroic tale, (nigh) impossible dream, adventurous spirit, great u"
    },
    {
      "question": "四隅",
      "answer": "よすみ,しぐう",
      "meaning": "four corners, four ordinal directions"
    },
    {
      "question": "抓る",
      "answer": "つねる,つめる",
      "meaning": "to pinch, to nip"
    },
    {
      "question": "灰燼",
      "answer": "かいじん",
      "meaning": "ash, embers, complete destruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "邪教",
      "answer": "じゃきょう",
      "meaning": "heretical religion, damaging religion, heresy"
    },
    {
      "question": "切断面",
      "answer": "せつだんめん",
      "meaning": "(cross) section (e.g. in a drawing), cutting plane"
    },
    {
      "question": "轟々",
      "answer": "ごうごう,とどろとどろ",
      "meaning": "thunderous, rumbling, thunderously, rumblingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "肉付き",
      "answer": "にくづき,ししつき",
      "meaning": "bodily build, degree of fleshiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "当直",
      "answer": "とうちょく",
      "meaning": "being on duty, being on watch, person on duty"
    },
    {
      "question": "前途",
      "answer": "ぜんと",
      "meaning": "future, prospects, outlook, journey ahead, distance yet to cover"
    },
    {
      "question": "向日葵",
      "answer": "ひまわり",
      "meaning": "sunflower (Helianthus annuus)"
    },
    {
      "question": "十字路",
      "answer": "じゅうじろ",
      "meaning": "crossroads, intersection"
    },
    {
      "question": "贅",
      "answer": "ぜい",
      "meaning": "extravagance, luxury"
    },
    {
      "question": "必需品",
      "answer": "ひつじゅひん",
      "meaning": "necessities, necessary article, requisite, essentials"
    },
    {
      "question": "掲示",
      "answer": "けいじ",
      "meaning": "notice, bulletin, post, posting, placard"
    },
    {
      "question": "若人",
      "answer": "わこうど,わかうど,わかびと",
      "meaning": "young person"
    },
    {
      "question": "身体検査",
      "answer": "しんたいけんさ",
      "meaning": "physical examination, medical checkup, frisking, pat-down, search"
    },
    {
      "question": "一番目",
      "answer": "いちばんめ",
      "meaning": "the first"
    },
    {
      "question": "船旅",
      "answer": "ふなたび",
      "meaning": "trip by boat, sea trip, voyage, cruise"
    },
    {
      "question": "単騎",
      "answer": "たんき",
      "meaning": "single horseman, wait for one tile to finish one's pair and one's hand, wait for half of one's pair"
    },
    {
      "question": "牧",
      "answer": "まき,ぼく",
      "meaning": "pasture, grazing land, regional governor in ancient China"
    },
    {
      "question": "充ちる",
      "answer": "みちる",
      "meaning": "to be full, to wax (e.g. moon), to rise (e.g. tide), to mature, to expire"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬱々",
      "answer": "うつうつ",
      "meaning": "gloomy, melancholy, pessimistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "帰郷",
      "answer": "ききょう",
      "meaning": "homecoming, return to one's home"
    },
    {
      "question": "冷血",
      "answer": "れいけつ",
      "meaning": "cold-bloodedness, coldheartedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "品格",
      "answer": "ひんかく",
      "meaning": "dignity, quality, grace, panache, level"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸止め",
      "answer": "すんどめ",
      "meaning": "stopping just before"
    },
    {
      "question": "腫らす",
      "answer": "はらす",
      "meaning": "to cause to swell, to inflame"
    },
    {
      "question": "静養",
      "answer": "せいよう",
      "meaning": "(convalescent) rest"
    },
    {
      "question": "生徒手帳",
      "answer": "せいとてちょう",
      "meaning": "student's handbook, small notebook that also acts as a student ID"
    },
    {
      "question": "異状",
      "answer": "いじょう",
      "meaning": "something wrong, accident, change, abnormality, aberration"
    },
    {
      "question": "切望",
      "answer": "せつぼう",
      "meaning": "earnest desire, eager hope, longing, yearning, hankering"
    },
    {
      "question": "絹糸",
      "answer": "けんし,きぬいと",
      "meaning": "silk thread"
    },
    {
      "question": "針路",
      "answer": "しんろ",
      "meaning": "course, direction"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮死",
      "answer": "かし",
      "meaning": "(state of) apparent death, suspended animation"
    },
    {
      "question": "激変",
      "answer": "げきへん",
      "meaning": "sudden change, upheaval"
    },
    {
      "question": "没入",
      "answer": "ぼつにゅう",
      "meaning": "immersion, being absorbed in"
    },
    {
      "question": "暴力団",
      "answer": "ぼうりょくだん",
      "meaning": "bōryokudan, gangster organization (organisation), crime syndicate, yakuza"
    },
    {
      "question": "欧米",
      "answer": "おうべい",
      "meaning": "Europe and America, the West"
    },
    {
      "question": "理事",
      "answer": "りじ",
      "meaning": "director, trustee"
    },
    {
      "question": "俯き",
      "answer": "うつむき",
      "meaning": "lying face down, upside down, prone"
    },
    {
      "question": "激辛",
      "answer": "げきから",
      "meaning": "extremely spicy, fiery hot, extremely harsh (criticism, review, etc.), scathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "初等",
      "answer": "しょとう",
      "meaning": "elementary, primary"
    },
    {
      "question": "蠍",
      "answer": "さそり",
      "meaning": "scorpion (Scorpiones spp.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "傷薬",
      "answer": "きずぐすり",
      "meaning": "salve, ointment, potion"
    },
    {
      "question": "逗留",
      "answer": "とうりゅう",
      "meaning": "staying, sojourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "気勢",
      "answer": "きせい",
      "meaning": "fervour, fervor, vigour, vigor, ardour, ardor, spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "淑やか",
      "answer": "しとやか",
      "meaning": "graceful, ladylike, modest, gentle, polite, quiet, well-mannered, refined (behavior)"
    },
    {
      "question": "張り込む",
      "answer": "はりこむ",
      "meaning": "to be on the lookout, to lie in wait"
    },
    {
      "question": "年明け",
      "answer": "としあけ,ねんあけ",
      "meaning": "beginning of the year, early in the New Year, expiration of a term of service"
    },
    {
      "question": "駄々",
      "answer": "だだ",
      "meaning": "tantrum, fretting"
    },
    {
      "question": "分布",
      "answer": "ぶんぷ",
      "meaning": "distribution, allocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "軽微",
      "answer": "けいび",
      "meaning": "slight, little, insignificant"
    },
    {
      "question": "協調",
      "answer": "きょうちょう",
      "meaning": "cooperation, conciliation, harmony, coordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "鞠",
      "answer": "まり",
      "meaning": "ball (for sport, games, etc.), kemari, type of football played by courtiers in ancient Japan"
    },
    {
      "question": "拳法",
      "answer": "けんぽう",
      "meaning": "Chinese martial arts, kung fu, wushu, quanfa, kenpō (martial arts), kempo"
    },
    {
      "question": "系譜",
      "answer": "けいふ",
      "meaning": "genealogy, lineage, family tree, pedigree"
    },
    {
      "question": "威",
      "answer": "おどし,い",
      "meaning": "leather strap binding the plates of traditional Japanese armor (armour), power, authority, might, in"
    },
    {
      "question": "薄皮",
      "answer": "うすかわ",
      "meaning": "thin skin"
    },
    {
      "question": "棒に振る",
      "answer": "ぼうにふる",
      "meaning": "to make a mess of, to sacrifice, to waste"
    },
    {
      "question": "落馬",
      "answer": "らくば",
      "meaning": "falling from a horse"
    },
    {
      "question": "替わり",
      "answer": "かわり,がわり",
      "meaning": "substitute, replacement, substituting, replacing, stand-in, proxy, alternate, deputy, relief, succes"
    },
    {
      "question": "無断",
      "answer": "むだん",
      "meaning": "without permission, without notice"
    },
    {
      "question": "一挙に",
      "answer": "いっきょに",
      "meaning": "at a stroke, with a single swoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "禿げる",
      "answer": "はげる",
      "meaning": "to lose hair, to become bald, to become bare (e.g. a mountain becomes bare of trees)"
    },
    {
      "question": "舎弟",
      "answer": "しゃてい",
      "meaning": "one's younger brother, underling (e.g. in yakuza), junior male peer, sworn younger brother"
    },
    {
      "question": "損耗",
      "answer": "そんもう",
      "meaning": "loss"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱源",
      "answer": "ねつげん",
      "meaning": "heat source"
    },
    {
      "question": "人騒がせ",
      "answer": "ひとさわがせ",
      "meaning": "person that annoys or causes trouble, false alarm"
    },
    {
      "question": "懊悩",
      "answer": "おうのう",
      "meaning": "anguish, trouble, agony"
    },
    {
      "question": "語り口",
      "answer": "かたりくち",
      "meaning": "way of reciting, way of telling a story"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱線",
      "answer": "ねっせん",
      "meaning": "heated wire, infrared rays, heat rays"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事量",
      "answer": "しごとりょう",
      "meaning": "(one's) workload, amount of work (to be) done by one"
    },
    {
      "question": "痴話喧嘩",
      "answer": "ちわげんか",
      "meaning": "lovers' quarrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "組長",
      "answer": "くみちょう",
      "meaning": "boss (esp. yakuza), foreman"
    },
    {
      "question": "減衰",
      "answer": "げんすい",
      "meaning": "attenuation, damping, decay"
    },
    {
      "question": "総督",
      "answer": "そうとく",
      "meaning": "governor-general, governor, viceroy"
    },
    {
      "question": "防寒",
      "answer": "ぼうかん",
      "meaning": "protection against cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "慈しみ",
      "answer": "いつくしみ",
      "meaning": "affection, love, fondness, tenderness"
    },
    {
      "question": "因み",
      "answer": "ちなみ",
      "meaning": "association, link, connection, pledge (esp. for marriage), promise"
    },
    {
      "question": "狩",
      "answer": "かり",
      "meaning": "hunting, harvesting (e.g. berries, fruit), picking, gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "返礼",
      "answer": "へんれい",
      "meaning": "return present, return gift, something done in return (as way of thanks), retaliation, revenge"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝廷",
      "answer": "ちょうてい",
      "meaning": "Imperial Court"
    },
    {
      "question": "焦げ臭い",
      "answer": "こげくさい",
      "meaning": "smelling burnt, tasting burnt, having a burnt smell"
    },
    {
      "question": "司令塔",
      "answer": "しれいとう",
      "meaning": "control tower, conning tower, leader, commander, person calling the shots, playmaker, game maker"
    },
    {
      "question": "伊勢",
      "answer": "いせ",
      "meaning": "Ise (former province located in the major part of present-day Mie Prefecture and parts of Aichi and"
    },
    {
      "question": "混戦",
      "answer": "こんせん",
      "meaning": "confused fight, free-for-all, melee, close contest, close match"
    },
    {
      "question": "石油",
      "answer": "せきゆ",
      "meaning": "oil, petroleum, kerosene, paraffin"
    },
    {
      "question": "表皮",
      "answer": "ひょうひ",
      "meaning": "epidermis, cuticle"
    },
    {
      "question": "白雪姫",
      "answer": "しらゆきひめ",
      "meaning": "Snow White"
    },
    {
      "question": "一桁",
      "answer": "ひとけた",
      "meaning": "one digit, one column, the 'ones' column"
    },
    {
      "question": "滅相",
      "answer": "めっそう",
      "meaning": "extravagant, absurd"
    },
    {
      "question": "高山",
      "answer": "こうざん",
      "meaning": "high mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "投射",
      "answer": "とうしゃ",
      "meaning": "projection"
    },
    {
      "question": "雑兵",
      "answer": "ぞうひょう,ざっぴょう",
      "meaning": "common soldier, private, rank and file, small fry, underling"
    },
    {
      "question": "敵討ち",
      "answer": "かたきうち",
      "meaning": "vengeance, revenge, retaliation"
    },
    {
      "question": "怠け者",
      "answer": "なまけもの",
      "meaning": "lazy person, lazy fellow, slothful person"
    },
    {
      "question": "寸分",
      "answer": "すんぶん,すんぷん",
      "meaning": "tiny bit"
    },
    {
      "question": "贋作",
      "answer": "がんさく",
      "meaning": "fake (work), counterfeit"
    },
    {
      "question": "親不孝",
      "answer": "おやふこう",
      "meaning": "lack of filial piety, disobedience to one's parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "星人",
      "answer": "せいじん",
      "meaning": "person from (the planet of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "歪曲",
      "answer": "わいきょく",
      "meaning": "distortion, falsification, perversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "機動性",
      "answer": "きどうせい",
      "meaning": "cavalry, mobility, maneuverability"
    },
    {
      "question": "初動",
      "answer": "しょどう",
      "meaning": "initial response (e.g. to a crisis), action in the earliest stages, initial shock (of an earthquake)"
    },
    {
      "question": "一括",
      "answer": "いっかつ",
      "meaning": "lumping together, summing up, bundle, lump, batch"
    },
    {
      "question": "水飛沫",
      "answer": "みずしぶき",
      "meaning": "splash (of water), spray"
    },
    {
      "question": "嗅ぎ回る",
      "answer": "かぎまわる",
      "meaning": "to sniff around, to snoop around, to nose about"
    },
    {
      "question": "苦になる",
      "answer": "くになる",
      "meaning": "to be bothered (by something), to suffer"
    },
    {
      "question": "日当たり",
      "answer": "ひあたり",
      "meaning": "exposure to the sun, sunny place, per day"
    },
    {
      "question": "超音波",
      "answer": "ちょうおんぱ",
      "meaning": "ultrasonic waves, ultrasound"
    },
    {
      "question": "后",
      "answer": "きさき,きさい,ご",
      "meaning": "empress, queen, after"
    },
    {
      "question": "旅費",
      "answer": "りょひ",
      "meaning": "travel expenses"
    },
    {
      "question": "楕円形",
      "answer": "だえんけい",
      "meaning": "elliptical shape"
    },
    {
      "question": "耳慣れる",
      "answer": "みみなれる",
      "meaning": "to be something familiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "野戦",
      "answer": "やせん",
      "meaning": "field battle, field operations, open battle, battlefield, battlefront"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓦",
      "answer": "グラム,かわら",
      "meaning": "gram, gramme, roof tile"
    },
    {
      "question": "健康診断",
      "answer": "けんこうしんだん",
      "meaning": "physical examination"
    },
    {
      "question": "暖まる",
      "answer": "あたたまる,あったまる",
      "meaning": "to warm oneself, to sun oneself, to warm up, to get warm"
    },
    {
      "question": "気管",
      "answer": "きかん",
      "meaning": "trachea"
    },
    {
      "question": "南極",
      "answer": "なんきょく",
      "meaning": "South Pole, the Antarctic, Antarctica"
    },
    {
      "question": "喜悦",
      "answer": "きえつ",
      "meaning": "joy"
    },
    {
      "question": "併走",
      "answer": "へいそう",
      "meaning": "running parallel (to), running side-by-side, keeping pace (with)"
    },
    {
      "question": "美点",
      "answer": "びてん",
      "meaning": "virtue, charm, merit, good point"
    },
    {
      "question": "週刊",
      "answer": "しゅうかん",
      "meaning": "weekly publication"
    },
    {
      "question": "呼吸困難",
      "answer": "こきゅうこんなん",
      "meaning": "labored breathing, laboured breathing, dyspnea, dyspnoea"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊歩道",
      "answer": "ゆうほどう",
      "meaning": "promenade, esplanade"
    },
    {
      "question": "大賞",
      "answer": "たいしょう",
      "meaning": "big prize, first prize"
    },
    {
      "question": "変幻自在",
      "answer": "へんげんじざい",
      "meaning": "phantasmagoric, protean, shape-shifting, kaleidoscopic, capable of ever-changing appearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "友軍",
      "answer": "ゆうぐん",
      "meaning": "friendly army, friendly troops, allied army"
    },
    {
      "question": "根絶",
      "answer": "こんぜつ",
      "meaning": "eradication, extermination, rooting out, stamping out, getting rid of"
    },
    {
      "question": "投石",
      "answer": "とうせき",
      "meaning": "stone throwing"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉尻",
      "answer": "ことばじり",
      "meaning": "word ending, way of ending one's words, slip of the tongue, verbal mistake"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜逃げ",
      "answer": "よにげ",
      "meaning": "night flight (without paying), skipping out by night, moonlight flit"
    },
    {
      "question": "町娘",
      "answer": "まちむすめ",
      "meaning": "town girl, girl raised in a town"
    },
    {
      "question": "面差し",
      "answer": "おもざし",
      "meaning": "looks, features"
    },
    {
      "question": "凝固",
      "answer": "ぎょうこ",
      "meaning": "coagulation, freezing, solidification"
    },
    {
      "question": "不相応",
      "answer": "ふそうおう",
      "meaning": "unsuited, inappropriate, improper, undeserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "忌",
      "answer": "いみ,き",
      "meaning": "mourning, abstinence, taboo, religious purification, pure, holy, mourning period, anniversary of one"
    },
    {
      "question": "姉御",
      "answer": "あねご",
      "meaning": "elder sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "与る",
      "answer": "あずかる",
      "meaning": "to participate in, to take part in, to play a part in, to receive, to be given, to enjoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "唱和",
      "answer": "しょうわ",
      "meaning": "cheering in chorus, saying in unison"
    },
    {
      "question": "婚姻届",
      "answer": "こんいんとどけ",
      "meaning": "marriage registration"
    },
    {
      "question": "点呼",
      "answer": "てんこ",
      "meaning": "roll-call, muster"
    },
    {
      "question": "早鐘",
      "answer": "はやがね",
      "meaning": "alarm bell"
    },
    {
      "question": "恩寵",
      "answer": "おんちょう",
      "meaning": "grace, favour, favor"
    },
    {
      "question": "砂煙",
      "answer": "すなけむり",
      "meaning": "cloud of sand (dust, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "育ての親",
      "answer": "そだてのおや",
      "meaning": "foster parents"
    },
    {
      "question": "水遊び",
      "answer": "みずあそび",
      "meaning": "bathing (in a lake, river, or in the sea), playing in the water, playing with water"
    },
    {
      "question": "肥大",
      "answer": "ひだい",
      "meaning": "swelling, enlargement, becoming fat, hypertrophy"
    },
    {
      "question": "鬼火",
      "answer": "おにび",
      "meaning": "will-o'-the-wisp, jack-o'-lantern"
    },
    {
      "question": "地力",
      "answer": "ちりょく,じりき",
      "meaning": "fertility, one's own potential, real ability, one's own strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "危機一髪",
      "answer": "ききいっぱつ",
      "meaning": "by a hair's breadth, in the nick of time, touch and go, close call, critical moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "粘り強い",
      "answer": "ねばりづよい",
      "meaning": "tenacious, persevering, persistent, stubborn, steadfast, sticky"
    },
    {
      "question": "天魔",
      "answer": "てんま",
      "meaning": "demon of the sixth heaven in the realm of desire who tries to prevent people from doing good"
    },
    {
      "question": "特級",
      "answer": "とっきゅう",
      "meaning": "high grade, special grade, classy"
    },
    {
      "question": "振り撒く",
      "answer": "ふりまく",
      "meaning": "to scatter, to sprinkle, to spray, to strew, to lavish (money, charm, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "解凍",
      "answer": "かいとう",
      "meaning": "thaw, defrosting, decompression (e.g. of a file), unpacking, extracting, unzipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "雨風",
      "answer": "あまかぜ,あめかぜ",
      "meaning": "rain and wind, driving rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "人民",
      "answer": "じんみん,おおみたから",
      "meaning": "the people, citizens, the populace, imperial subjects"
    },
    {
      "question": "統治者",
      "answer": "とうちしゃ",
      "meaning": "the ruler, sovereign"
    },
    {
      "question": "皆が皆",
      "answer": "みんながみんな,みながみな",
      "meaning": "each and all, every single one, everybody"
    },
    {
      "question": "入れ墨",
      "answer": "いれずみ",
      "meaning": "tattoo (esp. a traditional Japanese one), tattooing"
    },
    {
      "question": "保証人",
      "answer": "ほしょうにん",
      "meaning": "guarantor, surety, sponsor, reference, bondsman"
    },
    {
      "question": "単",
      "answer": "ひとえ,たん",
      "meaning": "one layer, single layer, monopetalous, unlined kimono, single-edged eyelid, eyelid with an epicanthi"
    },
    {
      "question": "四国",
      "answer": "しこく",
      "meaning": "Shikoku (smallest of the four main islands of Japan)"
    },
    {
      "question": "締まり",
      "answer": "しまり",
      "meaning": "closing, shutting, firmness, tightness, discipline, control"
    },
    {
      "question": "青黒い",
      "answer": "あおぐろい",
      "meaning": "black with hints of blue (as in a bruise), bluish black"
    },
    {
      "question": "偶像",
      "answer": "ぐうぞう",
      "meaning": "image, idol, statue"
    },
    {
      "question": "感染症",
      "answer": "かんせんしょう",
      "meaning": "infectious disease, infection"
    },
    {
      "question": "三者",
      "answer": "さんしゃ",
      "meaning": "three persons, three parties"
    },
    {
      "question": "無法",
      "answer": "むほう",
      "meaning": "lawlessness, injustice, wrong, outrage, outrageous, lawless, disorderly, unjust, unreasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "橋渡し",
      "answer": "はしわたし",
      "meaning": "bridge building, mediation, go-between, intermediary, (through the) good offices (of someone)"
    },
    {
      "question": "御伽噺",
      "answer": "おとぎばなし",
      "meaning": "fairy-tale, nursery-tale"
    },
    {
      "question": "道標",
      "answer": "どうひょう,みちじるし,みちしるべ",
      "meaning": "guidepost, signpost, guide, manual, handbook, tiger beetle (esp. the Japanese tiger beetle, Cicindel"
    },
    {
      "question": "建て直す",
      "answer": "たてなおす",
      "meaning": "to rebuild, to reconstruct"
    },
    {
      "question": "裏打ち",
      "answer": "うらうち",
      "meaning": "lining, backing, backing up (e.g. a theory), support, bolstering"
    },
    {
      "question": "千里",
      "answer": "せんり",
      "meaning": "1000 ri, (a) long distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "途",
      "answer": "みち,と,ど",
      "meaning": "road, path, street, lane, passage, route, way, distance, journey, road (e.g. to victory), course, wa"
    },
    {
      "question": "内輪",
      "answer": "うちわ,ないりん",
      "meaning": "family circle, one's circle (of friends, co-workers, etc.), one's fellows, in-group, private matters"
    },
    {
      "question": "示し",
      "answer": "しめし",
      "meaning": "lesson, discipline, example (e.g. set a bad example), revelation"
    },
    {
      "question": "害悪",
      "answer": "がいあく",
      "meaning": "harm, injury, evil (influence)"
    },
    {
      "question": "混迷",
      "answer": "こんめい",
      "meaning": "turmoil, chaos, confusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "情報操作",
      "answer": "じょうほうそうさ",
      "meaning": "manipulation of information, spin"
    },
    {
      "question": "海鮮",
      "answer": "かいせん",
      "meaning": "seafood"
    },
    {
      "question": "宝庫",
      "answer": "ほうこ",
      "meaning": "treasury, treasure house, storehouse, repository, treasure trove, rich source (of)"
    },
    {
      "question": "髭面",
      "answer": "ひげづら",
      "meaning": "bearded face, unshaven face, hairy face"
    },
    {
      "question": "応接",
      "answer": "おうせつ",
      "meaning": "reception (e.g. of visitors), dealing with"
    },
    {
      "question": "比類",
      "answer": "ひるい",
      "meaning": "parallel, equal, match"
    },
    {
      "question": "物思い",
      "answer": "ものおもい",
      "meaning": "reverie, meditation, anxiety, thought, pensiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "俗世",
      "answer": "ぞくせい,ぞくせ",
      "meaning": "this world, earthly life"
    },
    {
      "question": "見聞",
      "answer": "けんぶん,けんもん",
      "meaning": "information, experience, knowledge, observation"
    },
    {
      "question": "行く行く",
      "answer": "ゆくゆく",
      "meaning": "on the way, someday"
    },
    {
      "question": "元首",
      "answer": "げんしゅ",
      "meaning": "sovereign, ruler, head of state"
    },
    {
      "question": "絶壁",
      "answer": "ぜっぺき",
      "meaning": "precipice, cliff, flat head"
    },
    {
      "question": "触感",
      "answer": "しょっかん",
      "meaning": "sense of touch, sense of being touched, tactile sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰部",
      "answer": "いんぶ",
      "meaning": "the genital area"
    },
    {
      "question": "口移し",
      "answer": "くちうつし",
      "meaning": "mouth-to-mouth feeding, beak-to-beak feeding, mouth-to-mouth (resuscitation), conveying by word of m"
    },
    {
      "question": "崖下",
      "answer": "がいか,がけした",
      "meaning": "below a cliff"
    },
    {
      "question": "縦長",
      "answer": "たてなが",
      "meaning": "oblong, vertical writing style (e.g. on envelopes), portrait orientation"
    },
    {
      "question": "小雨",
      "answer": "こさめ,しょうう,こあめ",
      "meaning": "light rain, drizzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "先々代",
      "answer": "せんせんだい",
      "meaning": "the one before last, two generations, etc. previous"
    },
    {
      "question": "一人歩き",
      "answer": "ひとりあるき",
      "meaning": "taking on a life of its own (of a rumour, etc.), walking by oneself, talking a walk by oneself, walk"
    },
    {
      "question": "特色",
      "answer": "とくしょく",
      "meaning": "characteristic, feature, idiosyncrasy, personal colour, spot color (in printing)"
    },
    {
      "question": "早い話が",
      "answer": "はやいはなしが",
      "meaning": "in short, in a nutshell, in a word, to cut a long story short"
    },
    {
      "question": "処女膜",
      "answer": "しょじょまく",
      "meaning": "hymen"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び退る",
      "answer": "とびすさる",
      "meaning": "to leap back, to jump back"
    },
    {
      "question": "横並び",
      "answer": "よこならび",
      "meaning": "going along with something, following the crowd, treating something in an equal or egalitarian manne"
    },
    {
      "question": "部費",
      "answer": "ぶひ",
      "meaning": "club budget, club expense"
    },
    {
      "question": "散財",
      "answer": "さんざい",
      "meaning": "extravagant spending, wasteful spending, splurging, squandering"
    },
    {
      "question": "在宅",
      "answer": "ざいたく",
      "meaning": "being in, being at home"
    },
    {
      "question": "害す",
      "answer": "がいす",
      "meaning": "to injure, to damage, to harm, to hurt, to kill, to hinder, to obstruct"
    },
    {
      "question": "脱退",
      "answer": "だったい",
      "meaning": "withdrawal (e.g. from an organization), secession, leaving, pulling out"
    },
    {
      "question": "調度",
      "answer": "ちょうど",
      "meaning": "household items, furniture, furnishings, fixtures, supplies, bow and arrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "変わり身",
      "answer": "かわりみ",
      "meaning": "change of attitude (stance, position), lightness of foot, ability to dodge out of the way of an atta"
    },
    {
      "question": "不協和音",
      "answer": "ふきょうわおん",
      "meaning": "discord, dissonance, cacophony"
    },
    {
      "question": "勝手口",
      "answer": "かってぐち",
      "meaning": "kitchen door, back door, service door, tradesman's entrance, host's entrance to a tea-ceremony room"
    },
    {
      "question": "溺死",
      "answer": "できし",
      "meaning": "death by drowning"
    },
    {
      "question": "水入らず",
      "answer": "みずいらず",
      "meaning": "(being) by oneself, with no outsiders present"
    },
    {
      "question": "兵糧",
      "answer": "ひょうろう",
      "meaning": "(army) provisions, food"
    },
    {
      "question": "摩耗",
      "answer": "まもう",
      "meaning": "wear, abrasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "実例",
      "answer": "じつれい",
      "meaning": "example, illustration, precedent"
    },
    {
      "question": "裂帛",
      "answer": "れっぱく",
      "meaning": "cutting through cloth, sound of cutting through cloth, shrieking sound, woman's scream, loud scream,"
    },
    {
      "question": "白兵戦",
      "answer": "はくへいせん",
      "meaning": "hand-to-hand combat"
    },
    {
      "question": "間断",
      "answer": "かんだん",
      "meaning": "break in time, interruption, pause"
    },
    {
      "question": "負債",
      "answer": "ふさい",
      "meaning": "debt, liabilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "返り咲く",
      "answer": "かえりざく",
      "meaning": "to come back, to bloom a second time"
    },
    {
      "question": "規範",
      "answer": "きはん",
      "meaning": "model, standard, pattern, norm, criterion, example"
    },
    {
      "question": "従姉妹",
      "answer": "いとこ,じゅうしまい",
      "meaning": "cousin (female)"
    },
    {
      "question": "合掌",
      "answer": "がっしょう",
      "meaning": "pressing one's hands together in prayer, triangular frame of a thatched roof, yours sincerely, yours"
    },
    {
      "question": "綿菓子",
      "answer": "わたがし",
      "meaning": "cotton candy"
    },
    {
      "question": "斬首",
      "answer": "ざんしゅ",
      "meaning": "decapitation, decapitated head"
    },
    {
      "question": "本領",
      "answer": "ほんりょう",
      "meaning": "characteristic quality, special character, one's real ability, one's specialty, one's function, one'"
    },
    {
      "question": "注釈",
      "answer": "ちゅうしゃく",
      "meaning": "notes, comment, remark, annotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "禁呪",
      "answer": "きんじゅ",
      "meaning": "charm, incantation, spell, magic formula"
    },
    {
      "question": "朝焼け",
      "answer": "あさやけ",
      "meaning": "morning glow, sunrise colors, sunrise colours"
    },
    {
      "question": "休業",
      "answer": "きゅうぎょう",
      "meaning": "suspension of business, temporary closure (of a store, school, etc.), shutdown, holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "良心的",
      "answer": "りょうしんてき",
      "meaning": "upright, fair, honest"
    },
    {
      "question": "北欧",
      "answer": "ほくおう",
      "meaning": "Northern Europe, Nordic countries, Scandinavia"
    },
    {
      "question": "物流",
      "answer": "ぶつりゅう",
      "meaning": "physical distribution, distribution of goods, logistics"
    },
    {
      "question": "痛恨",
      "answer": "つうこん",
      "meaning": "regretful, sorrowful, bitter, contrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "機内",
      "answer": "きない",
      "meaning": "inside a plane, in-flight"
    },
    {
      "question": "高騰",
      "answer": "こうとう",
      "meaning": "sudden price jump, steep price rise"
    },
    {
      "question": "品行方正",
      "answer": "ひんこうほうせい",
      "meaning": "irreproachable conduct, good conduct, high morals"
    },
    {
      "question": "足並み",
      "answer": "あしなみ",
      "meaning": "pace, step"
    },
    {
      "question": "自明の理",
      "answer": "じめいのり",
      "meaning": "self-evident truth, obvious fact, truism, axiom"
    },
    {
      "question": "持久戦",
      "answer": "じきゅうせん",
      "meaning": "protracted war, war of attrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "神霊",
      "answer": "しんれい",
      "meaning": "divine spirit"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰惨",
      "answer": "いんさん",
      "meaning": "sadness and gloom"
    },
    {
      "question": "相手方",
      "answer": "あいてかた,あいてがた",
      "meaning": "other party, opposite party, opposing team, one's opponent, one's adversary"
    },
    {
      "question": "売り込み",
      "answer": "うりこみ",
      "meaning": "sales promotion, hard selling"
    },
    {
      "question": "怠い",
      "answer": "だるい,たるい",
      "meaning": "sluggish, languid, listless, heavy (heart, legs, etc.), dull, bothersome, tiresome, pain-in-the-ass"
    },
    {
      "question": "米粒",
      "answer": "こめつぶ",
      "meaning": "grain of rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち会い",
      "answer": "たちあい",
      "meaning": "presence (e.g. of an observer), observation, observer, witness, trading session (at an exchange)"
    },
    {
      "question": "導師",
      "answer": "どうし",
      "meaning": "officiating priest, presiding priest at a ceremony, religious teacher, highly-ranked priest, guru, i"
    },
    {
      "question": "没",
      "answer": "ぼつ",
      "meaning": "death, rejection (of a manuscript, etc.), lacking, without"
    },
    {
      "question": "客引き",
      "answer": "きゃくひき",
      "meaning": "touting, tout, barker, pander"
    },
    {
      "question": "離れ離れ",
      "answer": "はなればなれ,かれがれ",
      "meaning": "separate, scattered, apart, estranged, separated"
    },
    {
      "question": "大詰め",
      "answer": "おおづめ",
      "meaning": "final scene, the end, finale"
    },
    {
      "question": "為る",
      "answer": "する,なる",
      "meaning": "to do, to carry out, to perform, to cause to become, to make (into), to turn (into), to serve as, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "紫煙",
      "answer": "しえん",
      "meaning": "purple smoke, tobacco smoke"
    },
    {
      "question": "喩え",
      "answer": "たとえ",
      "meaning": "example, simile, metaphor, allegory, fable, parable"
    },
    {
      "question": "電線",
      "answer": "でんせん",
      "meaning": "electric line, electric cable, power cable, telephone line, telegraph wire"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝日",
      "answer": "しゅくじつ",
      "meaning": "national holiday, public holiday"
    },
    {
      "question": "言葉遊び",
      "answer": "ことばあそび",
      "meaning": "word game, wordplay, playing with words"
    },
    {
      "question": "本格",
      "answer": "ほんかく",
      "meaning": "original method or procedure, serious, orthodox, classical, genuine"
    },
    {
      "question": "訴訟",
      "answer": "そしょう",
      "meaning": "litigation, lawsuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "何時も",
      "answer": "いつも",
      "meaning": "always, usually, every time, never"
    },
    {
      "question": "跳ね",
      "answer": "はね",
      "meaning": "(a) jump, splashes (usu. of mud), upward turn at the bottom (e.g. of a vertical stroke of a kanji or"
    },
    {
      "question": "古株",
      "answer": "ふるかぶ",
      "meaning": "old-timer, veteran, senior, old stump, old roots"
    },
    {
      "question": "人出",
      "answer": "ひとで",
      "meaning": "crowd, turnout"
    },
    {
      "question": "単発",
      "answer": "たんぱつ",
      "meaning": "firing one shot at a time, single-shot gun, having only one engine, single-engined aeroplane, single"
    },
    {
      "question": "重畳",
      "answer": "ちょうじょう,じゅうじょう",
      "meaning": "placed one upon another, piled up, excellent, splendid, superimposition, superposition"
    },
    {
      "question": "難敵",
      "answer": "なんてき",
      "meaning": "formidable enemy"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘味",
      "answer": "あまみ,かんみ",
      "meaning": "sweetness, sugary taste, sweets, dessert, cake, charm, appeal, taste, flavour, flavor"
    },
    {
      "question": "調停",
      "answer": "ちょうてい",
      "meaning": "arbitration, conciliation, mediation"
    },
    {
      "question": "鍬",
      "answer": "くわ",
      "meaning": "hoe"
    },
    {
      "question": "大気圏",
      "answer": "たいきけん",
      "meaning": "the atmosphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "無地",
      "answer": "むじ",
      "meaning": "plain, unfigured, patternless, solid (color)"
    },
    {
      "question": "最長",
      "answer": "さいちょう",
      "meaning": "longest, oldest"
    },
    {
      "question": "陰影",
      "answer": "いんえい",
      "meaning": "shadow, shade, shading, gloom, nuance, shades of meaning, subtleties"
    },
    {
      "question": "緩み",
      "answer": "ゆるみ",
      "meaning": "slack, looseness, play"
    },
    {
      "question": "知略",
      "answer": "ちりゃく",
      "meaning": "ingenuity, resourcefulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "定住",
      "answer": "ていじゅう,じょうじゅう",
      "meaning": "settlement, permanent residency"
    },
    {
      "question": "滔々",
      "answer": "とうとう",
      "meaning": "torrentially, swiftly flowing (water, esp. river), voluminously flowing, (speak) eloquently, fluentl"
    },
    {
      "question": "無礼講",
      "answer": "ぶれいこう",
      "meaning": "no-holds-barred party, free and easy gathering"
    },
    {
      "question": "行き違い",
      "answer": "いきちがい,ゆきちがい",
      "meaning": "crossing without meeting (e.g. letters in the post, people on the road), going astray, difference of"
    },
    {
      "question": "自然発生",
      "answer": "しぜんはっせい",
      "meaning": "spontaneous generation, abiogenesis, natural occurrence, spontaneous occurrence"
    },
    {
      "question": "浮世離れ",
      "answer": "うきよばなれ",
      "meaning": "otherworldliness, detachment from the real world, lack of worldly sense"
    },
    {
      "question": "廻す",
      "answer": "まわす",
      "meaning": "to turn, to rotate, to spin, to twist, to gyrate, to pass around, to send around, to hand around, to"
    },
    {
      "question": "毒蛇",
      "answer": "どくじゃ,どくへび",
      "meaning": "poisonous snake, poisonous serpent"
    },
    {
      "question": "芽が出る",
      "answer": "めがでる",
      "meaning": "to bud, to sprout, to germinate, to have luck on one's side, to get lucky"
    },
    {
      "question": "横行",
      "answer": "おうこう,おうぎょう",
      "meaning": "walking sideways, staggering, striding, being rampant, being widespread, being prevalent"
    },
    {
      "question": "石版",
      "answer": "せきばん",
      "meaning": "lithograph, lithography"
    },
    {
      "question": "人智",
      "answer": "じんち",
      "meaning": "human intellect, knowledge"
    },
    {
      "question": "下旬",
      "answer": "げじゅん",
      "meaning": "last third of a month, 21st to the last day of a month"
    },
    {
      "question": "王権",
      "answer": "おうけん",
      "meaning": "royal authority, regal power, authority of the king"
    },
    {
      "question": "半球",
      "answer": "はんきゅう",
      "meaning": "hemisphere"
    },
    {
      "question": "返り",
      "answer": "かえり",
      "meaning": "turning over, flipping over, reply, response, marks written alongside characters in a classical Chin"
    },
    {
      "question": "購買部",
      "answer": "こうばいぶ",
      "meaning": "school store, co-op"
    },
    {
      "question": "仮設",
      "answer": "かせつ",
      "meaning": "temporary, provisional, to do something temporarily (esp. build temporary facilities), to do somethi"
    },
    {
      "question": "大波",
      "answer": "おおなみ",
      "meaning": "billow, surge, large wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "直訴",
      "answer": "じきそ",
      "meaning": "direct appeal"
    },
    {
      "question": "干上がる",
      "answer": "ひあがる",
      "meaning": "to dry up, to parch, to ebb away"
    },
    {
      "question": "鳥籠",
      "answer": "とりかご",
      "meaning": "birdcage"
    },
    {
      "question": "熱波",
      "answer": "ねっぱ",
      "meaning": "heat wave"
    },
    {
      "question": "運勢",
      "answer": "うんせい",
      "meaning": "fortune, luck"
    },
    {
      "question": "溶く",
      "answer": "とく",
      "meaning": "to dissolve (paint), to scramble (eggs), to melt (metal, etc.), to mix (water with flour, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "総力戦",
      "answer": "そうりょくせん",
      "meaning": "all-out war, total war"
    },
    {
      "question": "花形",
      "answer": "はながた,かけい",
      "meaning": "floral pattern, flourish, ornament, star (actor, player, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "散漫",
      "answer": "さんまん",
      "meaning": "vague, desultory, distracted, loose, half-hearted, diffuse, scattered"
    },
    {
      "question": "横穴",
      "answer": "よこあな,おうけつ",
      "meaning": "cave, tunnel, tunnel tomb (Kofun period)"
    },
    {
      "question": "防戦",
      "answer": "ぼうせん",
      "meaning": "defensive fight (battle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "雲間",
      "answer": "くもま",
      "meaning": "rift between clouds"
    },
    {
      "question": "手を突く",
      "answer": "てをつく",
      "meaning": "to place both hands on the ground (to express respect, apology or to present a request)"
    },
    {
      "question": "論点",
      "answer": "ろんてん",
      "meaning": "point in question (at issue)"
    },
    {
      "question": "甘言",
      "answer": "かんげん",
      "meaning": "sweet words, smooth talk, cajolery, flattery, sycophancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "樹液",
      "answer": "じゅえき",
      "meaning": "sap"
    },
    {
      "question": "朱雀",
      "answer": "すざく,すじゃく,しゅじゃく",
      "meaning": "Vermilion Bird (god said to rule over the southern heavens), seven mansions (Chinese constellations)"
    },
    {
      "question": "寮生",
      "answer": "りょうせい",
      "meaning": "boarder, boarding student"
    },
    {
      "question": "廃嫡",
      "answer": "はいちゃく",
      "meaning": "disinheritance"
    },
    {
      "question": "農夫",
      "answer": "のうふ",
      "meaning": "(male) farmer, peasant, farmhand"
    },
    {
      "question": "別腹",
      "answer": "べつばら",
      "meaning": "dessert stomach, having room for dessert despite being full"
    },
    {
      "question": "手傷",
      "answer": "てきず",
      "meaning": "wound suffered in a fight"
    },
    {
      "question": "紆余曲折",
      "answer": "うよきょくせつ",
      "meaning": "turns and twists, ups and downs, meandering, complications, vicissitudes"
    },
    {
      "question": "木彫り",
      "answer": "きぼり",
      "meaning": "wood carving, woodcraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "鉄扉",
      "answer": "てっぴ",
      "meaning": "iron door"
    },
    {
      "question": "短パン",
      "answer": "たんパン",
      "meaning": "shorts, short pants"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛び込み",
      "answer": "とびこみ",
      "meaning": "jump, plunge, dive, appearing without an appointment, bursting in, arriving unannounced, cropping up"
    },
    {
      "question": "混み合う",
      "answer": "こみあう",
      "meaning": "to be crowded, to be packed, to be jammed"
    },
    {
      "question": "湘南",
      "answer": "",
      "meaning": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "出会い頭",
      "answer": "であいがしら",
      "meaning": "in passing another (esp. colliding with oncoming traffic, bumping into a person), the moment two per"
    },
    {
      "question": "立ち竦む",
      "answer": "たちすくむ",
      "meaning": "to be petrified, to be unable to move, to be paralyzed (with horror), to be stupefied (with amazemen"
    },
    {
      "question": "業物",
      "answer": "わざもの",
      "meaning": "sharp sword"
    },
    {
      "question": "水圧",
      "answer": "すいあつ",
      "meaning": "water (hydraulic) pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "円陣",
      "answer": "えんじん",
      "meaning": "forming a circle, circular formation (orig. in battle), huddle, ring"
    },
    {
      "question": "常套手段",
      "answer": "じょうとうしゅだん",
      "meaning": "one's habitual practice, usual measure, old trick"
    },
    {
      "question": "力士",
      "answer": "りきし,りきじ",
      "meaning": "sumo wrestler, rikishi, strong man, Deva king"
    },
    {
      "question": "致命",
      "answer": "ちめい",
      "meaning": "fatal"
    },
    {
      "question": "射的",
      "answer": "しゃてき",
      "meaning": "target practice, marksmanship, target shooting (e.g. at a fair)"
    },
    {
      "question": "元締め",
      "answer": "もとじめ",
      "meaning": "manager, controller, administrator, chief treasurer, boss (of a gambling den)"
    },
    {
      "question": "誤作動",
      "answer": "ごさどう",
      "meaning": "malfunction, failure"
    },
    {
      "question": "感涙",
      "answer": "かんるい",
      "meaning": "tears (from being deeply moved), tears of gratitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "奉公",
      "answer": "ほうこう",
      "meaning": "live-in domestic service, live-in apprenticeship, public duty, public service"
    },
    {
      "question": "足払い",
      "answer": "あしばらい",
      "meaning": "ashibarai, foot sweep, sweeping one's opponent's legs from under them (judo, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "超然",
      "answer": "ちょうぜん",
      "meaning": "detached, aloof, transcendental"
    },
    {
      "question": "実力主義",
      "answer": "じつりょくしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "merit system (as opposed to seniority), meritocracy, ability-ism"
    },
    {
      "question": "双頭",
      "answer": "そうとう",
      "meaning": "double-headed"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍議",
      "answer": "ぐんぎ",
      "meaning": "war council"
    },
    {
      "question": "真一文字",
      "answer": "まいちもんじ",
      "meaning": "straight, as the crow flies"
    },
    {
      "question": "探り合い",
      "answer": "さぐりあい",
      "meaning": "probe each other, sound each other out"
    },
    {
      "question": "飛鳥",
      "answer": "ひちょう",
      "meaning": "flying bird"
    },
    {
      "question": "怨恨",
      "answer": "えんこん",
      "meaning": "enmity, grudge"
    },
    {
      "question": "春風",
      "answer": "はるかぜ,しゅんぷう",
      "meaning": "spring breeze"
    },
    {
      "question": "老師",
      "answer": "ろうし",
      "meaning": "old priest, sage, (Zen) teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "潜水",
      "answer": "せんすい",
      "meaning": "diving, submerging, going underwater"
    },
    {
      "question": "休学",
      "answer": "きゅうがく",
      "meaning": "temporary absence from school"
    },
    {
      "question": "転用",
      "answer": "てんよう",
      "meaning": "diversion, putting something to another use"
    },
    {
      "question": "化かす",
      "answer": "ばかす",
      "meaning": "to bewitch, to confuse, to enchant, to delude"
    },
    {
      "question": "新田",
      "answer": "しんでん,あらた",
      "meaning": "new rice field, newly developed rice field, wasteland or marshland newly reclaimed as a rice field ("
    },
    {
      "question": "悪感情",
      "answer": "あくかんじょう,あっかんじょう",
      "meaning": "ill feeling, ill will, animosity, bad impression"
    },
    {
      "question": "養殖",
      "answer": "ようしょく",
      "meaning": "aquaculture, culture, cultivation, raising"
    },
    {
      "question": "自壊",
      "answer": "じかい",
      "meaning": "disintegration, self-destruction"
    },
    {
      "question": "英才教育",
      "answer": "えいさいきょういく",
      "meaning": "gifted education, special education for gifted children"
    },
    {
      "question": "洗い出す",
      "answer": "あらいだす",
      "meaning": "to reveal by washing the surface, to expose by washing away dirt, earth, etc., to discover (by inves"
    },
    {
      "question": "身の上話",
      "answer": "みのうえばなし",
      "meaning": "life story, personal narrative, story of one's life"
    },
    {
      "question": "胸当て",
      "answer": "むねあて,むなあて",
      "meaning": "breastplate, chest protector, bib"
    },
    {
      "question": "人好き",
      "answer": "ひとずき",
      "meaning": "attractiveness, charm, amiability"
    },
    {
      "question": "随時",
      "answer": "ずいじ",
      "meaning": "as needed, as occasion demands, at any time"
    },
    {
      "question": "気泡",
      "answer": "きほう",
      "meaning": "(air) bubble (esp. in a liquid)"
    },
    {
      "question": "遊び心",
      "answer": "あそびごころ",
      "meaning": "playfulness, playful mood, imaginativeness"
    },
    {
      "question": "開通",
      "answer": "かいつう",
      "meaning": "opening (of a new road, railway, etc.), going into operation (e.g. telephone communication), beginni"
    },
    {
      "question": "風呂敷",
      "answer": "ふろしき",
      "meaning": "wrapping cloth, cloth wrapper"
    },
    {
      "question": "要職",
      "answer": "ようしょく",
      "meaning": "important post, important office, key position"
    },
    {
      "question": "掃射",
      "answer": "そうしゃ",
      "meaning": "sweeping with fire, mowing down, strafing"
    },
    {
      "question": "黄身",
      "answer": "きみ",
      "meaning": "egg yolk"
    },
    {
      "question": "内訳",
      "answer": "うちわけ",
      "meaning": "itemization (of expenses), the items, breakdown, classification"
    },
    {
      "question": "風邪薬",
      "answer": "かぜぐすり,かざぐすり",
      "meaning": "remedy for a cold, cold medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "治",
      "answer": "ち",
      "meaning": "politics, government, administration, rule, peace, medical treatment, cure"
    },
    {
      "question": "売れ行き",
      "answer": "うれゆき",
      "meaning": "sales, demand"
    },
    {
      "question": "予定調和",
      "answer": "よていちょうわ",
      "meaning": "pre-established harmony (i.e. Leibniz' 'harmonie préétablie')"
    },
    {
      "question": "批評",
      "answer": "ひひょう",
      "meaning": "criticism, review, commentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "幸先",
      "answer": "さいさき",
      "meaning": "sign (of things to come), good omen, good sign"
    },
    {
      "question": "鯛",
      "answer": "たい",
      "meaning": "sea bream (Sparidae), porgy, tai (species of reddish-brown Pacific sea bream, Pagrus major)"
    },
    {
      "question": "抵触",
      "answer": "ていしょく",
      "meaning": "infringement (of a law, treaty, etc.), contravention, running afoul, conflict (with a theory, claim,"
    },
    {
      "question": "税収",
      "answer": "ぜいしゅう",
      "meaning": "tax yields, revenue"
    },
    {
      "question": "後光",
      "answer": "ごこう",
      "meaning": "halo, aureole, aureola, nimbus, halo (optical phenomenon), glory"
    },
    {
      "question": "時雨",
      "answer": "しぐれ,じう",
      "meaning": "rain shower in late autumn (fall) or early winter, seasonable rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "鼻面",
      "answer": "はなづら",
      "meaning": "muzzle, snout"
    },
    {
      "question": "菓子パン",
      "answer": "かしパン",
      "meaning": "baked sweet goods (e.g. anpan, melon bread, etc.), sweet pastry, sweet bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "挽く",
      "answer": "ひく",
      "meaning": "to saw, to grind (e.g. coffee beans), to mill"
    },
    {
      "question": "戸締り",
      "answer": "とじまり",
      "meaning": "locking up (doors and windows), fastening the doors"
    },
    {
      "question": "栄え",
      "answer": "はえ,さかえ",
      "meaning": "glory, splendour, honour, prosperity, flourishing, success"
    },
    {
      "question": "関西弁",
      "answer": "かんさいべん",
      "meaning": "Kansai dialect"
    },
    {
      "question": "心が動く",
      "answer": "こころがうごく",
      "meaning": "to take a fancy to something, to be moved, to feel inclined to"
    },
    {
      "question": "極々",
      "answer": "ごくごく",
      "meaning": "extremely, highly"
    },
    {
      "question": "母校",
      "answer": "ぼこう",
      "meaning": "alma mater"
    },
    {
      "question": "小男",
      "answer": "こおとこ",
      "meaning": "small man"
    },
    {
      "question": "朴念仁",
      "answer": "ぼくねんじん",
      "meaning": "quiet unsociable person, obstinate person, blockhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "調書",
      "answer": "ちょうしょ",
      "meaning": "protocol, written evidence, record (investigation, interrogation, etc.), preliminary memo, charge sh"
    },
    {
      "question": "方言",
      "answer": "ほうげん",
      "meaning": "dialect, provincialism"
    },
    {
      "question": "被疑者",
      "answer": "ひぎしゃ",
      "meaning": "suspect (person)"
    },
    {
      "question": "撃滅",
      "answer": "げきめつ",
      "meaning": "destruction, annihilation, extermination"
    },
    {
      "question": "八の字",
      "answer": "はちのじ",
      "meaning": "figure eight, figure of eight, shape of 'hachi', the kanji for eight"
    },
    {
      "question": "新婦",
      "answer": "しんぷ",
      "meaning": "bride"
    },
    {
      "question": "輪切り",
      "answer": "わぎり",
      "meaning": "cutting in round slices, round slice, dividing into groups (e.g. by ability)"
    },
    {
      "question": "打算的",
      "answer": "ださんてき",
      "meaning": "calculating, mercenary, selfish, self-interested"
    },
    {
      "question": "着水",
      "answer": "ちゃくすい",
      "meaning": "landing on water, hitting the water, splashdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "突き崩す",
      "answer": "つきくずす",
      "meaning": "to knock down, to tear down, to level, to raze, to crush (e.g. enemy), to throw into confusion, to r"
    },
    {
      "question": "課金",
      "answer": "かきん",
      "meaning": "charges, billing, paying for items in online games"
    },
    {
      "question": "総力",
      "answer": "そうりょく",
      "meaning": "total energy, all efforts"
    },
    {
      "question": "人名",
      "answer": "じんめい",
      "meaning": "person's name"
    },
    {
      "question": "特質",
      "answer": "とくしつ",
      "meaning": "characteristic, feature, special quality"
    },
    {
      "question": "際する",
      "answer": "さいする",
      "meaning": "to arrive, to come to pass"
    },
    {
      "question": "女児",
      "answer": "じょじ",
      "meaning": "baby girl, primary schoolgirl"
    },
    {
      "question": "立会人",
      "answer": "たちあいにん",
      "meaning": "witness, observer"
    },
    {
      "question": "薬が効く",
      "answer": "やくがきく",
      "meaning": "to have medicine be effective"
    },
    {
      "question": "無類",
      "answer": "むるい",
      "meaning": "matchless, unequalled, unequaled"
    },
    {
      "question": "膠着",
      "answer": "こうちゃく",
      "meaning": "agglutination, adhesion, deadlock, stalemate, standstill"
    },
    {
      "question": "輿入れ",
      "answer": "こしいれ",
      "meaning": "wedding, bridal procession, marriage into a family"
    },
    {
      "question": "通し",
      "answer": "とおし,どおし",
      "meaning": "continuing from beginning to end, continuous run, consecutive run, appetizer, starter, hors d'oeuvre"
    },
    {
      "question": "頭を捻る",
      "answer": "あたまをひねる",
      "meaning": "to puzzle over, to think deeply about, to rack one's brains over (wrack)"
    },
    {
      "question": "錠前",
      "answer": "じょうまえ",
      "meaning": "lock"
    },
    {
      "question": "前払い",
      "answer": "まえばらい",
      "meaning": "payment in advance, prepayment"
    },
    {
      "question": "不平等",
      "answer": "ふびょうどう",
      "meaning": "inequality, unfairness"
    },
    {
      "question": "才女",
      "answer": "さいじょ",
      "meaning": "talented woman"
    },
    {
      "question": "取り立て",
      "answer": "とりたて",
      "meaning": "collection (e.g. of a debt), dunning, selection (for a position), exceptional promotion, patronage,"
    },
    {
      "question": "痩せ細る",
      "answer": "やせほそる",
      "meaning": "to lose weight, to become thin, to wither away"
    },
    {
      "question": "捻くれる",
      "answer": "ひねくれる",
      "meaning": "to become twisted, to grow distorted, to be curved, to bend, to get sulky, to sulk, to grow bitter,"
    },
    {
      "question": "罵り",
      "answer": "ののしり",
      "meaning": "abuse, curse, swearing, insult"
    },
    {
      "question": "小手先",
      "answer": "こてさき",
      "meaning": "tip of the hand, (use of) one's hands, cheap trick, superficial wit, superficial cleverness, cheap,"
    },
    {
      "question": "般若",
      "answer": "はんにゃ",
      "meaning": "prajna, wisdom required to attain enlightenment, noh mask of a grinning, horned demoness (represents"
    },
    {
      "question": "論争",
      "answer": "ろんそう",
      "meaning": "dispute, controversy"
    },
    {
      "question": "船舶",
      "answer": "せんぱく",
      "meaning": "vessel, ship, shipping, seacraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "仕事柄",
      "answer": "しごとがら",
      "meaning": "for work, in a manner related to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "道具屋",
      "answer": "どうぐや",
      "meaning": "second-hand shop, curio shop"
    },
    {
      "question": "剣豪",
      "answer": "けんごう",
      "meaning": "master fencer"
    },
    {
      "question": "孵化",
      "answer": "ふか",
      "meaning": "incubation, hatching"
    },
    {
      "question": "汐",
      "answer": "しお",
      "meaning": "tide, current, sea water, opportunity, chance"
    },
    {
      "question": "秘密主義",
      "answer": "ひみつしゅぎ",
      "meaning": "secretiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "比重",
      "answer": "ひじゅう",
      "meaning": "specific gravity, relative density, relative importance, weight"
    },
    {
      "question": "至近",
      "answer": "しきん",
      "meaning": "very near"
    },
    {
      "question": "提携",
      "answer": "ていけい",
      "meaning": "cooperation, tie-up, joint business, partnership, alliance, sponsorship"
    },
    {
      "question": "資本",
      "answer": "しほん",
      "meaning": "funds, capital"
    },
    {
      "question": "鏃",
      "answer": "やじり",
      "meaning": "arrowhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒飲み",
      "answer": "さけのみ",
      "meaning": "(heavy) drinker, drunkard, tippler, boozer"
    },
    {
      "question": "開祖",
      "answer": "かいそ",
      "meaning": "(sect) founder, apostle, originator, inventor"
    },
    {
      "question": "本邸",
      "answer": "ほんてい",
      "meaning": "principal residence"
    },
    {
      "question": "害獣",
      "answer": "がいじゅう",
      "meaning": "harmful animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "心臓部",
      "answer": "しんぞうぶ",
      "meaning": "central part"
    },
    {
      "question": "自生",
      "answer": "じせい",
      "meaning": "growing wild (naturally), native"
    },
    {
      "question": "文通",
      "answer": "ぶんつう",
      "meaning": "correspondence, exchange of letters"
    },
    {
      "question": "格言",
      "answer": "かくげん",
      "meaning": "saying, maxim, aphorism, proverb"
    },
    {
      "question": "感受性",
      "answer": "かんじゅせい",
      "meaning": "sensitivity, susceptibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "宿場町",
      "answer": "しゅくばまち",
      "meaning": "inn town, post town, post-station town"
    },
    {
      "question": "平衡感覚",
      "answer": "へいこうかんかく",
      "meaning": "sense of equilibrium, sense of balance"
    },
    {
      "question": "船首",
      "answer": "せんしゅ",
      "meaning": "bow (of boat), prow, stem"
    },
    {
      "question": "贖う",
      "answer": "あがなう",
      "meaning": "to atone for, to expiate, to redeem, to make up for, to compensate for"
    },
    {
      "question": "有耶無耶",
      "answer": "うやむや",
      "meaning": "indefinite, hazy, vague, unsettled, undecided"
    },
    {
      "question": "総理大臣",
      "answer": "そうりだいじん",
      "meaning": "prime minister (as the head of a cabinet government), premier"
    },
    {
      "question": "過激派",
      "answer": "かげきは",
      "meaning": "radical party, extremists"
    },
    {
      "question": "低空",
      "answer": "ていくう",
      "meaning": "low altitude, low sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "上様",
      "answer": "うえさま,うえざま,かみさま",
      "meaning": "emperor, shogun, honored person (honoured), (another person's) wife"
    },
    {
      "question": "転化",
      "answer": "てんか",
      "meaning": "change, transformation, inversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "中程",
      "answer": "なかほど",
      "meaning": "(about) middle, midway"
    },
    {
      "question": "人探し",
      "answer": "ひとさがし",
      "meaning": "searching for someone, search for a missing person, searching for a (job) candidate, recruitment, sc"
    },
    {
      "question": "帝位",
      "answer": "ていい",
      "meaning": "imperial throne, the Crown"
    },
    {
      "question": "滑り台",
      "answer": "すべりだい",
      "meaning": "(playground) slide, (ship) launching platform, sliding bed"
    },
    {
      "question": "仏教",
      "answer": "ぶっきょう",
      "meaning": "Buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "革張り",
      "answer": "かわばり",
      "meaning": "leather-covered"
    },
    {
      "question": "伯母さん",
      "answer": "おばさん",
      "meaning": "aunt"
    },
    {
      "question": "実弾",
      "answer": "じつだん",
      "meaning": "live bullets, live ammunition, ball cartridge, money"
    },
    {
      "question": "楚々",
      "answer": "そそ",
      "meaning": "graceful, neat"
    },
    {
      "question": "訝る",
      "answer": "いぶかる",
      "meaning": "to wonder, to puzzle oneself about, to feel anxious about, to suspect, to doubt"
    },
    {
      "question": "提言",
      "answer": "ていげん",
      "meaning": "proposal, motion, recommendation"
    },
    {
      "question": "拡声器",
      "answer": "かくせいき",
      "meaning": "megaphone, bullhorn, loudhailer"
    },
    {
      "question": "一躍",
      "answer": "いちやく",
      "meaning": "suddenly (rising to fame, etc.), instantly, immediately, overnight, one bound, one leap"
    },
    {
      "question": "随意",
      "answer": "ずいい,ずい",
      "meaning": "voluntary, optional, free, elective"
    },
    {
      "question": "凌辱",
      "answer": "りょうじょく",
      "meaning": "insult, affront, disgrace, indignity, sexual assault, rape"
    },
    {
      "question": "尚且つ",
      "answer": "なおかつ",
      "meaning": "besides, furthermore, on top of that, and yet, nevertheless, even so"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛮勇",
      "answer": "ばんゆう",
      "meaning": "foolhardiness, recklessness, savage valour, savage valor, brute courage"
    },
    {
      "question": "文武両道",
      "answer": "ぶんぶりょうどう",
      "meaning": "being accomplished in both the literary and military arts, doing well in both school and sports"
    },
    {
      "question": "主将",
      "answer": "しゅしょう",
      "meaning": "commander-in-chief, supreme commander, captain (of a team)"
    },
    {
      "question": "委託",
      "answer": "いたく",
      "meaning": "entrusting (something to a person), consignment (of goods), putting in someone's charge, trust, comm"
    },
    {
      "question": "打ち身",
      "answer": "うちみ",
      "meaning": "bruise"
    },
    {
      "question": "腰掛け",
      "answer": "こしかけ",
      "meaning": "seat, bench, temporary job while looking for a better job or until one marries"
    },
    {
      "question": "泡を食う",
      "answer": "あわをくう",
      "meaning": "to be flurried, to be confused, to lose one's head"
    },
    {
      "question": "ガラス瓶",
      "answer": "ガラスびん",
      "meaning": "glass bottle, glass jar, phial, vial"
    },
    {
      "question": "出題",
      "answer": "しゅつだい",
      "meaning": "setting a question (for an exam, quiz, etc.), setting a theme (for composition of poetry)"
    },
    {
      "question": "無精髭",
      "answer": "ぶしょうひげ",
      "meaning": "stubble, unshaven face, beard one has because one is too lazy to shave, 5-o'clock shadow"
    },
    {
      "question": "没する",
      "answer": "ぼっする",
      "meaning": "to sink, to go down, to set, to pass away, to die, to disappear, to vanish, to confiscate"
    },
    {
      "question": "競売",
      "answer": "きょうばい,けいばい",
      "meaning": "auction"
    },
    {
      "question": "確たる",
      "answer": "かくたる",
      "meaning": "certain, definite, clear, credible"
    },
    {
      "question": "軍備",
      "answer": "ぐんび",
      "meaning": "armaments, military preparations"
    },
    {
      "question": "出社",
      "answer": "しゅっしゃ",
      "meaning": "going to work (e.g. in the morning), coming to work"
    },
    {
      "question": "締め出す",
      "answer": "しめだす",
      "meaning": "to shut out, to bar, to lock out, to exclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "抗弁",
      "answer": "こうべん",
      "meaning": "protest, refutation, pleading"
    },
    {
      "question": "名手",
      "answer": "めいしゅ",
      "meaning": "master, expert, expert board game player (chess, go, shogi, etc.)"
    },
    {
      "question": "恋愛関係",
      "answer": "れんあいかんけい",
      "meaning": "love affair, love relationship"
    },
    {
      "question": "起る",
      "answer": "おこる",
      "meaning": "to occur, to happen"
    },
    {
      "question": "刊行",
      "answer": "かんこう",
      "meaning": "publication, issue"
    },
    {
      "question": "迷走",
      "answer": "めいそう",
      "meaning": "straying, wandering off course"
    },
    {
      "question": "寝惚ける",
      "answer": "ねぼける",
      "meaning": "to be still half asleep, to be half awake, to be not yet quite awake"
    },
    {
      "question": "仁義",
      "answer": "じんぎ",
      "meaning": "humanity and justice (esp. in Confucianism), virtue, duty, formal greeting (between yakuza, street v"
    },
    {
      "question": "底力",
      "answer": "そこぢから",
      "meaning": "hidden reserves of strength, latent energy, potentiality, real strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "尖端",
      "answer": "せんたん",
      "meaning": "pointed end, tip, point, cusp (of a leaf, crescent moon, etc.), apex (of a curve), forefront, vangua"
    },
    {
      "question": "単一",
      "answer": "たんいつ,たんいち",
      "meaning": "single, simple, sole, individual, unitary, D battery, D cell"
    },
    {
      "question": "訳が無い",
      "answer": "わけがない",
      "meaning": "there is no way that ..., easy, simple"
    },
    {
      "question": "草地",
      "answer": "くさち,そうち",
      "meaning": "grassland, meadow"
    },
    {
      "question": "実入り",
      "answer": "みいり",
      "meaning": "crop, harvest, ripeness, income, profits, loaded (e.g. intermodal containers in the transport indust"
    },
    {
      "question": "無一文",
      "answer": "むいちもん",
      "meaning": "penniless, broke"
    },
    {
      "question": "神頼み",
      "answer": "かみだのみ",
      "meaning": "entreaty to a deity"
    },
    {
      "question": "夜行性",
      "answer": "やこうせい",
      "meaning": "nocturnality, nocturnal habits"
    }
  ]}